<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Graphic Design on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/graphic-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Graphic Design on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/graphic-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>An Early Touchpoint</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/wacom-tablet-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/wacom-tablet-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: There was once a time when I worked in graphic design—mostly in newspapers—and as a result of that, I owned a tablet. For drawing, of course. It didn’t have a screen. I wasn’t a great artist by any means, but that little Wacom device was a nice functionality add when I was tweaking cutouts and hopping into Photoshop or Illustrator. (I’m pretty good at cutouts if I do say so myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brand bastardizations</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/brand-bastardizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/brand-bastardizations/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Last week, the internet collectively threw McDonald&amp;rsquo;s a nostalgic bone. On January 20th, a reporter for Canada.com reminded the Northern Hemisphere of the obscure phenomenon that was the McPizza, a food item that most people probably forgot existed—especially if those people were American. (It was largely a Canadian phenomenon.) But, as it turns out, two franchise locations in Ohio and West Virginia still sell the pies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMYK All The Way</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/color-printing-lithography-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/color-printing-lithography-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: In the 1990s, after much delay, the newspaper industry’s largest and most prominent newspapers finally started printing most of their pages in color on a regular basis. It was a much delayed phenomenon, driven less by a lack of technology and more by a mixture of cost and tradition. In 1993, The New York Times printed its first page in color, far later than most of the rest of the newspaper industry, and the only other big holdouts at that point were The Wall Street Journal and The Washington Post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clippy Couture</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/clip-art-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/clip-art-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Art is everywhere. It’s easier to access than it’s ever been. All you need to do to access art is to turn on your search engine of choice—Google, Flickr, Giphy—and start searching. The hard part of this, of course, is that this art is often copyrighted, and while there are cases where the copyright is a bit more loosey-goosey (thank you, Creative Commons), many times, if you’re trying to print off a flyer or newsletter for your local sect of Satanists, you might need a free alternative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forget Rand Paul, Let&#39;s Talk Paul Rand</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/rand-paul-paul-rand-logo-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/rand-paul-paul-rand-logo-design/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: A horrible thing has happened to search results in recent months. If you do a Google search for Paul Rand, nearly half the results on the first page—and all of the Google News results—are about Rand Paul, a man who has little to do with graceful, iconic logo design. In fact, if you actually knew something about logo design, you might be disappointed by Rand&amp;rsquo;s campaign logo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I believe in symmetry</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/i-believe-in-symmetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/i-believe-in-symmetry/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: The internet is full of dumb debates (as we all know), but a recent iPhone/Android argument took the cake for a lot of people. This week, _iMore_ editor-in-chief Rene Ritchie made the argument that Samsung&amp;rsquo;s Galaxy S6 phone was a worse phone than the iPhone because, unlike Apple&amp;rsquo;s device, the alignment of its ports was off. No, really. He suggested that it was a sign of shoddy craftsmanship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outside-the-Bottle Thinking</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/bottle-design-outside-the-bottle-thinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/bottle-design-outside-the-bottle-thinking/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: It may be the most famous hard-to-read bottle in history. For generations, Dr. Bronner&amp;rsquo;s 18-in-1 Pure Castile Soap has become an essential tool for many looking to stay clean without the extra chemicals they throw into more main-line soaps. But all the benefits that come with the soap (it&amp;rsquo;s highly concentrated, it&amp;rsquo;s effective at getting you clean) are joined by Emanuel Bronner&amp;rsquo;s unusual opinions about just about everything—particularly his unique take on religion called the &amp;ldquo;Moral ABC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Painting Outside The Lines</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/paint-shop-pro-shareware-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/paint-shop-pro-shareware-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: The dream of shareware, as previously discussed, was simply this: As long as you could put a good taste of a product onto a floppy disk, you could theoretically compete with companies ten times your size. Or bigger. It leveled the playing field for distribution, and that meant even if you were building an app in your living room on your night off while eating the cheapest ramen you could find, you could still feasibly take on giant software companies that can afford to promote themselves on television.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>