<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Television on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/television/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Television on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/television/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Distinguished Panel</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/panel-show-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/panel-show-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey guys, Ernie here with another piece from Andrew Egan about something nerdy and televised, two things we do well here at Tedium. (His last piece was a daily one about Beer Nuts.) Read on for more!
[big]Today in Tedium: Television programming has long been a rotating series of common staples. Talk shows, games shows, court shows, and soap operas air during the day. Sitcoms, dramas, and reality competitions (which are somehow distinct from game shows) dominate prime time hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Institute You Can’t Disparage</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/married-with-children-terry-rakolta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/married-with-children-terry-rakolta/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: The culture wars never really went away, but in an era when gun violence and online censorship are once again becoming hot topics in the news, now feels like a great time to discuss one of the greatest sources of controversy of the past 30 years—Married … With Children, an edge-busting TV sitcom that predated the Streisand Effect but may have been one of its earliest examples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Between the Bars</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/movie-letterboxing-pan-scan-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/movie-letterboxing-pan-scan-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Taking an experience like going to the movies and converting it to your living room is a hugely controversial thing, despite the fact we&amp;rsquo;ve been doing it for decades. Rich guy and wannabe disruptor Sean Parker is learning this the hard way, thanks to his efforts to sell a product called Screening Room. The service would allow homes access to first-run movies through a set-top box for a price of $50 a pop—not cheap at all, but potentially cheaper than a night at the movies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy, Don’t Rent</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/rent-to-own-rent-a-center-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/rent-to-own-rent-a-center-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Spend the weekend buying junk in honor of Black Friday and Cyber Monday? Lucky you. Whether your addiction of choice was Michaels, Macy’s, or Massdrop, hopefully you found just the right kind of crap. Of course, one of the key ways to sell crap is to draw people in with a TV, a laptop, or something else that’s shiny with a screen. But what if you’re trying to simply make ends need and you need a TV set or furniture?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dots Vs. Pixels</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/dots-per-inch-pixels-per-inch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/dots-per-inch-pixels-per-inch/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: If you stare into the heart of your smartphone for a while, you may start to make out the pixels. If your smartphone is really old, like the original iPhone or a cheap Android phone, that might not take a while, because the pixel resolution is quite low. But if you have an iPhone X, with its 458ppi (pixels per inch) OLED screen, perhaps it might not be so easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Effects</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/why-airport-stores-are-named-after-tv-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/why-airport-stores-are-named-after-tv-networks/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey all! In lieu of a new piece, tonight’s Tedium is a lightly updated classic edition discussing one of the weirdest phenomena you’ll see at the airport: The naming conventions of the stores. Admit it, you’re curious.
[big]Today in Tedium: When you travel to different places—in the U.S. in particular, perhaps less so outside of it—the airports often feel like they’re designed of a single piece of cloth, despite the fact that they’re most certainly not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Annoying National Upgrade</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/digital-television-upgrade-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/digital-television-upgrade-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: The move of the television airwaves from analog to digital in 2009 was perhaps the most unusual case of planned obsolescence in the modern age. Here was a decision, mandated by the Telecommunications Act of 1996 and forced upon hundreds of millions of people at once, that threw lots of people out of their routine. Many folks weren&amp;rsquo;t ready, or maybe they didn&amp;rsquo;t care enough about their TV signal quality to upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solved</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/unsolved-mysteries-modern-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/unsolved-mysteries-modern-updates/</guid>
      <description>[big]More than 30 years ago, onetime Eliot Ness stand-in Robert Stack found a way to embellish his legacy in the modern era.[/big]
The solution was through a show named Unsolved Mysteries, one of the first reality-based shows of the modern era, mixing scripted plots with true stories. First appearing as a special in 1987, it became a full-fledged series not long after the success of a similar program, America’s Most Wanted on Fox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV’s Hidden Math</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/tv-programming-quirks-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/tv-programming-quirks-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: It’s often said about the current era of television that it’s an embarrassment of riches, one of the best eras of television of all time, in part because the floodgates have bumped up the quality quotient. Netflix creates so much stuff (some great, much average) that we’re unaware of nearly all of it! It’s weird to think about, but both cable TV and local syndication had a similar effect on television in the ’80s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Four-Minute Villain</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/batman-tv-show-commercial-length/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/batman-tv-show-commercial-length/</guid>
      <description>One of the best parts of the streaming era is that you can avoid watching a ton of commercials if you don’t want to.
And in some ways, TV is responding to this change. Last year, Turner announced it was cutting back on commercials on its cable channels, and Fox—currently the market leader in commercial clutter—is trying to do the same. These days, 15 minutes of commercials in a single hour, give or take a couple of minutes, is about average.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Internet Will Be Televised</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/webtv-history-20th-anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/webtv-history-20th-anniversary/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Terrible product ideas are a dime a dozen, but what about ideas that are fascinating, and perhaps executionally sound, but conceptually flawed? How often do they come about? And how often is it that they stick around the market for 17 years, despite fairly limited public interest? Such is the case of WebTV, the set-top device that allowed you to surf a television-optimized version of the web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Invisible Puzzle</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/wireless-spectrum-allocation-challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/wireless-spectrum-allocation-challenges/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Barring our constant debates on net neutrality, one of the places where the Federal Communications Commission has the largest footprint is with our wireless spectrum. It’s a spectrum that has to serve many minders, and there are constant complaints about the spectrum being crowded. But those complaints, despite feeling modern and up-to-date, are far from new—we’ve been dealing with them pretty much ever since there was spectrum regulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lazarus Libraries</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/lost-and-found-film-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/lost-and-found-film-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey all, Ernie here with a piece from Andrew Egan, who is following his recent interest in film in a couple of new directions this time around. Check out what he found.
[big]Today in Tedium: Among the many pieces of dubious “evidence” cited by conspiracy theorists that say the moon landing was faked is the fact that the tapes of the original transmission were erased over. Surely, if America had actually landed on the moon those recordings would be an invaluable part of human history and not treated so carelessly as to be erased on accident years later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Old Scandal</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/bob-vila-this-old-house-departure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/bob-vila-this-old-house-departure/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: In an era when HGTV has turned home repair into a lasting form of light entertainment and figures like Property Brothers Jonathan and Drew Scott and Fixer Upper power couple Chip and Joanna Gaines into big-name public figures and experts at monetizing their names and work, it’s worth remembering the foundation for this approach—specifically, the home-repair experts that came before. One of those experts is a guy by the name of Bob Vila.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Too Terrible For Television</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/weird-unsold-television-pilots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/weird-unsold-television-pilots/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: The idea that there should be limits on the quality of what ends up on or TV screens is a common one that’s been around for ages. Hell, that’s why one of the defining shows of the 1980s is called You Can’t Do That On Television. Which is why, in a weird way, it kind of makes sense that many of the new shows actually getting on the air in 2017 are actually revivals of successful ones—including, as was just announced, Will and Grace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Universal Themes</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/universal-remote-control-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/universal-remote-control-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: The remote control was an important invention, not just because it saved the average person a couple of steps, but because it shares a clear lineage with every other handheld electronics device ever made. Your smartphone looks like it does because of the remote control. But less heralded—perhaps because of its roots as an aftermarket device—is the universal remote control, a device that made millions of devices that work similarly but are slightly different bend to its will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waaaaay Left of the Dial</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/frankenfm-radio-fcc-analog-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/frankenfm-radio-fcc-analog-tv/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: TV on the Radio isn&amp;rsquo;t just the name of a really freaking good band. Instead, it&amp;rsquo;s a quirk of the design of analog television. But a funny thing happened on the way to obscurity: As analog TV gave way to digital, a handful of risk-taking broadcasters, sensing an opportunity, have started to run those analog TV stations as FM radio stations—big FCC plans be damned. The shift is surprisingly contentious in the world of broadcast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebTV’s Greatest Celebrity User</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/r-stevie-moore-webtv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/r-stevie-moore-webtv/</guid>
      <description>[big]R. Stevie Moore is an extraordinary archivist of his own material. Recently, the online short film series Great Big Story released a superb mini documentary about Stevie and on April 6, 2018, R. Stevie Moore was featured on the front page of Wikipedia.[/big]
The page asked “Did you know R. Stevie Moore pioneered modern indie rock, earning him the sobriquet ‘the godfather of home recording?’”
Yes, Wikipedia. I believe we already knew that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s Your Gimmick?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/television-history-gimmicks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/television-history-gimmicks/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: These days, it seems like TV is all about gimmicks: Think reality shows, TV shows that recap the TV shows that literally just aired, limited series designed to recycle old hit shows, and even live theatre productions like The Wiz. TV executives are like P.T. Barnum-style hucksters, willing to try anything to keep us watching. And it&amp;rsquo;s always been that way, honestly—if they can make watching your boob tube into an &amp;ldquo;event,&amp;rdquo; they know they&amp;rsquo;ve sucked you in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Nobody Knows Your Name</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/tv-show-theme-song-composers-anonymous/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/tv-show-theme-song-composers-anonymous/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: One of the last acts of David Bowie, supreme rock star of the past 50 years who died Monday morning, was the release of his album, Blackstar. One of the ways Bowie promoted the closing chapter of his work was by doing something that he hadn&amp;rsquo;t done much of over the years: he gave the title track to the album to the producers of The Last Panthers, a new TV show in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Secret Amiga</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/cable-prevue-channel-secret-amiga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/cable-prevue-channel-secret-amiga/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: In terms of finding out what&amp;rsquo;s on the boob tube at any given time, we&amp;rsquo;ve come a long way from the overly condensed pages of TV Guide. In fact, the magazine was already looking awful obsolete in the 1980s and 1990s, when cable systems around the country began dedicating entire channels to listing TV schedules. Eventually, the approach led to the rise of the set-top box, the power-sucking block that serves as the liaison between you and your cable company.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>