<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Retro Gaming on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/retro-gaming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Retro Gaming on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 05:57:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/retro-gaming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Duck, Duck, Goose?</title>
      <link>/2018/07/18/duck-hunt-modern-mallard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 05:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/18/duck-hunt-modern-mallard/</guid>
      <description>The NES Zapper holds a unique place in pop culture. A gaming gimmick with somewhat limited support, the light gun, which worked by responding to a flash of light on a screen, carries a very specific sense of nostalgia for many because it was a very common pack-in cart for the Nintendo device.  It would never be released in its current form today—its somewhat realistic gun shape would never fly in 2018, in no small part because of the Lazer Tag saga that partly did in Nintendo’s one-time partner Worlds of Wonder—but it’s an amazing piece of nostalgia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What if Tedium … Had Lyrics?</title>
      <link>/2018/06/14/brentalfloss-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 06:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/14/brentalfloss-interview/</guid>
      <description>As our readers are now undoubtedly aware, there are two things I’m incredibly interested in—unique types of music and the history/technical aspects/playing the games of the original Nintendo Entertainment System (I’m also really into miniatures, FWIW). Knowing this, it was only a matter of time before I discovered someone who combined these two interests into one. Unlike U2, circa 1987, I found what I was looking for almost a decade ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Still Rocks</title>
      <link>/2018/05/18/nintendo-nes-chiptune-music-scene/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/18/nintendo-nes-chiptune-music-scene/</guid>
      <description>Hey all, Ernie here with another piece from David Buck, who&amp;rsquo;s currently in the midst of following his Nintendo muse. Feel free to follow along with him!
Today in Tedium: Gamers of a certain age may remember the opening notes of Super Mario Bros as well—or perhaps better than—any other song from their childhoods. As the pack-in title for the original Nintendo Entertainment System, the game was likely the first exposure to video games many of us had outside of arcades and Atari.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s New To You</title>
      <link>/2018/03/30/funcoland-history-used-video-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 07:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/30/funcoland-history-used-video-games/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In an era when digital storage is basically unlimited and space is running out by the second, there’s still a basic charm to physical objects that we’ve yet to really lose. Video games are a great example of this. Despite the fact that you can literally download any game under the sun and play it instantly, there is a quite healthy business online and elsewhere for physical product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharper Pixels</title>
      <link>/2017/12/01/analogue-super-nt-premium-retro-gaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/01/analogue-super-nt-premium-retro-gaming/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Recently, I had a big problem really put a damper on my retro-gaming experience. After modding my Super NES Classic, I proceeded to play one of my all-time favorite games, The Legend of the Mystical Ninja. I got all the way up to level 5, but when I ran into that level’s boss, something strange happened: The entire system crashed, hard. What happened? Well, the Super NES Classic’s emulator couldn’t handle what was on the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super FX Turbo Mode</title>
      <link>/2017/08/22/star-fox-super-fx-overclocking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 06:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/22/star-fox-super-fx-overclocking/</guid>
      <description>I’m going to come right out and say it: I want a Super NES Classic. I wanted an NES Classic, but that sold out too quickly and the variations on the market cost way too much money, so I have my finger on the trigger for potential pre-orders of the new device, expected to hit this week. I, like most of my other fellow retro geeks, can at least embrace the fact that we still have as much of a shot at getting these mini-consoles right now as we did Pearl Jam tickets circa 1994.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>