<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Musical Instruments on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/musical-instruments/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Musical Instruments on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 09:42:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/musical-instruments/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Big Idea, Synthesized</title>
      <link>/2016/11/18/casio-keyboards-casiotone-cultural-impact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/11/18/casio-keyboards-casiotone-cultural-impact/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In the late 1970s, a man who had changed the business world by turning massive calculators into handheld devices decided that he wanted to scratch another itch. And with that itch scratched, he introduced a world of creativity to bedroom warriors around the country—a set of training wheels to the musically inclined. The devices he created proudly ignored their weaknesses and succeeded despite themselves. And they even inspired pop culture in ways big and small.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre String Theories</title>
      <link>/2016/05/20/prepared-guitar-bizarre-string-theories/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/05/20/prepared-guitar-bizarre-string-theories/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Of the many fascinating experiments on the internet these days involving red hot nickel balls, my personal favorite is this one, involving two guitars. This clip, apparently inspired by nickel-ball innovator Matthew Neuland&amp;rsquo;s uncle, at first attempted to show whether a fiery nickel ball would put the guitar out of tune. Then Neuland used the nickel ball to destroy the strings. It&amp;rsquo;s far from the first example of someone messing with guitar strings just to see what might happen—in fact, there&amp;rsquo;s something of a whole subgenre of guitar playing based on the concept of modifying or breaking guitars in unusual ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searching for the perfect tones</title>
      <link>/2015/04/29/unusual-musical-instruments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/04/29/unusual-musical-instruments/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: If you&amp;rsquo;ve never seen a 12-foot-tall upright piano, you&amp;rsquo;re in for a treat. The neo-classical German musician Nils Frahm recorded his latest album, Solo, on such a device, the Klavins Model 370. Frahm told Pitchfork that the experience was so inspiring that he wanted to launch a crowdfunding effort to help the piano&amp;rsquo;s creator, David Klavins, build an even taller instrument. (Read about that here.) Today, inspired by Frahm&amp;rsquo;s excitement, we want to talk about some incredibly bizarre instruments.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>