<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t mess with the Michelin Man</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/michelin-guide-unusual-side-businesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/michelin-guide-unusual-side-businesses/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: The problem with giving anyone on the street the right to review a restaurant is that he or she can easily be influenced by the wider political or social climate in setting their review score. When it comes to Yelp, the way the wind blows has a ton of influence on the final rating, something Indiana&amp;rsquo;s Memories Pizza learned the hard way when they took a stance in favor of the state&amp;rsquo;s controversial religious freedom law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything Must Go</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/liquidation-sales-everything-must-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/liquidation-sales-everything-must-go/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a great deal on athletic goods and live in a big city on the East Coast, your best option may perhaps be City Sports. The athletic chain, which has been around for more than 30 years, announced earlier this month that it was closing its doors, ensuring this Black Friday is a little bit more of a Bleak Friday for fans of italicized Helvetica type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ted Turner&#39;s Satellite Of Love</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/ted-turner-tbs-superstation-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/ted-turner-tbs-superstation-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: For a brief moment in time, independent local television stations held an impressive level of power over the country as a whole. They could share regional messages with national audiences, advertise to millions more people than they ever could on their crusty UHF signals, and punch far above their potential. The era of the superstation is past, but it undeniably had a massive effect on cable television.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gift Of Abstraction</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/gift-cards-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/gift-cards-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: You ever run into a situation where you return something to a store, and the only option that you have available to you is to receive the balance as a gift card? Certainly, this is a frustrating state of affairs, especially if it’s a store you don’t particularly like. Despite that, the gift card—a retail phenomenon that came out of nowhere slightly more than two decades ago to redefine our relationship with gifts—has become a hugely popular industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Neighbors You Love to Hate</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/homeowners-associations-ruin-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/homeowners-associations-ruin-everything/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: You probably don’t need to read it from me to know that homeowners associations are pretty much the worst thing ever to happen to neighborhoods, but in case you need more evidence, 11-year-old Sara Marston has plenty. Marston found out recently that a popular Halloween display in her neighborhood wouldn’t go up this year due to a set of restrictions specifically targeting that house. She put up an online petition, hoping she would get 100 supporters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Shell Game</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/shell-companies-easy-to-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/shell-companies-easy-to-launch/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Last week, the journalists at the Las Vegas Review-Journal had a problem: Their newspaper had a new owner, but they couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out who the hell it was. After roughly a week of reporting, they finally figured out exactly who spent $140 million on the paper—one Sheldon Adelson, the casino owner and major Republican donor—but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t easy to get quite that far. Thanks to the law, there was nothing requiring the owner to come forward and reveal themselves to the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trimmed For Space</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/newspaper-newsprint-cuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/newspaper-newsprint-cuts/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
_Editor’s note: Tonight’s Tedium is an updated rerun of a classic issue about the stuff that newspapers get rid of when trying to slim down. Unspoken in this article: Usually, the final step of this process is people. And with the recent sagas of L.A. Weekly and (on the digital side of things) DNAinfo, now felt like a good time to revisit. (If you&amp;rsquo;ve read before, keep reading; there&amp;rsquo;s a new section on newsprint.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>