<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Libraries on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/libraries/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Libraries on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/libraries/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey, I Shrunk The Page</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/microfiche-microfilm-libraries-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/microfiche-microfilm-libraries-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Do me a favor while you read these opening lines. Pick up your phone, and open up your photos app. Scroll through the many pictures of you, your dumb friends, and your crazy family. Pick a photo—it can be any photo, really, and blow it up so it fills the whole screen. Still with me? Good. Now, tell me, how would you recreate this experience using physical devices alone—where you flipped through thousands of tiny images and blew up a really big one to a size where you can actually read it without (and here&amp;rsquo;s the key part) destroying the original?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Windex Problem</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/information-literacy-students-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/information-literacy-students-problem/</guid>
      <description>[big]If you’ve been a longtime reader of Tedium, you’ve probably noticed that my byline shows up most of the time. Maybe 80 to 90 percent of the time.[/big]
In part, this is because this is my project, and I limit the number of things we publish every month. Also in part, it&amp;rsquo;s because I feel uncomfortable with having writers work for me for free. (The one person I do have writing outside pieces, Andrew Egan, has actually been getting paid for them!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>