<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Movie Industry on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/movie-industry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Movie Industry on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 07:31:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/movie-industry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sound and the Fury</title>
      <link>/2018/08/01/indiana-jones-sound-design-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 07:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/01/indiana-jones-sound-design-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey all, Ernie here with a piece from Andrew Egan about a specific kind of movie magic—the kind you hear, whether during a dramatic fall or the crack of a whip. Enjoy!
Today in Tedium: Returning to my sunny little Brooklyn apartment a few weeks ago, I heard a familiar sound coming from my living room. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t music or dialogue but the second I heard it, I knew exactly what one of my roommates was watching in our living room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lazies</title>
      <link>/2018/01/23/the-razzies-lazy-nominations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 07:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/23/the-razzies-lazy-nominations/</guid>
      <description>The Golden Raspberry Awards are one of our greatest homespun counterculture traditions, one that set the stage for appreciation of bad film on a mainstream scale. While it didn’t change the world, it’s certainly an important institution.  But the award ceremony, which has always been designed as a way to piggyback on the attention of the Academy Awards, may be at a point where it its relevance is hitting rock-bottom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Copyright Goes Copywrong</title>
      <link>/2017/10/25/public-domain-film-history-copyright/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/25/public-domain-film-history-copyright/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: When horror movie icon George A. Romero died earlier this year, it should have started a copyright expiration timeline for his most famous and influential work, the 1968 classic and Halloween icon Night of the Living Dead. But something really scary happened to the film before it became a hit: Due to a last-second title change and a distributor error, the former Night of the Flesh Eaters fell into the public domain upon its release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Yourself A Treat</title>
      <link>/2017/08/16/lets-all-go-lobby-movie-snipe-advertising/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 07:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/16/lets-all-go-lobby-movie-snipe-advertising/</guid>
      <description>Editor’s note: Hey all, Ernie here—just wanted to let you guys know I’m handing the reins over to Andrew Egan once again. (If you want some of my thoughts on things, I did a recent interview with LetterList.) Last time, he told us about a time-storing device; this time, he has a stalling tactic of sorts. Check it out!
Today in Tedium: As we&amp;rsquo;ve noted before, long-running traditions in movies are slowly dying as media becomes digitized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Comment</title>
      <link>/2017/02/22/dvd-audio-commentary-decline/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/02/22/dvd-audio-commentary-decline/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Back again for another round is Andrew Egan, who most recently brought us the story of Scatman John. Tonight, he tells us about his time digging in the menus on random DVDs. (By the way, a quick shout-out to Kenn Messman, who recently made a big donation to the site. Thanks!)
Today in Tedium: As the formats hosting our favorite movies, music, and games change, some things will be lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Before Netflix</title>
      <link>/2017/01/06/first-streaming-service-itv-hong-kong/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/06/first-streaming-service-itv-hong-kong/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Earlier this week, I got a little grumpy over at Product Hunt, due to an undercurrent of snark around the fact that Netflix still has a DVD service. The reason for this was that too many people were skeptical about whether such a service was still necessary. It absolutely, totally is, and I’ll give you one reason why: Netflix’s DVD service has roughly 93,000 options, while its streaming service (between shows and movies) has fewer than 8,000 options—ensuring that DVDs will have a reason to exist for quite a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Destroy the White House … Again</title>
      <link>/2016/06/24/white-house-independence-day-explosion-scene/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2016 06:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/06/24/white-house-independence-day-explosion-scene/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It was an explosion that only the aliens saw coming. Almost exactly 20 years ago, the film Independence Day hit theaters and featured perhaps the single most iconic visual effect of the 1990s—a short, but effective shot of The White House getting destroyed by a gigantic alien mothership. The scene is memorable for a lot of reasons, one of which is that it looked pretty realistic. If you&amp;rsquo;re like me, you probably are wondering: How did they get that set to look so, uh, White House-y?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack Abramoff, Film Producer</title>
      <link>/2016/04/08/jack-abramoff-film-producer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2016 07:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/04/08/jack-abramoff-film-producer/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: No matter how many redemption tours he goes on, Jack Abramoff remains an infamous name in political circles. In the mid-2000s, he was the man at the center of a wide array of lobbying scandals, sometimes involving obscure parts of the United States like the Northern Mariana Islands and Guam. A decade ago this month, Abramoff was planning for a prison stay, having just been sentenced in a fraud case involving a casino cruise line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Format War Footnotes</title>
      <link>/2015/09/04/format-wars-laserdisc-hitclips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2015 08:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/09/04/format-wars-laserdisc-hitclips/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: They say that history is written by the people who win—a standard that translates to wars and land grabs of all types. But it also translates pretty effectively to format wars. Generally, when we reminisce about old-school formats, we tend to focus on vinyl records, tape decks, and floppy disks, but those only really scratch the surface of the kind of bizarre formats out there to grab content from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Education</title>
      <link>/2015/07/10/bad-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/07/10/bad-education/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The life of a child actor is anything but traditional. Between long stays on sets and a formative experience in the public spotlight, it’s no wonder that some former child stars resort to using drugs, going crazy on reality shows, or licking donuts. On the plus side, you still get to go to school—but even there, the experience is anything but traditional. There may be some really good on-set teachers, but sometimes it’s just a drunk guy trying to freeload on a movie set rather than teach kids algebra.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worst. Birthday. Ever.</title>
      <link>/2015/05/27/happy-birthday-copyright-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/27/happy-birthday-copyright-case/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: 80 years ago, the nature of one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most popular tunes changed forever. It&amp;rsquo;s a song you&amp;rsquo;ve probably sung before, about a bajillion times. &amp;ldquo;Happy birthday to you, happy birthday …&amp;rdquo; you know the rest. In 1935, &amp;ldquo;Happy Birthday&amp;rdquo; was copyrighted, and as a result, it&amp;rsquo;s rare to hear the song performed in any film or concert. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re gonna talk about copyright, traditional songs, and the ways in which people who had no role in creating those songs are making big bucks off of the unwitting public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bootleg this issue</title>
      <link>/2015/03/11/bootleg-this-issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/11/bootleg-this-issue/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Last month, a director named Joseph Kahn released the _Mighty Morphin Power Rangers_ film that nobody was asking for—but despite that low ceiling, he more than topped it. The 14-minute short film starred people who have actually been cast in real movies and TV shows (James Van Der Beek and Katee Sackhoff), and took the franchise in a dark, gritty new direction that definitely has nothing in common with the Saved By the Bell-in-costume motif that the franchise was known for in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>House of product cards</title>
      <link>/2015/03/06/house-of-product-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/06/house-of-product-cards/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Last weekend, you may have been like me and binged on House of Cards. Along the way, you may have spotted a few direct references to big-name brands … many of which may have paid for the chance to be on screen with Frank Underwood and SPOILER ALERT. But the nature of products on screen and elsewhere have become so prevalent that they just bleed into the action after a while—subliminally influencing us along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vulcan creativity</title>
      <link>/2015/03/04/leonard-nimoy-vulcan-creativity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/04/leonard-nimoy-vulcan-creativity/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: William Shatner got all the weirdo pop attention back in the 1960s, but his _Star Trek_ co-star deserved just as much of it—if not more. The just-departed Leonard Nimoy (God rest his half-Vulcan soul) recorded a number of pop albums in the 1960s, including his own renditions of &amp;ldquo;I Walk the Line&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Proud Mary.&amp;rdquo; But the career highlight to top them all was a bizarro pop tune about a fantasy character who sported ears nearly as pointy as Spock&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re a Winner</title>
      <link>/2015/02/20/awards-shows-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/20/awards-shows-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: A few weeks back, one of our readers, Greg Pace, had an idea for a Tedium issue: One where we highlight the most random and obscure awards we can possibly find. The idea was fascinating enough, but his reasoning for us doing so was what sold us on the idea. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m too lazy to find interesting information about awards, so I thought maybe you would for me,&amp;rdquo; he wrote.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>