<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Landline Phones on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/landline-phones/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Landline Phones on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 05:09:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/landline-phones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Weaponized Slogan</title>
      <link>/2017/02/02/weird-scam-calls-verizon-slogan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 05:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/02/02/weird-scam-calls-verizon-slogan/</guid>
      <description>A not-so-innocent question: For years, Verizon sold millions of people on the promise of solid cellular phone signals with a simple question. “Can you hear me now?” asked Paul Marcarelli, the living pitchman who spent years in anonymity because of his ties to the brand. (He’s much happier with Sprint.)  But that question, so innocent-seeming, has become weaponized in the hands of a bunch of scamming robocallers. The Better Business Bureau reported this week that scammers were calling unsuspecting people, asking people on the other end of the line if they can hear them, then hanging up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Dial Up the Weirdness</title>
      <link>/2016/07/06/weird-telephone-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/07/06/weird-telephone-numbers/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: NYNEX hasn&amp;rsquo;t been a going concern since Smash Mouth was first telling us to walk on the sun. (You might know it under its current post-merger name, Verizon.) But that didn&amp;rsquo;t stop me last night from dialing up a message on my Google Hangouts window with an automated request from a NYNEX operator that I deposit five cents or my phone call will be terminated. (Couldn&amp;rsquo;t do it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>