<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sega on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/sega/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sega on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 07:59:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/sega/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Modem Madness</title>
      <link>/2017/09/19/video-game-modem-experiments/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 07:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/19/video-game-modem-experiments/</guid>
      <description>A couple of months ago, I gave a little notice to Sega’s early attempt to tie cable connections with video games, the Sega Channel. Certainly, it was the most interesting communications-related experiment that Sega had formulated that year. But as it turns out, it was probably not Sega’s most interesting experiment involving communications. Far from it.  Now, to start off, Sega is famously a company that, during the Genesis/Mega Drive era at least, was not opposed to add-ons for this device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sega, In Channel Form</title>
      <link>/2017/07/20/sega-channel-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 07:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/20/sega-channel-history/</guid>
      <description>If you’re a fan of Nintendo today, odds are you’ve been getting a bit of an earful about the company’s botched voice chat, which is a key element of the company’s online service for the Switch.  But video game companies failing to properly roll out online features is a problem that’s anything but new—in fact, it’s been happening for decades, a mixture of failing to understand the audience and failing to properly use the technology in the right context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reverse-Engineering The Industry</title>
      <link>/2017/03/10/video-games-reverse-engineering-tengen-accolade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/10/video-games-reverse-engineering-tengen-accolade/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: When it comes to video game consoles, the manufacturers don’t like it when you bend the rules. But it happens anyway. Technically inclined individuals inevitably want to bend the platforms to their will, despite platform owners that want to protect their massive investments, and aren’t afraid to resort to lawsuits to get their way. There are plenty of cases like this, most infamously the case of the Game Genie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adapters, Unplugged</title>
      <link>/2016/09/28/ac-adapters-power-outlet-purpose/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 07:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/09/28/ac-adapters-power-outlet-purpose/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Power outlets are frustrating, but the devices we use on a daily basis? They don&amp;rsquo;t necessarily make things easier. In fact, the bricks that come with many modern devices, from your router to your Bluetooth speakers to your game console, tend to be giant, and at first, they were designed without any consideration for the fact that there was ample competition for your limited outlet space. Why have AC adapters traditionally been so frustrating?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lost (And Found) Levels</title>
      <link>/2016/06/17/hidden-content-video-games-cutting-room-floor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 07:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/06/17/hidden-content-video-games-cutting-room-floor/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It took a while for us to culturally admit it, but video games are a form of art on the level of many films—and that means that game developers are very much auteurs in the way that film directors are. (Or, depending on the game, schlockmeisters.) But as anyone who has ever used a Game Genie could tell you, there are things that developers don&amp;rsquo;t want you to see, at a basic level far removed from a mere easter egg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big in Brazil</title>
      <link>/2015/07/17/sega-master-system-brazil/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/07/17/sega-master-system-brazil/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Here’s a true fact that will blow your mind—the game-maker Sega started out as an American company, not as a Japanese one. Sure, much of its success came about after it moved to Japan, but it was not by any means a company that necessarily needed Japan, like notable competitors Nintendo, Sony, and NEC did. While the company had one solid era of major success in the American market—where the Sega Genesis went toe-to-toe with the Super NES and became one of the most popular systems of the ‘90s—it was Brazil where Sega really came into its own.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>