<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Movie Reviews on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/movie-reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Movie Reviews on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 07:51:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/movie-reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Same Name Game</title>
      <link>/2018/05/30/same-name-movie-review-locus-of-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 07:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/30/same-name-movie-review-locus-of-control/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with a piece from Andrew Egan, who may have just invented a new kind of movie review with this piece. If you’re looking for a soundtrack for this issue, I recommend this one.
Today in Tedium: The content explosion has had some strange side effects. Binge watching is altering our brains and decreasing production costs have nurtured YouTubers’ desire for mainstream success. But as Amazon, Netflix, and Hollywood in general prepare to spend billions on original content in the coming years, an even stranger phenomenon is happening in plain sight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tommy’s Back</title>
      <link>/2018/04/03/best-friends-tommy-wiseau-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 07:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/03/best-friends-tommy-wiseau-review/</guid>
      <description>Tommy Wiseau, the legendary auteur of The Room, may not be a great filmmaker in the traditional sense, but he has a pretty enthused fanbase—a base of which I admit being a part of. And that fanbase, which has stuck with Wiseau through unusual projects like his 2015 Hulu series The Neighbors, has gotten a lot of mileage out of a single film that has owned the midnight movie circuit for years.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>