<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Websites on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/websites/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Websites on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/websites/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Blogging Dead?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/is-blogging-dead-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/is-blogging-dead-2018/</guid>
      <description>[big]Is a newsletter a blog? And if it is, does that make what I do with Tedium blogging? And if so, is that practice in decline as we enter 2018?[/big]
That’s not exactly how I approach this process, certainly, but I think it’s worth discussing at length at the moment, as the culture of blogging evolves away from what it once was. Over at JSTOR’s excellent daily news site, author Farah Mohammed analyzes blogging in the past tense, pondering whether the medium is in broader decline, as big-name bloggers like Nicholas Kristof leave the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Thanks, Spammers</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/seo-spammers-ruining-open-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/seo-spammers-ruining-open-web/</guid>
      <description>[big]Tedium has a decent number of readers, but when it comes down to it, it’s a small blip on the larger internet—a small professional publisher at a time when so many of our publishers are large and centralized.[/big]
As a result of this relatively unique status, I get a lot of messages on a fairly regular basis asking me to do one of a few things:
 Update a link on a story I’ve already written to get in a business I didn’t previously mention.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>