<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Guitars on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/guitars/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Guitars on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/guitars/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre String Theories</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/prepared-guitar-bizarre-string-theories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/prepared-guitar-bizarre-string-theories/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Of the many fascinating experiments on the internet these days involving red hot nickel balls, my personal favorite is this one, involving two guitars. This clip, apparently inspired by nickel-ball innovator Matthew Neuland&amp;rsquo;s uncle, at first attempted to show whether a fiery nickel ball would put the guitar out of tune. Then Neuland used the nickel ball to destroy the strings. It&amp;rsquo;s far from the first example of someone messing with guitar strings just to see what might happen—in fact, there&amp;rsquo;s something of a whole subgenre of guitar playing based on the concept of modifying or breaking guitars in unusual ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Damage &amp; Dissonance</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/fixing-broken-guitars-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/fixing-broken-guitars-lessons/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: It&amp;rsquo;s not often that we get to say, &amp;ldquo;Poor Bryan Adams,&amp;rdquo; but a recent experience he dealt with at an Egyptian airport was definitely worthy of that rarely used phrase. Adams, the artist behind most of our important schmaltz-rock, had most of his instruments tagged by Egyptian customs officials who couldn&amp;rsquo;t care less whether they were handling a 1957 Martin guitar or a guitar promoted by the guy from Maroon 5.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>