<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Television on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/digital-television/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital Television on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 09:21:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/digital-television/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Next Annoying National Upgrade</title>
      <link>/2017/12/06/atsc-3-0-digital-television-standard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 09:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/06/atsc-3-0-digital-television-standard/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: With all the recent chatter about Ajit Pai’s aggressive attempt to roll back net neutrality standards, it’s easy for other parts of the Federal Communications Commission’s winding docket to get lost. But there are things that the FCC is doing beyond ruining your internet that are worth discussing. One of those things is the recent passage of a measure to allow the voluntary rollout of ATSC 3.0, a television transmission standard that could rejigger the way we watch the boob tube.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital TV’s Tiny Achilles Heel</title>
      <link>/2017/07/04/portable-digital-television-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 07:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/04/portable-digital-television-problems/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to technology, I have a lot of love for edge cases—situations where the march of innovation actually makes things a little bit worse.  Which means that I’ve become a pretty sizable fan of the YouTube channel Techmoan in recent months. Host Mat Taylor’s magical ability to drop matter-of-fact bits of knowledge about obscure AV equipment is unparalleled, and his clip this past weekend highlighting the way that the move to digital television (basically) killed the portable TV is no exception.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Annoying National Upgrade</title>
      <link>/2016/04/27/digital-television-upgrade-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 07:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/04/27/digital-television-upgrade-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The move of the television airwaves from analog to digital in 2009 was perhaps the most unusual case of planned obsolescence in the modern age. Here was a decision, mandated by the Telecommunications Act of 1996 and forced upon hundreds of millions of people at once, that threw lots of people out of their routine. Many folks weren&amp;rsquo;t ready, or maybe they didn&amp;rsquo;t care enough about their TV signal quality to upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>