<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Commercials on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/commercials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Commercials on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 07:44:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/commercials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Please Clap</title>
      <link>/2018/03/23/the-clapper-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 07:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/23/the-clapper-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The tale of Ring, the startup that Amazon just acquired recently, is a fascinating one: An idea that got rejected on Shark Tank under a different name, the concept quickly found steam from new investors like the rapper Nas and became one of the most interesting forms of home automation, an industry that, according to Statista, is worth a cool $18.9 billion in 2018. But home automation had to start somewhere, and I’d like to argue that, barring any homes of the future, it really started gaining mainstream momentum with a device marketed by a guy perhaps better known for the Chia Pet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art, Commerce, and Zamfir</title>
      <link>/2017/07/26/heartland-music-direct-tv-music-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 07:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/26/heartland-music-direct-tv-music-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: When I grew up, I listened to a lot of John Denver. Well, not really full songs, so much as the 10-second snippets of tunes that played during his commercials on late-night cable TV. “You fill up my senses like a night in the forest,” Denver sang to the masses, even though he was really only singing to Annie, his first wife. But those choruses and hooks had a way of bleeding together into one super-song.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cutting A Rug</title>
      <link>/2017/01/11/carpet-history-evolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/11/carpet-history-evolution/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: I have a song stuck in my head right now. A jingle, really. It’s been stuck in my head for the last 15 years, at least. It’s probably stuck in your head, too—and if you’re near Chicago, it’s been stuck in your head since the days of disco. It’s the work of a man who spent decades trying to sell us carpet. Hardwood flooring too, maybe windows as well, but mostly carpet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>