<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ocr on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/ocr/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ocr on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 07:31:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/ocr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Scanning And Sorting</title>
      <link>/2017/09/01/check-processing-history-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 07:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/01/check-processing-history-automation/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The physical check, for most general purposes, is a sheer relic—basically used mostly for specific big-ticket purchases like rent, it certainly doesn’t have the sex appeal of, say, blockchain-based currencies like Ethereum and Litecoin. But it’s worth keeping in mind that check scanning, sorting, and distribution played an important early role in electronic commerce. Before we got niceties like ACH and magnetic strips, it set the wheels in motion for our highly automated commerce-based world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seek And Spell</title>
      <link>/2017/03/23/ocr-typography-optical-character-recognition-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 07:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/23/ocr-typography-optical-character-recognition-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: We live in a world where facial recognition has become so sophisticated that we’re being forced to ask very serious ethical questions about it. (In the U.S., the depth of the FBI’s facial-recognition capabilities are raising some serious questions from Congress. In China, it’s being used to detect toilet paper theft. To each country their own.) But I want to take a step back from the big hairy ethical questions and consider how we started on this road—with typography.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>