<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Curly Howard on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/curly-howard/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Curly Howard on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/curly-howard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stone Stooges</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/three-stooges-gravestone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/three-stooges-gravestone/</guid>
      <description>[big]There was once a time when The Three Stooges ruled the late-night roost with a series of TV marathons that ensured the Vaudeville-era comedians would have a longer reach than many of their contemporaries. For decades, TBS owned this little niche.[/big]
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C_pN1eqjMWw
Even now, cable networks like IFC and AMC run the Stooges at odd times, in the middle of the night, mostly on weekends, as fillers between other movies. In some ways, their broad brand of slapstick humor has grown into a niche endeavor in the modern day—in part because more sophisticated takes on physical humor (think the eyerolls and subtle cringeiness of The Office and its variants, or Paul Rudd’s cafeteria scene from Wet Hot American Summer) have made the pokes and prods of Moe Howard and his second bananas seem a little dull.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stooge Story</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/three-stooges-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/three-stooges-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: A while back, I wrote this piece on the Sound Blaster where I spent a bit of time explaining that internal expansion ports were once very common in PCs. It was the type of thing that, had I written the story even five years earlier, might not even have been necessary. But so many people have grown up without them, on laptops and tablets, that the explainer was actually useful.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>