<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nestlé on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/nestl%C3%A9/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nestlé on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/nestl%C3%A9/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hot Pocket Diaspora</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/hot-pocket-history-iran-jewish-diaspora/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/hot-pocket-history-iran-jewish-diaspora/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Laugh all you want, but Hot Pockets are the ultimate modern food. Incredibly easy to eat and simple to cook, they cleverly were designed to be easy to microwave and completely, utterly portable. Less known about the Hot Pocket, however, is its origins, which are the product of a duo of Iranian-born Jewish immigrants who arguably popularized the concept of microwavable frozen meals. Jim Gaffigan hates these things, but we admit something of a respect for them as a bottom-up success story (that just happens to be incredibly unhealthy).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Bowl &#39;Em Over</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/cereal-around-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/cereal-around-the-world/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Cereal is basically the perfect food, in my opinion, especially in Life form. Simple to make, easy to eat, and available in options varying from over-the-top healthy to teeth-destroying, it&amp;rsquo;s a part of many breakfasts that will never go away. Or will it? Last month, the internet jumped on a New York Times story that implied millennials were losing interest in breakfast cereal across the board, in part because these lazy kids had to clean up after themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>