<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Phone Numbers on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/phone-numbers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Phone Numbers on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 07:18:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/phone-numbers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chinese Robocall Blues</title>
      <link>/2018/05/16/spam-robocalls-history-comparison/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 07:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/16/spam-robocalls-history-comparison/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Recently, I got a phone call from a number I’d never seen before. In other words, an average day. But this call was weird, largely because it was decidedly not for me. It sounded like Chinese, which was confirmed when I had the bright idea of holding my phone against my laptop’s microphone so Google Translate could make it out. Suddenly, it became slightly more clear: The message was a robocall—a strange one at that, one that suggested some sort of immigration trouble for the caller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out Of Order</title>
      <link>/2017/11/01/telephone-area-codes-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 07:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/01/telephone-area-codes-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: From a distance, at least, there seems to be no rhyme or reason to the way we got our telephone numbers. And it’s becoming even less clear thanks to the increasing sophistication of the phone technologies we use. In particular, the layout of the area code system seems to have been picked at random, with no thought as to how the broader system should work. Or am I simply missing something bigger?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Dialing, More Weirdness</title>
      <link>/2017/06/28/weird-phone-number-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 07:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/28/weird-phone-number-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Almost exactly a year ago, we wrote up a lengthy piece on weird telephone numbers. This piece has been a sleeper hit of sorts in Tedium history. Many of our pieces, if they do gain steam, tend to pick up within a week of writing. Not this one. Instead, the piece went to the top of Google for dozens of variations on the search term “weird phone numbers,” “creepy phone numbers,” and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Weaponized Slogan</title>
      <link>/2017/02/02/weird-scam-calls-verizon-slogan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 05:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/02/02/weird-scam-calls-verizon-slogan/</guid>
      <description>A not-so-innocent question: For years, Verizon sold millions of people on the promise of solid cellular phone signals with a simple question. “Can you hear me now?” asked Paul Marcarelli, the living pitchman who spent years in anonymity because of his ties to the brand. (He’s much happier with Sprint.)  But that question, so innocent-seeming, has become weaponized in the hands of a bunch of scamming robocallers. The Better Business Bureau reported this week that scammers were calling unsuspecting people, asking people on the other end of the line if they can hear them, then hanging up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Dial Up the Weirdness</title>
      <link>/2016/07/06/weird-telephone-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/07/06/weird-telephone-numbers/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: NYNEX hasn&amp;rsquo;t been a going concern since Smash Mouth was first telling us to walk on the sun. (You might know it under its current post-merger name, Verizon.) But that didn&amp;rsquo;t stop me last night from dialing up a message on my Google Hangouts window with an automated request from a NYNEX operator that I deposit five cents or my phone call will be terminated. (Couldn&amp;rsquo;t do it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>