<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alternative Rock on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/alternative-rock/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Alternative Rock on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 07:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/alternative-rock/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Maybe You’ve Been Brainwashed Too</title>
      <link>/2018/10/10/new-radicals-gregg-alexander-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/10/new-radicals-gregg-alexander-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Two decades ago this month, a couple of things happened in the world of music that forever shaped the way I thought about it. One, the Barenaked Ladies scored a number-one hit on the Billboard Hot 100 with “One Week,” and a band called The New Radicals released their first and only album, *Maybe You’ve Been Brainwashed Too*—whose lead single, “You Get What You Give,” would turn the band into the perfect one-hit wonder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything You Want</title>
      <link>/2018/08/02/vertical-horizon-verizon-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/02/vertical-horizon-verizon-theory/</guid>
      <description>On April 3, 2000, one of the most prominent companies of the 21st century was born. That day, the name and logo for Verizon became known to the masses. The company, for better or worse, became a defining middleman, fundamental to the way we use our phones and access our internet.  The next day, a popular rock band released a physical single for what would become their biggest hit. “Everything You Want,” a song from Vertical Horizon&amp;rsquo;s first major label record, had already been on the radio for a few months by this point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Wave Titans</title>
      <link>/2018/03/14/oingo-boingo-danny-elfman-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 07:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/14/oingo-boingo-danny-elfman-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with another piece from David Buck. Last we saw of him, he was talking to Tom Bodett. Tonight, he’s obsessing over an iconic West Coast band. Read on; it&amp;rsquo;s worth it.
Today in Tedium: If you’re a fan of director Tim Burton, you may recognize the name Danny Elfman. If you’re a Nightmare before Christmas fan, you may even recognize his voice. But, did you know he started his music career with a band called The Mystic Knights of the Oingo Boingo (later just Oingo Boingo)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Literal Dad Rock</title>
      <link>/2018/03/12/adrian-belew-oh-daddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 20:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/12/adrian-belew-oh-daddy/</guid>
      <description>It doesn’t get nearly as much attention as, say, 1992, but 1989 may have been the most interesting year for modern rock.  The reason for this was that the creation of Billboard’s Modern Rock Tracks chart the year prior created a context for people in the music industry who never would have had a chance at having a mainstream hit otherwise. And MTV, with its 120 Minutes franchise going strong, was ready to push the songs, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why “Zombie” Lingers</title>
      <link>/2018/01/16/cranberries-zombie-legacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 08:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/16/cranberries-zombie-legacy/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s painful every time we lose a major rock star, especially one who still had a lot of years left in front of them, as Irish singer and Cranberries frontwoman Dolores O’Riordan did. She hadn’t even hit age 50 yet, and her career was such that her biggest successes came and went before she had hit the age of 30. “Linger” and “Zombie” were sizable hits before she had even turned 24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congratulations I’m Sorry</title>
      <link>/2017/09/29/gin-blossoms-hey-jealousy-tragedy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 06:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/29/gin-blossoms-hey-jealousy-tragedy/</guid>
      <description>“Do you think it’d be all right if I could just crash here tonight?” The introduction to “Hey Jealousy,” the 1992 song by the Gin Blossoms, introduces a lackadaisical ne’er-do-well, one who laments the loss of an old relationship while asking his ex for a place to ward off his hangover, because he has nowhere else to go.  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ah5gAkna3jI
Unlike Nirvana or Pearl Jam, the darkness of the lyrics wasn’t matched by a darkness in the melody—the tune, in fact, had more in common with a melodic tune from R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chartered Waters</title>
      <link>/2016/04/20/billboard-pop-charts-alternative-charts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 07:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/04/20/billboard-pop-charts-alternative-charts/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: As a fan of the underdog, I love reading the bottom half of music charts. Forget Billboard&amp;rsquo;s Hot 100; I wanna see what&amp;rsquo;s happening on the Bubbling Under Hot 100 chart, if that indie band I&amp;rsquo;m digging actually has a chance of breaking into the top half. (Oh, who am I kidding? I spent the last week listening to Hüsker Dü and American Music Club. My taste is off the grid these days.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>