<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Newspapers on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/newspapers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Newspapers on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 03:21:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/newspapers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Funny Page</title>
      <link>/2018/02/20/newspaper-funny-pages-rethink-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 03:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/20/newspaper-funny-pages-rethink-2018/</guid>
      <description>At the beginning of 2018, we’re on the cusp of something that might arguably be one of the biggest changes to newspapers in generations: Comic strips, one of the newspaper’s great standbys, are starting to “age out.”  This took quite a long time, but two major things have happened in recent weeks that suggest a major sea change is on the way: the January death of Mort Walker, who was responsible for creating Beetle Bailey and co-creating Hi and Lois, and the decision by cartoonist Guy Gilchrist (who has plenty of years in front of him) to stop doing Nancy, whose final edition published on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trimmed For Space</title>
      <link>/2017/12/08/newspaper-newsprint-cuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 09:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/08/newspaper-newsprint-cuts/</guid>
      <description>_Editor’s note: Tonight’s Tedium is an updated rerun of a classic issue about the stuff that newspapers get rid of when trying to slim down. Unspoken in this article: Usually, the final step of this process is people. And with the recent sagas of L.A. Weekly and (on the digital side of things) DNAinfo, now felt like a good time to revisit. (If you&amp;rsquo;ve read before, keep reading; there&amp;rsquo;s a new section on newsprint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMYK All The Way</title>
      <link>/2017/04/19/color-printing-lithography-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 07:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/04/19/color-printing-lithography-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In the 1990s, after much delay, the newspaper industry’s largest and most prominent newspapers finally started printing most of their pages in color on a regular basis. It was a much delayed phenomenon, driven less by a lack of technology and more by a mixture of cost and tradition. In 1993, The New York Times printed its first page in color, far later than most of the rest of the newspaper industry, and the only other big holdouts at that point were The Wall Street Journal and The Washington Post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News In Small Bytes</title>
      <link>/2016/11/04/online-news-history-compuserve-videotex/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 07:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/11/04/online-news-history-compuserve-videotex/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Publishing words on a computer is not a difficult task these days. We have so many options to write words and distribute them through a computerized interface that we take the whole process for granted. (You probably published something in the time it took you to read the previous two sentences.) But there was a time when publishing through a computer was painful, cumbersome, and expensive. It also had little in common with the free-for-all that allows for the creation of all sorts of terrible/fascinating content online by random folks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey, I Shrunk The Page</title>
      <link>/2016/06/15/microfiche-microfilm-libraries-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/06/15/microfiche-microfilm-libraries-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Do me a favor while you read these opening lines. Pick up your phone, and open up your photos app. Scroll through the many pictures of you, your dumb friends, and your crazy family. Pick a photo—it can be any photo, really, and blow it up so it fills the whole screen. Still with me? Good. Now, tell me, how would you recreate this experience using physical devices alone—where you flipped through thousands of tiny images and blew up a really big one to a size where you can actually read it without (and here&amp;rsquo;s the key part) destroying the original?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Invention Of News</title>
      <link>/2015/05/22/press-releases-invention-of-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2015 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/22/press-releases-invention-of-news/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Press releases are like chum for the enterprising marketer. For decades, these blurbs have been designed to draw in journalists looking for the next story, _something_ to fill the page or make hay for their audiences. Sometimes, they&amp;rsquo;re successful—such as Nintendo of America&amp;rsquo;s cheeky press release, released Wednesday, that pointed out their VP of sales has the last name Bowser. But a lot of the time, they&amp;rsquo;re full of irrelevant crap.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>