<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Products on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/products/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Products on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 07:41:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/products/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Generic Internet Article</title>
      <link>/2015/10/23/generic-products-private-labels/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 07:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/10/23/generic-products-private-labels/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In 1986, about a decade removed from his icon-setting days as lead singer of the Sex Pistols, British punk architect John Lydon released an album with his follow-up band, Public Image, Ltd., that had an extremely high-concept name. In fact, it didn&amp;rsquo;t technically have a name at all. If you bought the record on vinyl, it was called Album; if you bought it on CD, it was called Compact Disc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Army Life</title>
      <link>/2015/09/23/swiss-army-knife-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/09/23/swiss-army-knife-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: I’ve decided that I’m a big fan of Swiss army knives. Not the knives themselves, necessarily—I can never properly finagle my nails to pull the blades out of the casing—but the idea behind them. A single object with numerous uses is an incredibly powerful idea, and one that the Swiss Army Knife got to first. Something about this simple, elegant concept gets lost somewhere in a Bed Bath and Beyond run, probably because multi-tools probably cut away at their stuff-laden businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>House of product cards</title>
      <link>/2015/03/06/house-of-product-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/06/house-of-product-cards/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Last weekend, you may have been like me and binged on House of Cards. Along the way, you may have spotted a few direct references to big-name brands … many of which may have paid for the chance to be on screen with Frank Underwood and SPOILER ALERT. But the nature of products on screen and elsewhere have become so prevalent that they just bleed into the action after a while—subliminally influencing us along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>