<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Health on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Health on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 07:40:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Drip And Drive</title>
      <link>/2018/03/21/blood-donation-bloodmobile-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/21/blood-donation-bloodmobile-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Recently, my wife has really gotten into putting on blood drives, in no small part because of their ability to save lives—by making the iron-laden resources already running through our veins and arteries available to people who need them just a little bit more. These blood drives, quite often, happen in public places. You don’t have to go to the Red Cross; the Red Cross will come to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Not Trust</title>
      <link>/2017/12/05/do-not-resuscitate-tattoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/05/do-not-resuscitate-tattoo/</guid>
      <description>A tattoo probably isn’t a binding legal document, but it certainly seems like a convincing argument. Clearly you must believe what you tattoo on yourself if you’re willing to go to that level of permanence, right?  But a recent saga involving a patient at a Miami hospital proved that question is a little more fraught than it seems. Doctors at Jackson Memorial Hospital, located at the University of Miami, were presented with a unconscious 70-year-old man who had a “Do Not Resuscitate” tattoo, along with his apparent signature, emblazoned on his chest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Case Of Emergency</title>
      <link>/2017/06/21/911-emergency-system-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 07:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/21/911-emergency-system-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Of all the things William Shatner has done in his career—captain of the starship USS Enterprise, veteran police officer, totally-game muse for Ben Folds, fairly good tweeter for being 86 years old—the one thing that&amp;rsquo;s stuck with me the most is his years on Rescue 911, the early reality show that was America&amp;rsquo;s Most Wanted (mostly) without the crime and Unsolved Mysteries with the solutions laid out clear as day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Live Forever</title>
      <link>/2017/01/20/worlds-hottest-peppers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 23:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/20/worlds-hottest-peppers/</guid>
      <description>Eating hot peppers is apparently a great way to avoid having a stroke or heart attack, according to a recent study from the University of Vermont’s Larner College of Medicine. The study found that people who ate hot peppers tended to live longer despite the fact that they had other bad habits, such as smoking.  To be fair, it’s not entirely clear where the direct tie is between the peppers and the longevity (the researchers speculate that capsaicin helps prevent obesity), but going by the crazy logic of studies like this, it only makes sense that we take a logical leap of our own: If you eat increasingly hotter peppers, you should theoretically be able to live forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asbestos: It Isn&#39;t Snow</title>
      <link>/2016/07/29/asbestos-danger-risk-litigation-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/07/29/asbestos-danger-risk-litigation-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Throughout our history as a country, we&amp;rsquo;ve quickly turned on popular products we once liked because of unintended effects from that product, usually health-related. (You know, like Chipotle.) But perhaps the product we&amp;rsquo;ve most famously done this with is asbestos, the naturally occurring fibery crystals that gained infamy after it was realized that those fibers were dangerous carcinogens. They represent an issue that still gets frequently litigated today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This one&#39;s for the wounded</title>
      <link>/2015/05/20/history-of-bandages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/20/history-of-bandages/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Blood is a terrible thing to waste, and for centuries, the ways to stop blood from leaving the body were inefficient at best and not exactly easy to use. But one day, a guy spotted a problem that his wife was having and came up with one of the most brilliant solutions for solving simple injuries that the world had ever seen. And we’ve only kept innovating from there.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>