<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weird Laws on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/weird-laws/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Weird Laws on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 06:18:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/weird-laws/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>We Can Dance If We Want To</title>
      <link>/2017/10/31/nyc-dancing-regulation-repeal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 06:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/31/nyc-dancing-regulation-repeal/</guid>
      <description>New York City has long been known as a fairly progressive place, one known as welcoming to ethnic and cultural groups long marginalized by society. So it’s surprising that the city’s laws regarding dancing are more appropriate for a small town in an ‘80s movie.  The city’s long, strange aversion to dancing is finally expected to come to an end on October 31st when a prohibition-era law is expected to be repealed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stating The Seemingly Obvious</title>
      <link>/2017/04/27/utah-bar-restaurant-sign-regulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 07:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/04/27/utah-bar-restaurant-sign-regulation/</guid>
      <description>Utah is a great state, but with its historic ties to the Mormon religion (and that religion’s hard-to-ignore political clout), it occasionally runs into some head-scratching situations—especially when it comes to alcohol.  The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints prohibits its members from consuming alcohol, and that has informed the state’s laws on the issue over the years.
Beer is sold at bars and some restaurants, but at an alcohol level that barely even counts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>