<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gardening on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/gardening/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gardening on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 05:44:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/gardening/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Seedy Politics</title>
      <link>/2016/04/06/seed-industry-bureaucracy-politics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 05:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/04/06/seed-industry-bureaucracy-politics/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: This time of the year is perfect for planting a garden, so it&amp;rsquo;s natural to hit your local store and buy a bunch of tomato seeds, perhaps some carrot seeds, and maybe you&amp;rsquo;re in the mood for some spice, so you add a couple of habanero seeds to the cart. Soon, you might plant these seeds in the ground, without even giving a second thought to the fact that you showed your support to the commercial seed industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get off my lawn</title>
      <link>/2015/06/16/lawn-care-history-get-off-my-lawn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 06:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/16/lawn-care-history-get-off-my-lawn/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Rich people care about their grass way more than normal people do. Now, rarely is this an issue, but in recent months, the ongoing California drought has made this mundane issue a political one. This week, the city of Rancho Santa Fe became a target of this culture clash after _The Washington Post_ highlighted the water-rationing requirement it soon faces. Local residents aren&amp;rsquo;t happy. “When we bought, we didn’t plan on getting a place that looks like we’re living in an African savanna,” said conservative radio host and local resident Steve Yuhas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>