<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dollar Stores on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/dollar-stores/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dollar Stores on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/dollar-stores/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;d Buy That for a Dollar</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/dollar-stores-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/dollar-stores-analysis/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: The dollar store is one of capitalism&amp;rsquo;s greatest gifts to itself, if you think about it. Here&amp;rsquo;s a business model that has, quite brilliantly, taken advantage of the ebbs and flows of supply and demand. It turns products that don&amp;rsquo;t cost a lot to produce into things that actually make money hand over fist, despite the seemingly tight margins. Like companies that turn the liquidation of products into a viable business model and the makers of generic products, dollar stores have their place in the pantheon of retail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When It Rains, It Pours</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/umbrella-patents-innovation-challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/umbrella-patents-innovation-challenges/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Umbrellas are a good way to protect your head in case of inclement weather. Problem is, they’re not a perfect way. And that is made obvious by the fact that you’re sometimes hit by at least a little of the wet stuff even after you use such a device. If it gets windy (or even if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t), their structural integrity breaks down easily, exposing users to rain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Tech Hit Retail</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/point-of-sale-retail-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/point-of-sale-retail-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: If it feels like the the “robots are trying to steal our jobs” meme is a new development, I have some news for you: It’s really not. For decades, automation has been implied to be the cause of—and solution to—all life’s problems. Nowhere is this more the case than in the halls of retail, where automation helped redefine our interaction with shopping in important ways. And those innovations are still happening.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>