<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mail Order on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/mail-order/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mail Order on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/mail-order/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Delivered To Your Door</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/monthly-subscription-box-delivery-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/monthly-subscription-box-delivery-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Don’t let the talk of content on the cloud fool you. It’s easier than ever to get physical stuff mailed to your duplex nearly every single day of the year. (OK, maybe it’s not Jetsons-easy yet. We’ll get there.) In recent years, that’s led to the rise of subscription box services like Birchbox, BlueApron, and Loot Crate. (Personally, I’m obsessed with Blue Bottle’s biweekly coffee bean delivery service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retail’s Tech Champion</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/sears-technology-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/sears-technology-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: For a wide variety of reasons, Sears has been a company creaking its way through modern times for longer than many of the people reading this have even been alive. It was a fundamental company to the American revolution—while it didn’t invent the mail-order catalog, it made it a successful business and set the stage for decades of followers. But I don’t want to wallow in Sears’ failings; there are plenty of other outlets for that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The first 12 cost a penny, but …</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/columbia-house-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/columbia-house-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Yesterday, a coworker and good friend of mine revealed to me a fact that made me feel very old. We were talking about Spotify—and his desire not to pay $10 per month for the service—and I referenced Columbia House. He did not know what I was talking about. I was taken aback by this news—I thought everyone knew what Columbia House was! The mail-order CD service (along with its competitor BMG) had a bright moment in the early &amp;lsquo;90s, only to see its business model fall apart thanks to iTunes, and later, Spotify.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>