<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Modem on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/modem/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Modem on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 07:15:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/modem/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nothing But Net (And Ads)</title>
      <link>/2018/08/08/juno-netzero-free-dialup-internet-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/08/juno-netzero-free-dialup-internet-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: People want an improbable deal, no matter how unlikely that deal might actually be. Hence the strong interest in MoviePass, a company with a model so doomed that people were suggesting it would initially fail not long after it started offering free daily tickets at $9.99 per month. (Instead, its fast decline took about a year, even with a high burn rate, and now the company is changing its model because it has no other choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Soft</title>
      <link>/2017/03/21/dial-up-soft-modem-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 07:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/21/dial-up-soft-modem-history/</guid>
      <description>Dial-up modems were underpowered enough back in the days of AOL, but at the height of their popularity, manufacturers figured out a way to make them even worse.  During the late ‘90s, a spate of companies, including big name modem manufacturers like U.S. Robotics, Motorola, and PCtel, had the idea to replace hardware-based modems, which generally required a separate digital signal processor to manage the dial-up connection, with software-based equivalents, which took this task and put it on top of the CPU already being used.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>