<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Salt Water on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/salt-water/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Salt Water on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 08:36:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/salt-water/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>You Can&#39;t Drink Saltwater</title>
      <link>/2016/03/02/desalination-saltwater-reverse-osmosis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 08:36:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/03/02/desalination-saltwater-reverse-osmosis/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Salt is a great substance, and one that deserves an important place in our culture. But salt is also the most annoying substance on the planet, in that it makes nearly all of our water supply basically unusable for drinking purposes. Now, removing salt from water is not a painless process, but in an era when drought is a fact of life in places as far-flung as Australia and California, desalination is becoming an increasingly important process for increasing our freshwater supply by just a little bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lithium&#39;s on Fire</title>
      <link>/2015/12/11/lithium-mining-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/11/lithium-mining-growth/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Those stupid hoverboards that have shown up just about everywhere lately have a big problem, and its name is lithium. In recent weeks, numerous news stories have cropped up about these devices and their tendency to cause fires. The problem is that many of these devices are knockoffs that use really cruddy low-quality lithium batteries, batteries so cruddy that airlines are now telling customers to leave their stupid wheeled floaty devices at home.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>