<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Outsider Music on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/outsider-music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Outsider Music on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/outsider-music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>90 Seconds of Failure</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/shooby-taylor-showtime-at-the-apollo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/shooby-taylor-showtime-at-the-apollo/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend—inspired by the forthcoming release of The Disaster Artist, a film about my favorite movie—I finally saw Ed Wood. It took me way too long.
Ed Wood is a great film about a terrible filmmaker, as well as a great story about the creative muse, and how it sometimes doesn’t hit the cues of the popular taste. Wood’s masterwork, Plan 9 From Outer Space, doesn’t need any more words written about it—but the origin story of its reputation as the “worst movie” is nearly as fascinating as its creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>His Name Was Larry</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/larry-wild-man-fischer-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/larry-wild-man-fischer-story/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Hey all, Ernie here with another piece from David Buck, who wrote his first Tedium piece on outsider icon R. Stevie Moore. Turns out his knowledge of outsider artists goes deep—as you&amp;rsquo;ll see with today&amp;rsquo;s piece.
[big]Today in Tedium: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve got a camera, loaded with film,&amp;rdquo; he sang, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m gonna take a picture of you.&amp;rdquo; I became particularly fascinated with the unique vocal stylings of Larry “Wild Man” Fischer after hearing his song &amp;ldquo;I Got a Camera&amp;rdquo; on a warm summer day, just before my freshman year of high school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moore R. Stevie Moore</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/r-stevie-moore-starting-points/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/r-stevie-moore-starting-points/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: This is a companion piece to yesterday&amp;rsquo;s newsletter issue on R. Stevie Moore, by David Buck. Read that first, then come back here.
&amp;nbsp;
[big]R. Stevie Moore&amp;rsquo;s vast body of work may intimidate some and may delight others. I&amp;rsquo;ve taken the liberty of curating a list of my top R. Stevie Moore songs that will entertain, amuse and otherwise. They also serve as a great introduction to the man and his work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock On Chicago</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/wesley-willis-remembrance-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/wesley-willis-remembrance-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey guys, Ernie here with a fresh Tedium piece comes from outsider artist aficionado and newsletter contributor David J. Buck, who hit us up last time with a piece on Wild Man Fischer. By popular demand, here’s a piece on Wesley Willis!
&amp;nbsp;
[big]Today in Tedium: People loved Wesley Willis. Despite a rough upbringing, struggles with mental illness, extreme poverty and an abusive family, he was friendly and lovable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Man With 400 Albums</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/r-stevie-moore-outsider-music-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/r-stevie-moore-outsider-music-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Hey all, Ernie from Tedium here! So I&amp;rsquo;m happy to introduce David Buck, a first-time writer for the newsletter who&amp;rsquo;s a massive fan of a guy you&amp;rsquo;re probably not even aware of. He makes me excited about the guy, to be honest. Read on—tonight&amp;rsquo;s piece is a total treat. And be sure to check out his list for newbies!
&amp;nbsp;
[big]Today in Tedium: Many great artists exist outside the mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wesley Willis WinAmp Connection</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/wesley-willis-winamp-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/wesley-willis-winamp-history/</guid>
      <description>[big]Wesley Willis was a prolific musician and wonderful artist. Beloved by most folks he ran across, it’s no surprise his legacy would live on in an unlikely place—your computer.[/big]
Some may recognize Mike the llama as the mascot of legendary music software WinAmp. But did you know, there is a somewhat tenuous, but quite obvious connection to Wesley built into the software?
Windows users in the mid-to-late 90s are probably used WinAmp or know of it in some capacity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>