<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Grammar on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/grammar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Grammar on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 19:03:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/grammar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>They Stopped (Sorta)</title>
      <link>/2017/03/27/singular-they-ap-stylebook-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 19:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/27/singular-they-ap-stylebook-update/</guid>
      <description>Last summer, I wrote an impassioned plea in favor of embracing the singular “they,” which I called “the Rodney Dangerfield of grammar.”  Basically, this word use, which has no simple singular equivalent that doesn’t dive into awkward gender politics when the subject’s grammar hasn’t been revealed, has been written around for hundreds of years by newspapers and in other formalized grammar settings. The Associated Press, notably, had resisted changing its mind on this issue, even as the linguistic tide started to favor it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They Should Stop</title>
      <link>/2016/08/05/singular-they-grammar-copy-editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 07:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/08/05/singular-they-grammar-copy-editing/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Of all the turf wars that have complicated the landscape of grammar over the past few hundred years, the most complicated and frustrating may be that of the singular &amp;ldquo;they.&amp;rdquo; It may be the most controversial word use in the English language—because it highlights a hole in the language where a better-fitting word should go. It creates a conflict between writers and editors who want things to follow the natural symmetry of Latin, and people who find they the only logical option for referring to a single person without a gender attached.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>