<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weird Internet on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/weird-internet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Weird Internet on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 04:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/weird-internet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>In front of the music</title>
      <link>/2015/06/03/worst-album-covers-analyzed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/03/worst-album-covers-analyzed/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Nearly as long as there has been the internet, there have been lists of terrible album covers—many of which predate the internet and are looked at using modern standards for humor and kitsch. But the problem with these images is that there&amp;rsquo;s often no story behind them, because they&amp;rsquo;re often not shared with any information to speak of. They&amp;rsquo;re historic memes, but they never seem to have any attached history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The History of Internet Explorer Hatred</title>
      <link>/2015/03/20/the-history-of-internet-explorer-hatred/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/20/the-history-of-internet-explorer-hatred/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Your browser says a lot about you. It highlights your socioeconomic class, your knowledge of computing, your inherent biases, and even the likelihood that you’re a failure at just about everything. For many people, using Internet Explorer was a sign that your relative or co-worker didn’t “get it,” and their resistance to changing browsers was a sign that they never would. Developers, without knowing your name or your circumstances, would curse you under your breath, because your clicking on their website made their job harder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Internet&#39;s First Hater</title>
      <link>/2015/01/07/meet-the-internets-first-hater/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/07/meet-the-internets-first-hater/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Two decades ago this month, a guy named Mirsky changed the internet forever in his own subtle way. His product? A site called Mirsky&amp;rsquo;s Worst of the Web. It was one of the internet&amp;rsquo;s first true phenomena and an icon of Web 1.0 culture. For a couple of years, he could count press mentions from sources as prominent as The Washington Post, People, and The Los Angeles Times.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>