<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Laserdisc on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/laserdisc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Laserdisc on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 07:35:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/laserdisc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sing Your Heart Out</title>
      <link>/2017/08/11/karaoke-technology-evolution-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/11/karaoke-technology-evolution-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Apologies to Chris Carrabba and his decades-old heartbreak, but my favorite karaoke song is totally at the Dashboard Confessional singer’s expense. During the height of the emo era, I was shocked that the heart-bleeding-on-floor anthem “Screaming Infidelities” was commonly featured in the books at karaoke bars, because it seemed like the opposite of a good karaoke song. So, knowing it was available, I decided to make it my signature song.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Killed The Encyclopedia?</title>
      <link>/2017/07/14/who-killed-the-encyclopedia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 07:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/14/who-killed-the-encyclopedia/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The CD-ROM was sold to the public and the world as a way to bring interactive multimedia experiences into our homes. (Certainly, that&amp;rsquo;s how the magazine world tried to sell it.) But beyond that, it was a sheer amount of storage for a price that was insane to consider at the time. And that meant that some of the earliest products produced for the CD-ROM format were of the reference variety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Discs Die</title>
      <link>/2017/02/03/disc-rot-phenomenon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/02/03/disc-rot-phenomenon/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Often, it looks like a coffee stain—a noticeable discoloration that for whatever reason you can’t get rid of. Sometimes, it looks like tiny pin pricks on the surface. And there are other times when the whole thing changes color. In any case, when you run into what’s known as “disc rot,” you’re out a great album or an interesting movie. It’s a serious situation, whether you’re a digital archivist or simply someone who wants to watch a movie on a weird format like a Laserdisc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Format War Footnotes</title>
      <link>/2015/09/04/format-wars-laserdisc-hitclips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2015 08:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/09/04/format-wars-laserdisc-hitclips/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: They say that history is written by the people who win—a standard that translates to wars and land grabs of all types. But it also translates pretty effectively to format wars. Generally, when we reminisce about old-school formats, we tend to focus on vinyl records, tape decks, and floppy disks, but those only really scratch the surface of the kind of bizarre formats out there to grab content from.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>