<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Education on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Education on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 07:40:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Trapper Keeper Contraband</title>
      <link>/2018/08/29/trapper-keeper-contraband-decline/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/29/trapper-keeper-contraband-decline/</guid>
      <description>Editor’s note: With the idea of treating my work as something of a living document, I sometimes update old Tedium issues in an effort to keep them up to date. When I was updating this one, though, I noticed something weird, and as a result, I wrote a much bigger update than usual. Read on, pals.
Today in Tedium: Schools are weird. They get super-political about the strangest things, because kids tend to get hung up about stupid things and those stupid things tend to affect what happens in the classroom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Toy That Talked Back</title>
      <link>/2018/06/20/speak-and-spell-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/20/speak-and-spell-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Four decades ago this month, a company that helped set the stage for the modern computing era got into the toy market thanks to an announcement at the 1978 Summer Consumer Electronics Show. While it wasn’t the first time that kids got their hands on something truly electronic, its influence ran deep, even as its technology was fairly primitive. With its robotic voice and limited memory, the Speak &amp;amp; Spell somehow mixed the seemingly incompatible worlds of education and entertainment in an impressive way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Blocks, Literally</title>
      <link>/2017/05/17/alphabet-blocks-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 07:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/17/alphabet-blocks-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: We talk a lot about technology in this newsletter, but the fact of the matter is that if you zoom out a little bit and think about it, we’re really telling the story about how we got to the modern day—how the boring, mundane, or unusual elements of our lives got us to this point. The building blocks, so to say. This time, we’re not going metaphorical with our block talk, like we did in the last issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total Edutainment Forever</title>
      <link>/2017/04/14/edutainment-math-blaster-chocolate-covered-broccoli/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 07:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/04/14/edutainment-math-blaster-chocolate-covered-broccoli/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Forcing education and entertainment together is a great way to ensure you don’t really do either all that well. (Case in point: The Jack Hanna repeat wasteland, targeted toward young teens as part of an advertising loophole, that is FCC-mandated educational television on broadcast stations.) Games are no exception. In the infancy of computers, educators quickly figured out that computer games could be a great vessel for both education and entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Education</title>
      <link>/2015/07/10/bad-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/07/10/bad-education/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The life of a child actor is anything but traditional. Between long stays on sets and a formative experience in the public spotlight, it’s no wonder that some former child stars resort to using drugs, going crazy on reality shows, or licking donuts. On the plus side, you still get to go to school—but even there, the experience is anything but traditional. There may be some really good on-set teachers, but sometimes it’s just a drunk guy trying to freeload on a movie set rather than teach kids algebra.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>