<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cable Television on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/cable-television/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cable Television on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 06:37:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/cable-television/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Case Of The Missing Channel</title>
      <link>/2018/04/06/genesis-storytime-cable-channel-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 06:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/06/genesis-storytime-cable-channel-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with an epic find from Andrew Egan. He worked really hard on this one and I wanna give him a ton of credit here. Strap in for an epic piece.
Today in Tedium: Permanence and importance are at the center of Percy Shelley&amp;rsquo;s classic poem Ozymandias. &amp;ldquo;Look upon my works ye mighty and despair,&amp;rdquo; an ancient king extols from a crumbling statue before the poem concludes. &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; the long and level sands stretch far away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Internet Will Be Televised</title>
      <link>/2016/09/14/webtv-history-20th-anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 07:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/09/14/webtv-history-20th-anniversary/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Terrible product ideas are a dime a dozen, but what about ideas that are fascinating, and perhaps executionally sound, but conceptually flawed? How often do they come about? And how often is it that they stick around the market for 17 years, despite fairly limited public interest? Such is the case of WebTV, the set-top device that allowed you to surf a television-optimized version of the web. On September 18, 1996—20 years ago this week—a startup firm released a device that meant to bring the internet to the living room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Secret Amiga</title>
      <link>/2016/03/30/cable-prevue-channel-secret-amiga/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 07:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/03/30/cable-prevue-channel-secret-amiga/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In terms of finding out what&amp;rsquo;s on the boob tube at any given time, we&amp;rsquo;ve come a long way from the overly condensed pages of TV Guide. In fact, the magazine was already looking awful obsolete in the 1980s and 1990s, when cable systems around the country began dedicating entire channels to listing TV schedules. Eventually, the approach led to the rise of the set-top box, the power-sucking block that serves as the liaison between you and your cable company.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>