<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reverse Engineering on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/reverse-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reverse Engineering on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 09:18:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/reverse-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Absolutely Brilliant!</title>
      <link>/2018/06/15/codemasters-history-nes-nintendo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/15/codemasters-history-nes-nintendo/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie from Tedium here with another piece from David Buck, who’s become something of a megafan of a video game company that wasn’t afraid to break the rules.
Today in Tedium: Throughout the years of the original Nintendo Entertainment System’s life, several companies produced games for the system. The licensed games—titles sporting the official Nintendo seal of quality—came from companies like Konami and Capcom, complete with Nintendo approved hardware, marketing and support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reverse-Engineering The Industry</title>
      <link>/2017/03/10/video-games-reverse-engineering-tengen-accolade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/10/video-games-reverse-engineering-tengen-accolade/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: When it comes to video game consoles, the manufacturers don’t like it when you bend the rules. But it happens anyway. Technically inclined individuals inevitably want to bend the platforms to their will, despite platform owners that want to protect their massive investments, and aren’t afraid to resort to lawsuits to get their way. There are plenty of cases like this, most infamously the case of the Game Genie.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>