<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Radio on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/radio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Radio on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 07:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/radio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Maybe You’ve Been Brainwashed Too</title>
      <link>/2018/10/10/new-radicals-gregg-alexander-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/10/new-radicals-gregg-alexander-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Two decades ago this month, a couple of things happened in the world of music that forever shaped the way I thought about it. One, the Barenaked Ladies scored a number-one hit on the Billboard Hot 100 with “One Week,” and a band called The New Radicals released their first and only album, *Maybe You’ve Been Brainwashed Too*—whose lead single, “You Get What You Give,” would turn the band into the perfect one-hit wonder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leavin’ The Light On</title>
      <link>/2018/02/21/tom-bodett-motel-6-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 09:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/21/tom-bodett-motel-6-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey all, Ernie here with another slice of life from my pal David Buck. This time, he gives us the story of the Great American Motel Chain, and the man whose voice defines that story.
Today in Tedium: You may recognize the voice of Tom Bodett as the whimsical narrator of those hilarious Motel 6 radio spots that have been floating around the airwaves for the past thirty years. Today’s Tedium seeks to explore the career of the man behind the voice and how he helped take what was essentially a discount motel chain and helped change its image through what AdAge magazine calls “the greatest ads of all time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy, Don’t Rent</title>
      <link>/2017/11/29/rent-to-own-rent-a-center-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/29/rent-to-own-rent-a-center-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Spend the weekend buying junk in honor of Black Friday and Cyber Monday? Lucky you. Whether your addiction of choice was Michaels, Macy’s, or Massdrop, hopefully you found just the right kind of crap. Of course, one of the key ways to sell crap is to draw people in with a TV, a laptop, or something else that’s shiny with a screen. But what if you’re trying to simply make ends need and you need a TV set or furniture?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swearing In Code</title>
      <link>/2017/05/18/pearls-before-swine-morse-code-swearing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 06:59:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/18/pearls-before-swine-morse-code-swearing/</guid>
      <description>Unless you’re listening to a numbers station for work reasons, odds are that you aren’t going to need Morse Code for any good reason. Which means that, if you want to take advantage of the lack of general knowledge of Morse Code, you absolutely can.  The folk group Pearls Before Swine, a modest psychedelic phenomenon in 1967, thought they were pulling a fast one on their audience when they recorded the tune “Oh Dear (Miss Morse),” the most popular song from the band’s hit album One Nation Underground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Invisible Puzzle</title>
      <link>/2017/05/12/wireless-spectrum-allocation-challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 07:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/12/wireless-spectrum-allocation-challenges/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Barring our constant debates on net neutrality, one of the places where the Federal Communications Commission has the largest footprint is with our wireless spectrum. It’s a spectrum that has to serve many minders, and there are constant complaints about the spectrum being crowded. But those complaints, despite feeling modern and up-to-date, are far from new—we’ve been dealing with them pretty much ever since there was spectrum regulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Around the World</title>
      <link>/2017/04/04/le-globe-radiooooo-online-radio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/04/04/le-globe-radiooooo-online-radio/</guid>
      <description>When you find an outlet that creates a sense of adventure around something as pedestrian and overexposed as online music, you know it’s worth a bookmark.  The French website Radiooooo, an online time machine that combines a Mercator projection of the globe with a radio, feels like the modern version of the shortwave radio, in some ways—except with the added dimension of time.
In a New Yorker piece last year, founder Benjamin Moreau recalled that he had the idea based on an experience of listening to modern music in his 1966 Renault Caravelle, and finding the result fully unappealing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You’re Wearing An Antenna</title>
      <link>/2017/01/23/headphones-fm-radio-antenna/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/23/headphones-fm-radio-antenna/</guid>
      <description>As it turns out, the release of the iPhone 7 last fall likely closed the door on something the broadcast industry has long crossed its fingers for.  My piece last week on FMX, the discarded radio technology that faded from view, drew a comment from reader Conrad Kramer, who was drawn to one of the side elements, where I discussed efforts by the broadcasting industry to get FM radio functionality enabled in smartphones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Touch That Dial</title>
      <link>/2017/01/18/radio-technology-upgrades-fmx-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/18/radio-technology-upgrades-fmx-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Recently, the Norwegian government—which has helped the country become first-movers on the electric car front—decided that it wanted to be ahead of another kind of curve. It was a curve that not everyone was ready for, however. Norway recently decided to drop FM radio, in favor of a modern equivalent, digital audio broadcasting (DAB). This early move comes with a lot of risks, as does every other attempt to mess with the technology that drives the airwaves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Many Lives of Packard Bell</title>
      <link>/2016/12/28/packard-bell-multiple-brand-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/12/28/packard-bell-multiple-brand-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Let’s go back in time about 20 years, to two days after Christmas, 1996. On this day, as I was becoming accustomed to Bush’s second album, millions of families around the United States were unpacking and setting up their first home computers. For those who skipped the Commodore and Apple II eras, who didn’t have a Videotex installed in their televisions, and had no idea who Commander Keen even was, this was the moment in time when they joined the internet revolution, brandishing their their AOL or Hotmail addresses for all the world to see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waaaaay Left of the Dial</title>
      <link>/2016/07/01/frankenfm-radio-fcc-analog-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/07/01/frankenfm-radio-fcc-analog-tv/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: TV on the Radio isn&amp;rsquo;t just the name of a really freaking good band. Instead, it&amp;rsquo;s a quirk of the design of analog television. But a funny thing happened on the way to obscurity: As analog TV gave way to digital, a handful of risk-taking broadcasters, sensing an opportunity, have started to run those analog TV stations as FM radio stations—big FCC plans be damned. The shift is surprisingly contentious in the world of broadcast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Signal Beats Noise</title>
      <link>/2016/05/13/dxing-radio-television-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 07:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/05/13/dxing-radio-television-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: For decades, television owners haven&amp;rsquo;t been content with simply embracing the options already in front of them. There are lots of tales of this nature throughout TV history—from the people who owned (or in some cases, built) massive satellite dishes so they could pick up obscure television signals from other parts of the world, to the public-access weirdos who have long created their own kinds of television (some of whom got really lucky), to the people who got obsessed with the Amiga in the &amp;lsquo;90s.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>