<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Apple on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/apple/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Apple on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/apple/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Clone Wars</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/apple-ii-clones-franklin-vtech/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/apple-ii-clones-franklin-vtech/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Often, retrospectives on computer history focus pretty intently on the IBM PC era and how that system’s many clones helped to democratize computing by centering most computing-industry efforts on a single platform—a major breakthrough at the time. But other platforms attracted clones as well—including the Apple II, though the computing giant’s protectionist habits kicked in quickly. And oddly enough, it may have the best thing for everyone involved—including consumers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech’s Biggest Racket</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/apple-magsafe-charger-racket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/apple-magsafe-charger-racket/</guid>
      <description>[big]Over at the New York Times, John Herrman has given voice to a certain kind of obsolescence that we’ve come to see a lot—that created not by the technology itself, but by the constant forward thrust of technology that has forced a device that technically still has a lot of years left in it into the dumpster.[/big]
“If my old iPad could talk, it might ask me what has changed,” he wrote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Mouse Pads Money Could Buy</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/mouse-pads-invention-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/mouse-pads-invention-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Is there a product that has meshed as well with the modern office as the mouse pad? The squishy, rubbery rectangle, home to a million snazzy designs and a defining piece of cubicle furniture, was (and still kinda is) like a Trapper Keeper for adults, a commodity product that was an essential accessory for computer users for decades. Even in an age where optical mice rule the roost, mouse pads are still common.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Polyphonic Screed</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/cell-phone-ringtone-history-evolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/cell-phone-ringtone-history-evolution/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: For nearly a century, the ring that we associated with a telephone sounded like a variation on this noise. It was simple, consistent. It was boring. And we eventually improved on it, especially in the digital age. When our phones shrank to pocket dimensions and their innards integrated into tiny circuits, it allowed us to redefine exactly a ringtone could be. But that created another problem entirely—the default noise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U Can’t Touch This</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/apple-touch-bar-north-carolina-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/apple-touch-bar-north-carolina-bar/</guid>
      <description>[big]Our computers are becoming so sophisticated that they might just include built-in cheating functionality—even if it’s not really intended. Which should make life pretty interesting for teachers and assessment boards.[/big]
Today’s example involves Apple’s modestly useful Touch Bar, which was met with a modest level of derision when it was first announced in September. Sensing a problem, the Board of Law Examiners of the State of North Carolina recently announced that it would require people taking the bar to turn off the Touch Bar, out of concern that it would allow users to cheat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Screwed Up</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/screw-history-standards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/screw-history-standards/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Despite the name of this internet publication, I&amp;rsquo;ve never mentioned what might perhaps be the most tedious part of the world&amp;rsquo;s modern existence, the most basic of building blocks that connects every one of our devices, manufacturing processes, and likely even the chair you&amp;rsquo;re sitting in right now: The screw. It strikes me that screws are the ultimate example of objects that hide under our noses that we never think about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Window Dressing</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/windows-fake-osx-macos-interface-skins-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/windows-fake-osx-macos-interface-skins-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: There’s something about the macOS operating system that kind of drives people wild. (Heck, even the original Mac OS has its strong partisans.) In the 17 years since Apple first launched the first iteration of the operating system based on its Darwin Unix variant, something fairly curious started to happen: People without Macs suddenly wanted the operating system, if not the hardware it ran on. This phenomenon is somewhat common today—I personally just set up a Hackintosh of my own recently—but I’d like to highlight a different kind of “Hackintosh,” the kind that played dress-up with Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>With ARM Wide Open</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/acorn-arm-holdings-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/acorn-arm-holdings-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: The computer industry is full of noble failures. Big ones. Little ones. Ideas that were 10 years too early. Ideas that were 15 years too early. Ideas that were 30 years too early. And concepts that, while fundamental to the way that our computing culture works today, hadn’t yet reached their full potential. Though certainly successful in its early years, the ARM processor very much fits in the latter category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You probably don&#39;t understand watches</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/apple-watch-haters-you-probably-dont-understand-watches/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/apple-watch-haters-you-probably-dont-understand-watches/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: If someone shows you a $10,000 watch, do you understand its inherent value, or do you roll your eyes? Do you think it looks ugly? Do you think that watches that cost a quarter of the average American&amp;rsquo;s salary make any sense whatsoever? Do you see them as an opportunity to play up the class wars a little more? Or are you a techie thinking about watches in terms of that awesome laptop with the USB-C port?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>