<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Internet Archive on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/internet-archive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Internet Archive on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 09:13:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/internet-archive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Doing It For Erma</title>
      <link>/2017/12/19/let-erma-do-it-internet-archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/19/let-erma-do-it-internet-archive/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this year, I got incredibly fascinated by a book. One that had fallen off of store shelves nearly 60 years ago. The problem was, I had no way of getting hold of that book without actually going to the trouble of buying it.  Perhaps that was a little annoying, but David O. Woodbury’s 1956 work Let Erma Do It, which is titled after one of the first automated check-sorting systems ever produced, was a worthy book at the front end of the era of automation that has brought us so many things since.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down With Snippet View</title>
      <link>/2017/06/27/google-books-snippet-view-archival/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 03:29:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/27/google-books-snippet-view-archival/</guid>
      <description>You may or may not have noticed this, but Tedium relies pretty heavily on archival content to exist. This newsletter and publication is not just about offering up weird facts: It&amp;rsquo;s often about introducing facts that have otherwise been forgotten about by the public at large.  Sometimes, this takes me in some interesting directions. An example I regularly cite is my piece on lemon juice squeeze bottles. It was the rare piece I had the chance to mostly write ahead of time, and while there were some incredibly useful starting points on the issue from the Beach Packaging Design, I find it important that, even if an existing resource like this offers a starting point, I spend time doing some digging of my own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Impurrfect History</title>
      <link>/2017/01/25/cats-dot-com-domain-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 21:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/25/cats-dot-com-domain-history/</guid>
      <description>Let’s face facts: Having an awesome domain name is no guarantee for success. This was proven just a couple of weeks ago in my piece about the failure of Pets.com. But it still highlights a whole lot of potential.  Which is why the recent domain sale of Cats.com—literally, an entire domain name for the internet’s favorite animal—is one that we should closely watch. The domain is currently sitting at $125,000 on the auction site Flippa, and will sell to the highest bidder in the next five days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Internet&#39;s First Election</title>
      <link>/2016/10/19/1992-election-internet-influence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 07:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/10/19/1992-election-internet-influence/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: For the past 20 years, a familiar trend has exposed itself with the turn of every U.S. presidential election cycle: Each one is ever-slightly more defined (heck, even redefined) by technology, particularly online trends that have come along in the three years prior. In 1996, it was a coming-out party for the web. In 2000, the growth of online news began to have an impact on how we researched candidates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>