<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Domains on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/domains/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Domains on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 06:27:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/domains/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Purple Unicorn</title>
      <link>/2017/11/07/purple-com-domain-sold/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 06:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/07/purple-com-domain-sold/</guid>
      <description>For more than 23 years, the Purple.com domain reflected one guy’s simple, colorful vision. But last week, the man who owned what was secretly becoming the internet’s most valuable domain finally sold it. To … wait for it … a mattress company.  Per Domain Investing, Purple Innovations LLC, the company that owns the hipster mattress giant worth an estimated $1.1 billion, purchased the domain from Jeff Abrahamson, who spent more than two decades pledging that he would never sell the domain—instead suggesting he’d rather hold onto the URL and license it out to an interested party for a six-digit sum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Purple</title>
      <link>/2017/03/23/purple-com-early-domain-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 06:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/23/purple-com-early-domain-website/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE (11/06/2017): He finally sold out to the hipster mattress giant. Read an update here.
Can you build a brand while working around one of the oldest sites on the internet? The answer appears to be yes.  Since 1994, a guy named Jeff Abrahamson has run the website Purple.com, a domain name which lives up to its name—the site features a deep, rich hue of purple (originally #DD00FF, now #7D26CD), a link to an FAQ page, and an offer to advertise in a very minimal way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>