<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Computers on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/computers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Computers on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 06:39:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/computers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Persistence</title>
      <link>/2018/10/05/sgi-collector-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 06:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/05/sgi-collector-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey all, Ernie here with a recent piece of mine that also showed up in Motherboard. In case you haven&amp;rsquo;t read it yet, it&amp;rsquo;s a good one and highlights both SGI and the the excellent community IRIX.cc. Read on, and hope you dig!
Today in Tedium: Recently, I was faced with an unusual question about a piece of hardware that very few people have ever used. The question: What makes a giant workstation, one that once cost as much as a house when it was first produced in the early ‘90s and makes as much noise as a vacuum, so appealing to a 16-year-old?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Command Line</title>
      <link>/2018/07/18/dos-nostalgia-squirrel-monkey-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/18/dos-nostalgia-squirrel-monkey-interview/</guid>
      <description>Hey all, Ernie here with a fresh piece from David Buck, who has moved away from his NES for a while to tell you all about how awesome DOS is as a creative medium. Yeah, DOS.
Today in Tedium: From the early 90s, up until 2005 or so, I did much of my computer gaming on an American Megatrends IBM PC, running MS-DOS and Windows 3.11. I even got online once using Netscape Communicator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Toy That Talked Back</title>
      <link>/2018/06/20/speak-and-spell-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/20/speak-and-spell-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Four decades ago this month, a company that helped set the stage for the modern computing era got into the toy market thanks to an announcement at the 1978 Summer Consumer Electronics Show. While it wasn’t the first time that kids got their hands on something truly electronic, its influence ran deep, even as its technology was fairly primitive. With its robotic voice and limited memory, the Speak &amp;amp; Spell somehow mixed the seemingly incompatible worlds of education and entertainment in an impressive way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>With ARM Wide Open</title>
      <link>/2018/06/08/acorn-arm-holdings-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/08/acorn-arm-holdings-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The computer industry is full of noble failures. Big ones. Little ones. Ideas that were 10 years too early. Ideas that were 15 years too early. Ideas that were 30 years too early. And concepts that, while fundamental to the way that our computing culture works today, hadn’t yet reached their full potential. Though certainly successful in its early years, the ARM processor very much fits in the latter category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Some Noise</title>
      <link>/2018/05/11/sound-blaster-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/11/sound-blaster-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey all, Ernie here with a classic (though lightly updated) Tedium piece about one of the defining pieces of ’90s computer technology: The Sound Blaster. Crank it up!
Today in Tedium: Before we embraced MP3s as the official noise of the internet (taking the place of screechy modems), it took a while before the synthesized notes of our musical past could be modulated through the inner-workings of a computer. Some of our earliest computers, for example, could only make very basic bleeps and bloops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Oracle That Spoke Too Soon</title>
      <link>/2018/04/13/larry-ellison-network-computer-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 07:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/13/larry-ellison-network-computer-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Oracle has a few reasons to hate Google. The search company built a significant chunk of its empire, the Android operating system, based on Java, a programming language created by one of Oracle’s largest acquisitions, Sun Microsystems. As a result, the two companies have been going at it in court for years now. Google won a few rounds, but Oracle, more importantly, won the latest, likely ensuring a Supreme Court showdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camper Van Mainframe</title>
      <link>/2018/03/16/early-portable-computer-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 07:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/16/early-portable-computer-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Portability is relative. When former Texas Instruments employees Rod Canion, Jim Harris and Bill Murto created a portable version of the IBM PC in 1982, it was a hulking device that weight 28 pounds and was roughly the size of a sewing machine. If you sold a desktop computer that weighed 28 pounds in 2018, you’d be laughed off the block. But the device, called the Compaq Portable, was revolutionary for its time and thrust the company that made it into the mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How&#39;s Your Soldering Technique?</title>
      <link>/2018/01/26/soldering-technology-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 09:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/26/soldering-technology-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: A lot of people use electronics with little to no idea of what actually happens inside of the little box they have on their desk or in their pockets. Sure, we might talk about the chips inside of that machine, or the processing power, but rarely do we think about the connective tissue holding many of the circuits onto the silicon. That tissue is solder, the meltable filler metal that has existed in one form or another for more than 4,000 years—long before electronics even existed as a modern context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dots Vs. Pixels</title>
      <link>/2018/01/19/dots-per-inch-pixels-per-inch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 09:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/19/dots-per-inch-pixels-per-inch/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: If you stare into the heart of your smartphone for a while, you may start to make out the pixels. If your smartphone is really old, like the original iPhone or a cheap Android phone, that might not take a while, because the pixel resolution is quite low. But if you have an iPhone X, with its 458ppi (pixels per inch) OLED screen, perhaps it might not be so easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flash Forward</title>
      <link>/2017/11/24/flash-memory-compactflash-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 09:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/24/flash-memory-compactflash-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Thanksgiving, of course, was a day full of memories. You, of course, need a place to store all those memories—and for a long time, preferably in a way that makes them easy to access for many years to come. It would also help if that method was easy to carry, easy to store, and, well, was standardized. For years, when it came to pictures, that format was, of course, film.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Scrolling Orb</title>
      <link>/2017/10/13/trackball-input-device-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/13/trackball-input-device-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Ever find yourself in a bar with a single arcade machine, and the machine is inevitably not targeting gamers? Like, rather than, say, a fighting game or something iconic like NBA Jam or even Donkey Kong, it’s either a variation of Big Buck Hunter, a bowling game like Silver Strike Bowling, or a golf game like Golden Tee. These games, of course, aim for a wide audience, quite literally in the case of Big Buck Hunter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Early Touchpoint</title>
      <link>/2017/09/22/wacom-tablet-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 07:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/22/wacom-tablet-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: There was once a time when I worked in graphic design—mostly in newspapers—and as a result of that, I owned a tablet. For drawing, of course. It didn’t have a screen. I wasn’t a great artist by any means, but that little Wacom device was a nice functionality add when I was tweaking cutouts and hopping into Photoshop or Illustrator. (I’m pretty good at cutouts if I do say so myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Booting Up The Cash Register</title>
      <link>/2017/08/04/early-computer-retailers-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 07:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/04/early-computer-retailers-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The modern computer store, as I&amp;rsquo;ve argued in the past, is a bit of a mess. It’s all about the hard sell (in a gigantic box) at the cost of any personality whatsoever. It was so bad that Apple (and later, Microsoft) had to create its own self-branded stores to ensure their products were seen in the proper light. This is kind of painful, of course, because personal computers were really the domain of the hobbyist at first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Tech Hit Retail</title>
      <link>/2017/07/21/point-of-sale-retail-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 07:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/21/point-of-sale-retail-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: If it feels like the the “robots are trying to steal our jobs” meme is a new development, I have some news for you: It’s really not. For decades, automation has been implied to be the cause of—and solution to—all life’s problems. Nowhere is this more the case than in the halls of retail, where automation helped redefine our interaction with shopping in important ways. And those innovations are still happening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Spin Me Right Round, Baby</title>
      <link>/2017/05/31/early-hard-drive-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 07:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/31/early-hard-drive-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Hard drives may be the most fundamental building block of the computer revolution. Hitting the perfect balance between size and cost, it was a defining piece of computer history, one that made our machines more permanent and helped us rethink the way we store information. With a hard drive, we were eventually able to move away from the idea of thinking of our documents in terms of a linear order and a physical space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>86’ed</title>
      <link>/2017/05/19/intel-386-486-trademark-battles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/19/intel-386-486-trademark-battles/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Why did Intel move away from naming its widely used microprocessors after numbers—you know, like the 286 and the 386? They were perfectly succinct, along with easy to remember—what’s not to like? As it turns out, Intel was very much into the idea of using these numbers, and really wanted to stick with it. But legal and trademark-related problems got in the way. The same spirit of reverse-engineering innovation that gave Intel its longtime advantage in the world of desktop computers ultimately cost it the right to hold onto its numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operating In Obscurity</title>
      <link>/2017/04/21/obscure-operating-systems-os2-qnx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 07:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/04/21/obscure-operating-systems-os2-qnx/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Operating systems are the cockroaches of the digital revolution. They’re everywhere, hiding in low-level crevices, and most of the time, you don’t really notice when they’re there—except, of course, when they draw attention to themselves. (Cough, cough Windows 8 cough.) But most of those operating systems fade from view—except when they don’t. Case in point: The company Arca Noae claims it’s about to launch a brand-new version of IBM’s coulda-been ‘90s contender, OS/2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Soft</title>
      <link>/2017/03/21/dial-up-soft-modem-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 07:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/21/dial-up-soft-modem-history/</guid>
      <description>Dial-up modems were underpowered enough back in the days of AOL, but at the height of their popularity, manufacturers figured out a way to make them even worse.  During the late ‘90s, a spate of companies, including big name modem manufacturers like U.S. Robotics, Motorola, and PCtel, had the idea to replace hardware-based modems, which generally required a separate digital signal processor to manage the dial-up connection, with software-based equivalents, which took this task and put it on top of the CPU already being used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s All In The Cards</title>
      <link>/2017/01/27/pcmcia-pc-card-laptop-expansion-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/27/pcmcia-pc-card-laptop-expansion-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The problem with laptops has, at least in recent years, been one of expandability. Once you buy a machine, you’re generally stuck with it, unless you’re willing to take it apart with repairs that have more in common with surgery than mechanics. Part of this has to do with the complexity of our modern machines, but a bigger part is the fact that, simply, upgradability has become less of a concern for manufacturers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Many Lives of Packard Bell</title>
      <link>/2016/12/28/packard-bell-multiple-brand-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/12/28/packard-bell-multiple-brand-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Let’s go back in time about 20 years, to two days after Christmas, 1996. On this day, as I was becoming accustomed to Bush’s second album, millions of families around the United States were unpacking and setting up their first home computers. For those who skipped the Commodore and Apple II eras, who didn’t have a Videotex installed in their televisions, and had no idea who Commander Keen even was, this was the moment in time when they joined the internet revolution, brandishing their their AOL or Hotmail addresses for all the world to see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Annoying Clicking Sound</title>
      <link>/2016/12/07/iomega-zip-disk-click-of-death-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/12/07/iomega-zip-disk-click-of-death-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: As proprietary, non-standardized formats go, Iomega’s Zip drive got a heck of a lot further than most of its competitors. It managed to improve on a format people were used to (the old floppy) just enough that it ensured it’d gain popularity. It fit niches for people who had to share a lot of data. And it even had a sizable base of home users—which was impressive for its time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons From The Video Professor</title>
      <link>/2016/11/16/video-professor-infomercial-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 08:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/11/16/video-professor-infomercial-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Home computers and infomercials were always meant to go together. Here were these devices, arguably the most complex products ever to enter homes in Middle America, and they needed a lot of explaining at first. (Not complicated explanations, mind you. Simple ones.) Enter Video Professor. For two decades, John Scherer made millions by selling educational products to the public, mostly through late-night infomercials and on home-shopping networks like QVC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Original In-App Purchase</title>
      <link>/2016/10/28/shareware-history-legacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 07:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/10/28/shareware-history-legacy/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Before software, purchases generally worked like this: You walked into a store, you bought a physical object, and that object was yours until it became damaged or outdated, and you threw it out. But software, being much smaller in physical space than any commercial object that came before it, wasn&amp;rsquo;t limited by these rules. Data came in bits and bytes, and could be dripped out or distributed in any number of ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Were Selling Computers All Wrong</title>
      <link>/2016/10/12/big-box-retail-computers-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 07:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/10/12/big-box-retail-computers-problems/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The big-box technology store isn&amp;rsquo;t dead yet—and in the case of Best Buy, it&amp;rsquo;s actually doing pretty well, beating financial estimates by a country mile. But as a whole, the concept of the sprawling electronics chain is far from its peak. In fact, it&amp;rsquo;s sort of another shade of the office-supply store. Despite that, investors keep trying to revive this idea. Right now, an investor named Ronny Shmoel is trying to bring Circuit City back to life as a physical presence, roughly seven years after the brand was mothballed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Is Running Out</title>
      <link>/2016/07/20/y2k-hoarding-survivalists-freakout/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 07:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/07/20/y2k-hoarding-survivalists-freakout/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The latter months of 1999 were like looking into the great unknown, and all thanks to a computer bug the public barely even understood. A logical person could tell you that odds were high you were going to fall asleep as the ball dropped, wake up in the morning, turn on the lights, and still hear the dulcet tones of Moby&amp;rsquo;s pop-electronica experiments rattling on the radio the next morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Other Windows</title>
      <link>/2016/04/29/geoworks-windows-3-1-competitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/04/29/geoworks-windows-3-1-competitor/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Back in the early &amp;lsquo;90s, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a sure thing that Microsoft Windows was going to take over the market, even though they had a clear lead over many of their competitors, thanks to MS-DOS. In fact, one of the iconic GUI-based experiences of the era, AOL, hedged its bets for a while, creating and maintaining a DOS version of its iconic pseudo-internet software using an GUI platform few were familiar with: GeoWorks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Secret Amiga</title>
      <link>/2016/03/30/cable-prevue-channel-secret-amiga/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 07:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/03/30/cable-prevue-channel-secret-amiga/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In terms of finding out what&amp;rsquo;s on the boob tube at any given time, we&amp;rsquo;ve come a long way from the overly condensed pages of TV Guide. In fact, the magazine was already looking awful obsolete in the 1980s and 1990s, when cable systems around the country began dedicating entire channels to listing TV schedules. Eventually, the approach led to the rise of the set-top box, the power-sucking block that serves as the liaison between you and your cable company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Some Noise</title>
      <link>/2016/02/10/creative-sound-blaster-sound-card-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 05:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/02/10/creative-sound-blaster-sound-card-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Before we embraced MP3s as the official noise of the internet (taking the place of screechy modems), it took a while before the synthesized notes of our musical past could be modulated through the inner-workings of a computer. Some of our earliest computers, for example, could only make very basic bleeps and bloops. But in 1989, everything changed when a Singaporean company called Creative Technology hit upon the perfect approach for synthesizing sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A phone book for computers</title>
      <link>/2015/08/12/computer-shopper-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 08:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/12/computer-shopper-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The phone book isn&amp;rsquo;t really anyone&amp;rsquo;s idea of an innovative product, but it definitely had its place on the shelf of many a home before the internet took over. In the late throes of the age of the white pages, however, an unusually large magazine stole the hearts of many a techie, and in the process became something of a bible for people looking to replace their 286 with a 486—and maybe buy a laser printer in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re going viral</title>
      <link>/2015/07/24/early-computer-virus-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 06:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/07/24/early-computer-virus-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The computer virus has kind of taken on a life of its own in popular culture, often being seen as a device that destroys computers and data, while making itself known in the process. Things have changed since that hallowed era—the malware is still with us, but the way it attacks computers has changed drastically since the &amp;lsquo;80s. Today, we talk about computer viruses as if we&amp;rsquo;re in the midst of an archaeological dig.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tales Of The Interwebs</title>
      <link>/2015/02/18/early-internet-history-tales/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2015 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/18/early-internet-history-tales/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Last week, one of the men who created the internet as we know it sounded the alarms on its future. Vinton Cerf, a Google executive and one of the architects of ARPANET, noted that decades of files could be lost to history, with no way to access the documents, due to lacking digital preservation efforts. “When you think about the quantity of documentation from our daily lives that is captured in digital form, like our interactions by email, people’s tweets, and all of the world wide web, it’s clear that we stand to lose an awful lot of our history,” he said, according to The Guardian.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>