<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 09:15:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Straight Flush</title>
      <link>/2018/03/07/uncle-johns-bathroom-reader-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/07/uncle-johns-bathroom-reader-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie from Tedium here with a fresh piece from Andrew Egan, who wants to tell you all about a series of books that come in handy during a certain time of the day … uh, I’ll let him explain it. Thanks Andrew!
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: Book publishing is no stranger to specialty products. From leather-bound editions of classic literature, to coffee table books, publishers will provide anything to take advantage of people’s need to look smart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biography, Unauthorized</title>
      <link>/2018/01/10/kitty-kelley-michael-wolff-unauthorized-biography-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/10/kitty-kelley-michael-wolff-unauthorized-biography-history/</guid>
      <description>Editor’s note: Hey guys, Ernie here with a surprisingly timely piece from Andrew Egan. Just a word of warning—the subject matter is a little on the scandalous side, so if you’re not in the mood for that, may I suggest this piece about Teddy Ruxpin instead? If you’re cool with it, keep reading.
Today in Tedium: The rules guiding journalists have never been understood by the larger public. Phrases like “off the record” and “confirmed source” seem self-explanatory but are governed by detailed rules that often flumox seasoned journalists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Running Out of Widgets</title>
      <link>/2017/09/13/barnes-noble-third-place-widgets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 05:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/13/barnes-noble-third-place-widgets/</guid>
      <description>Editor’s note: Apple’s revelation on Tuesday that it was rethinking its approach to stores into something akin to a “town square” got me thinking about an old piece I wrote a while back—one that I, ironically, was just interviewed about for Ozy. In lieu of a fresh one, here’s a lightly refreshed 2015 piece that still feels pretty relevant.
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: When physical objects can be turned into a series of bits and bytes and streamed over the airwaves, the result is that stores start running out of things to sell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who’s Who? Who Cares</title>
      <link>/2017/07/19/whos-who-vanity-publishing-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 07:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/19/whos-who-vanity-publishing-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: On an average day floating through the press release service PR Newswire, it’s inevitable that you run into a list of people who are designated as new members of the “Who’s Who” list. The list always varies but the intent is always the same: To give a person notice for their life and career. The problem with these lists is that, in an era where everyone is seemingly notable for something, they seem to amount to a hill of beans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Killed The Encyclopedia?</title>
      <link>/2017/07/14/who-killed-the-encyclopedia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 07:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/14/who-killed-the-encyclopedia/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The CD-ROM was sold to the public and the world as a way to bring interactive multimedia experiences into our homes. (Certainly, that&amp;rsquo;s how the magazine world tried to sell it.) But beyond that, it was a sheer amount of storage for a price that was insane to consider at the time. And that meant that some of the earliest products produced for the CD-ROM format were of the reference variety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Gnome Fad</title>
      <link>/2017/03/07/gnomes-1977-literary-fad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 09:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/07/gnomes-1977-literary-fad/</guid>
      <description>Quick: Four decades ago, back in 1977, what was the biggest pop-culture phenomena around? You probably said disco, maybe Star Wars. Fleetwood Mac was big that year. Maybe you thought of Laverne &amp;amp; Shirley, the top-rated show of that year.  But one surprisingly forgotten but unappreciated piece of pop culture that hit in a big way that year was the Gnome fad. The 1977 kid’s book, published in English in October of that year, became a massive phenomenon, one that was a mainstay on the New York Times bestseller list for more than a year after its release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delivered To Your Door</title>
      <link>/2017/02/17/monthly-subscription-box-delivery-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/02/17/monthly-subscription-box-delivery-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Don’t let the talk of content on the cloud fool you. It’s easier than ever to get physical stuff mailed to your duplex nearly every single day of the year. (OK, maybe it’s not Jetsons-easy yet. We’ll get there.) In recent years, that’s led to the rise of subscription box services like Birchbox, BlueApron, and Loot Crate. (Personally, I’m obsessed with Blue Bottle’s biweekly coffee bean delivery service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books on Vinyl</title>
      <link>/2016/02/19/audiobooks-blind-vinyl-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 09:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/02/19/audiobooks-blind-vinyl-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It&amp;rsquo;s the great challenge of a newsletter editor when they hear this phrase—&amp;rdquo;hey, this newsletter would be really good as a podcast!&amp;rdquo; I understand the demand for things like this, because people love sounds running into their ears when they&amp;rsquo;re on the go, and you have to physically press your fingers down on your phone to read Tedium. But I&amp;rsquo;m way more clever and way less likely to say &amp;ldquo;like&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;y&amp;rsquo;know&amp;rdquo; when I write things down, so that&amp;rsquo;s why this comes in a text format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burn After Reading</title>
      <link>/2015/07/08/burn-after-reading-controversial-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/07/08/burn-after-reading-controversial-books/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In the age of the internet, it&amp;rsquo;s easier than ever to get one&amp;rsquo;s hand on information that touches the very edge of the First Amendment&amp;rsquo;s limits. (We are by no means recommending you do that. Stick to Disney.com.) But before that, if you wanted to tell someone how to make a bomb in the kitchen of your mom—as an al-Qaeda magazine once infamously put it—it came down to literature.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>