<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Currency on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/currency/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Currency on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 09:15:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/currency/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cashing In Early</title>
      <link>/2017/11/28/digicash-ecash-bitcoin-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/28/digicash-ecash-bitcoin-history/</guid>
      <description>Cryptocurrency is having a bit of a moment right now, thanks in no small part to bitcoin, the currency launched under unusual circumstances that has suddenly become really, really popular. (As I write this, it’s continuing its daylong flirtation with the $10,000 valuation mark.)  But of course, while cryptocurrency is growing in popularity, bitcoin and other blockchain-based currencies can’t come close to making the claim to being the first digital currency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your money is worthless here</title>
      <link>/2015/06/24/your-money-is-worthless-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 07:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/24/your-money-is-worthless-here/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: If you&amp;rsquo;re watching the right digital substation, the message is hard to ignore. Ron Paul says we&amp;rsquo;re facing a catastrophic financial crisis that could leave you screwed. That&amp;rsquo;s a weird message to hear from any former politician, even one with the libertarian bonafides of Ron Paul. (His son Rand must be psyched that this is how he&amp;rsquo;s spending his retirement.) But the paid ads, which are designed to get you to buy some financial services you don&amp;rsquo;t need, nonetheless offer a funhouse mirror from which to consider the market forces that cause currency to lose its value.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>