<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 07:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Members Only</title>
      <link>/2018/06/29/non-performing-band-members-coldplay-grateful-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/29/non-performing-band-members-coldplay-grateful-dead/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: “Look at the stars, look how they shine for you, and all the things that you do, non-performing band member …” I personally gained a major distaste for Coldplay sometime in the early naughts, when I failed to understand the appeal of “Clocks,” despite having enjoyed Parachutes. Perhaps it’s for that reason I never realized that Coldplay has five members, that I assumed they were a quartet. Certainly there are four members on stage actually playing the songs, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What if Tedium … Had Lyrics?</title>
      <link>/2018/06/14/brentalfloss-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 06:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/14/brentalfloss-interview/</guid>
      <description>As our readers are now undoubtedly aware, there are two things I’m incredibly interested in—unique types of music and the history/technical aspects/playing the games of the original Nintendo Entertainment System (I’m also really into miniatures, FWIW). Knowing this, it was only a matter of time before I discovered someone who combined these two interests into one. Unlike U2, circa 1987, I found what I was looking for almost a decade ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mystic Knights of the Movie Soundtrack</title>
      <link>/2018/03/15/oingo-boingo-pop-culture-appearances/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 07:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/15/oingo-boingo-pop-culture-appearances/</guid>
      <description>Before Danny Elfman became the go-to guy for scoring great films, his band Oingo Boingo was a mid-&amp;lsquo;80s go-to for soundtrack contributions. This ensured that, even as Elfman moved away from the band, Oingo Boingo would carry a massive pop-culture footprint.  &amp;ldquo;I think Oingo&amp;rsquo;s music is good for the audience for those films; the people will relate to it,&amp;rdquo; Elfman said of the phenomenon, according to the Encyclopedia of Pop, Rock &amp;amp; Soul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Wave Titans</title>
      <link>/2018/03/14/oingo-boingo-danny-elfman-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 07:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/14/oingo-boingo-danny-elfman-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with another piece from David Buck. Last we saw of him, he was talking to Tom Bodett. Tonight, he’s obsessing over an iconic West Coast band. Read on; it&amp;rsquo;s worth it.
Today in Tedium: If you’re a fan of director Tim Burton, you may recognize the name Danny Elfman. If you’re a Nightmare before Christmas fan, you may even recognize his voice. But, did you know he started his music career with a band called The Mystic Knights of the Oingo Boingo (later just Oingo Boingo)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh? Haven’t You Heard?</title>
      <link>/2018/02/02/surfin-bird-song-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/02/surfin-bird-song-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with another piece from David Buck, who knows the truth about the Surfin’ Bird. Previously, he was talkin’ Y2K.
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: In a recent Tedium piece, Ernie posed the question: “Can one become nostalgic for abrasive noises?” He was referring to alarm clocks, but that got me thinking about songs others may find annoying or abrasive like “It’s Halloween” by the Shaggs, just about anything by the Legendary Stardust Cowboy, and an old surf song that seems to keep popping up in my life—“Surfin’ Bird.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primitive Streaming Gods</title>
      <link>/2018/01/31/legal-music-streaming-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/31/legal-music-streaming-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: This week, the music industry had a pretty good reason to cheer, and not just because of the Grammys. They won big in Washington, after the the United States Copyright Royalty Board ruled in favor of songwriters that felt like they had gotten the short end of the stick from Spotify, Apple Music, and the like. Over the next five years, the guy who wrote “All Star” and the dude who wrote “Fish Heads” will see their royalties go up by nearly 45 percent—a sign that, given time, the system works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock On Chicago</title>
      <link>/2017/11/17/wesley-willis-remembrance-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 09:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/17/wesley-willis-remembrance-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with a fresh Tedium piece comes from outsider artist aficionado and newsletter contributor David J. Buck, who hit us up last time with a piece on Wild Man Fischer. By popular demand, here’s a piece on Wesley Willis!
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: People loved Wesley Willis. Despite a rough upbringing, struggles with mental illness, extreme poverty and an abusive family, he was friendly and lovable. Wesley became a Chicago icon, building a network of friends, fans, and followers along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hide And Seek</title>
      <link>/2017/11/10/hidden-tracks-album-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 09:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/10/hidden-tracks-album-history/</guid>
      <description>Editor’s note: Tonight’s issue is a slightly expanded rerun of a classic issue of Tedium with some additional info added in spots where it makes sense. Enjoy!
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: We gained a lot when albums went fully digital, but we also lost a bunch of stuff along the way. Among the things we lost: Record sleeves, media towers, and Tower Records. We have digital equivalents of all these things, so it&amp;rsquo;s not like we necessarily miss them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Behind By A Century</title>
      <link>/2017/11/10/the-tragically-hip-appreciation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 06:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/10/the-tragically-hip-appreciation/</guid>
      <description>My wife, for years, has had this tendency of deciding to watch some shows, usually dramas, only after their run has completed, which I’m sure that TV studios friggin’ love. Sometimes, though, there’s so much out there that it’s just functionally easier to tackle a body of work like Weeds in full, over the span of a week, rather than as a number of disparate, easily-forgotten pieces.  Music, which has always been more of my forte, often doesn’t have this problem—a song is usually self-contained in a theme, and an album usually stands on its own as a complete thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congratulations I’m Sorry</title>
      <link>/2017/09/29/gin-blossoms-hey-jealousy-tragedy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 06:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/29/gin-blossoms-hey-jealousy-tragedy/</guid>
      <description>“Do you think it’d be all right if I could just crash here tonight?” The introduction to “Hey Jealousy,” the 1992 song by the Gin Blossoms, introduces a lackadaisical ne’er-do-well, one who laments the loss of an old relationship while asking his ex for a place to ward off his hangover, because he has nowhere else to go.  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ah5gAkna3jI
Unlike Nirvana or Pearl Jam, the darkness of the lyrics wasn’t matched by a darkness in the melody—the tune, in fact, had more in common with a melodic tune from R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art, Commerce, and Zamfir</title>
      <link>/2017/07/26/heartland-music-direct-tv-music-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 07:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/26/heartland-music-direct-tv-music-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: When I grew up, I listened to a lot of John Denver. Well, not really full songs, so much as the 10-second snippets of tunes that played during his commercials on late-night cable TV. “You fill up my senses like a night in the forest,” Denver sang to the masses, even though he was really only singing to Annie, his first wife. But those choruses and hooks had a way of bleeding together into one super-song.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Countering the Counterculture</title>
      <link>/2017/01/09/countering-the-counterculture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/09/countering-the-counterculture/</guid>
      <description>When someone mentions the phrase “Christian music,” what comes to mind? Beyond hymnals, maybe DC Talk, Jars of Clay, Kirk Franklin, or Amy Grant? Those are all good answers—answers that highlight the fact that “Jesus music” has occasionally gone mainstream in the past few decades. Heck, sometimes bands that are mainstream but spiritual, like Lifehouse, go out of their way to avoid the “Christian band” label.  But there was a time when Christian rock was less about reaching broad audiences and more about speaking out against a disinterested public—think the visceral reaction to *Time Magazine*’s &amp;ldquo;Is God Dead?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Damage &amp; Dissonance</title>
      <link>/2016/03/18/fixing-broken-guitars-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 05:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/03/18/fixing-broken-guitars-lessons/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It&amp;rsquo;s not often that we get to say, &amp;ldquo;Poor Bryan Adams,&amp;rdquo; but a recent experience he dealt with at an Egyptian airport was definitely worthy of that rarely used phrase. Adams, the artist behind most of our important schmaltz-rock, had most of his instruments tagged by Egyptian customs officials who couldn&amp;rsquo;t care less whether they were handling a 1957 Martin guitar or a guitar promoted by the guy from Maroon 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trippin&#39; On A Hole In A Paper Heart</title>
      <link>/2015/12/09/scott-weiland-stone-temple-pilots-what-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2015 07:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/09/scott-weiland-stone-temple-pilots-what-next/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: As we were putting the finishing touches on last Thursday&amp;rsquo;s Tedium, a terrible bit of news hit the internet—the death of Scott Weiland, one of the most influential rock vocalists of the last quarter-century. Weiland&amp;rsquo;s death, for many, was not a surprise, and that fact was touched upon by his former band, Stone Temple Pilots. In 2013, Weiland was kicked out of the band he helped make famous, leading to a lengthy legal battle between the two sides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tape Deck Heart</title>
      <link>/2015/08/21/magnetic-tape-revival/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2015 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/21/magnetic-tape-revival/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: When&amp;rsquo;s the big comeback for magnetic tapes coming around, anyway? These days, vinyl is making a serious comeback with the public. Even Taylor Swift is selling a ton of vinyl records these days. But in a world where streaming and optical discs are more common than ever, the magnetic tape—which arguably has as much nostalgic hipster cachet as the vinyl record, and across a variety of formats at that—hasn&amp;rsquo;t seen nearly as much love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of Creative Destruction</title>
      <link>/2015/08/07/a-tale-of-creative-destruction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/07/a-tale-of-creative-destruction/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The early Counting Crows hit &amp;ldquo;Mr. Jones&amp;rdquo; was a lie. Take that back—the incident was real, and Adam Duritz did hang out with a guy with the last name Jones, but the song&amp;rsquo;s whole plotline about how they were gonna be happier when they were famous didn&amp;rsquo;t come to pass. If you go to a Counting Crows show these days, in fact, the lyric is now &amp;ldquo;we all wanna be big, big stars, yeah, but then we get second thoughts about that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The first 12 cost a penny, but …</title>
      <link>/2015/06/12/columbia-house-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/12/columbia-house-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Yesterday, a coworker and good friend of mine revealed to me a fact that made me feel very old. We were talking about Spotify—and his desire not to pay $10 per month for the service—and I referenced Columbia House. He did not know what I was talking about. I was taken aback by this news—I thought everyone knew what Columbia House was! The mail-order CD service (along with its competitor BMG) had a bright moment in the early &amp;lsquo;90s, only to see its business model fall apart thanks to iTunes, and later, Spotify.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In front of the music</title>
      <link>/2015/06/03/worst-album-covers-analyzed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/03/worst-album-covers-analyzed/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Nearly as long as there has been the internet, there have been lists of terrible album covers—many of which predate the internet and are looked at using modern standards for humor and kitsch. But the problem with these images is that there&amp;rsquo;s often no story behind them, because they&amp;rsquo;re often not shared with any information to speak of. They&amp;rsquo;re historic memes, but they never seem to have any attached history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searching for the perfect tones</title>
      <link>/2015/04/29/unusual-musical-instruments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/04/29/unusual-musical-instruments/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: If you&amp;rsquo;ve never seen a 12-foot-tall upright piano, you&amp;rsquo;re in for a treat. The neo-classical German musician Nils Frahm recorded his latest album, Solo, on such a device, the Klavins Model 370. Frahm told Pitchfork that the experience was so inspiring that he wanted to launch a crowdfunding effort to help the piano&amp;rsquo;s creator, David Klavins, build an even taller instrument. (Read about that here.) Today, inspired by Frahm&amp;rsquo;s excitement, we want to talk about some incredibly bizarre instruments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walk on the Vinyl Side</title>
      <link>/2015/04/17/soundalike-records-walk-on-the-vinyl-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 07:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/04/17/soundalike-records-walk-on-the-vinyl-side/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Late rock legend Lou Reed has been in the news lately for a somewhat odd reason. On Monday, Reed&amp;rsquo;s sister wrote about her brother&amp;rsquo;s medical situation during his teenage years—when, the rumor goes, his parents had him undergo electroshock therapy to fend off homosexual urges. (Lou did undergo the controversial therapy treatment, but his sister denies that latent homosexuality was the cause. Speaking of their parents, she explains: &amp;ldquo;They were caught in a bewildering web of guilt, fear, and poor psychiatric care.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>