<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Branding on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/branding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Branding on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 07:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/branding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Giving Candy A Bad Name</title>
      <link>/2018/09/21/ayds-candy-branding-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/09/21/ayds-candy-branding-problem/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: A few years ago, the wireless industry thought it could win a potentially lucrative game—that of the mobile wallet, which was just starting to get off the ground thanks to the smartphone. They had all the elements in place to pull it off, including support of most of the major wireless providers. But there was a problem—the name. Back in 2010, naming a technology product ISIS Wallet might have seemed like a novel idea, but by 2014, the name had become forever associated with a terrorist organization, and the idea had completely lost momentum as a result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Many Lives of Packard Bell</title>
      <link>/2016/12/28/packard-bell-multiple-brand-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/12/28/packard-bell-multiple-brand-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Let’s go back in time about 20 years, to two days after Christmas, 1996. On this day, as I was becoming accustomed to Bush’s second album, millions of families around the United States were unpacking and setting up their first home computers. For those who skipped the Commodore and Apple II eras, who didn’t have a Videotex installed in their televisions, and had no idea who Commander Keen even was, this was the moment in time when they joined the internet revolution, brandishing their their AOL or Hotmail addresses for all the world to see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America The Processed</title>
      <link>/2016/05/11/america-beer-budweiser-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/05/11/america-beer-budweiser-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: How arrogant do you have to be to name your product after an entire country, to assume that you&amp;rsquo;ve earned that right? On Tuesday, the no-longer-American company Anheuser-Busch InBev announced that it was temporarily changing the name of its inexplicably popular beverage Budweiser to America, ahead of the 2016 election. &amp;ldquo;It’s something that we could have not done overnight. If we’d launched Budweiser yesterday, as a new brand, we probably wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have had the license to do it,&amp;rdquo; Budweiser Vice President Ricardo Marques told Fast Company&amp;rsquo;s design vertical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generic Internet Article</title>
      <link>/2015/10/23/generic-products-private-labels/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 07:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/10/23/generic-products-private-labels/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In 1986, about a decade removed from his icon-setting days as lead singer of the Sex Pistols, British punk architect John Lydon released an album with his follow-up band, Public Image, Ltd., that had an extremely high-concept name. In fact, it didn&amp;rsquo;t technically have a name at all. If you bought the record on vinyl, it was called Album; if you bought it on CD, it was called Compact Disc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Invention Of News</title>
      <link>/2015/05/22/press-releases-invention-of-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2015 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/22/press-releases-invention-of-news/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Press releases are like chum for the enterprising marketer. For decades, these blurbs have been designed to draw in journalists looking for the next story, _something_ to fill the page or make hay for their audiences. Sometimes, they&amp;rsquo;re successful—such as Nintendo of America&amp;rsquo;s cheeky press release, released Wednesday, that pointed out their VP of sales has the last name Bowser. But a lot of the time, they&amp;rsquo;re full of irrelevant crap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forget Rand Paul, Let&#39;s Talk Paul Rand</title>
      <link>/2015/04/15/rand-paul-paul-rand-logo-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2015 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/04/15/rand-paul-paul-rand-logo-design/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: A horrible thing has happened to search results in recent months. If you do a Google search for Paul Rand, nearly half the results on the first page—and all of the Google News results—are about Rand Paul, a man who has little to do with graceful, iconic logo design. In fact, if you actually knew something about logo design, you might be disappointed by Rand&amp;rsquo;s campaign logo. (It&amp;rsquo;s better than Hillary&amp;rsquo;s, we&amp;rsquo;ll give him that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t mess with the Michelin Man</title>
      <link>/2015/04/10/michelin-guide-unusual-side-businesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/04/10/michelin-guide-unusual-side-businesses/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The problem with giving anyone on the street the right to review a restaurant is that he or she can easily be influenced by the wider political or social climate in setting their review score. When it comes to Yelp, the way the wind blows has a ton of influence on the final rating, something Indiana&amp;rsquo;s Memories Pizza learned the hard way when they took a stance in favor of the state&amp;rsquo;s controversial religious freedom law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brand bastardizations</title>
      <link>/2015/01/28/brand-bastardizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/28/brand-bastardizations/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Last week, the internet collectively threw McDonald&amp;rsquo;s a nostalgic bone. On January 20th, a reporter for Canada.com reminded the Northern Hemisphere of the obscure phenomenon that was the McPizza, a food item that most people probably forgot existed—especially if those people were American. (It was largely a Canadian phenomenon.) But, as it turns out, two franchise locations in Ohio and West Virginia still sell the pies. It’s a pretty good lesson in the age of organic food: process nourishment the right way, and everyone will still salivate.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>