<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Northwest Airlines on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/northwest-airlines/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Northwest Airlines on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 07:18:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/northwest-airlines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximum Cargo</title>
      <link>/2017/09/27/combi-planes-cargo-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 07:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/27/combi-planes-cargo-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Earlier this year, when the CEO of United Airlines was put in front of a Senate panel and asked to defend his company’s notably shoddy treatment of a passenger, Sen. Bill Nelson (D-FL) described his interactions with air passengers as such: “[They] feel like they’re being treated as self-loading cargo rather than as valued consumers.&amp;rdquo; That’s an interesting comparison point. If an airline isn’t shipping passengers from one side of the country or world to another, it’s shipping cargo that may be inanimate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You Not Entertained?</title>
      <link>/2017/02/24/in-flight-entertainment-system-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/02/24/in-flight-entertainment-system-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: There was a time when in-flight entertainment was better than anything you could actually bring onto a plane. That time has long passed, and some airlines are looking to get rid of seat-back screens, in favor of letting you use whatever screen you have with you—while making the WiFi better so you’d actually want to do that. Odds are that not many people are going to miss those screens.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>