<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pop Culture on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/pop-culture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pop Culture on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/pop-culture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of Creative Destruction</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/a-tale-of-creative-destruction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/a-tale-of-creative-destruction/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: The early Counting Crows hit &amp;ldquo;Mr. Jones&amp;rdquo; was a lie. Take that back—the incident was real, and Adam Duritz did hang out with a guy with the last name Jones, but the song&amp;rsquo;s whole plotline about how they were gonna be happier when they were famous didn&amp;rsquo;t come to pass. If you go to a Counting Crows show these days, in fact, the lyric is now &amp;ldquo;we all wanna be big, big stars, yeah, but then we get second thoughts about that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas In Clay</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/claymation-christmas-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/claymation-christmas-celebration/</guid>
      <description>[big]The strange thing about holiday classics, whether TV or film, is the way that they get drilled into the canon of nostalgia, a mush of themed entertainment along the lines of A Charlie Brown Christmas or A Christmas Story. These pieces of entertainment get repeated in part because we build memories around them. I wrote a piece about this phenomenon a couple of years ago.[/big]
But what happens if you create a piece of art that seems destined for the Christmas nostalgia ringer, and … for whatever reason, it just doesn’t happen?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Livin&#39; on the Edge</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/art-decency-shocking-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/art-decency-shocking-content/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: That sound you hear is Tipper Gore&amp;rsquo;s eyes bulging out. On June 1, a new video game called Hatred aims for the absolute edge of decency and taste, with a plot line that essentially involves killing innocent people en masse for no good reason other than to push forth the destruction of society. &amp;ldquo;We say ‘yes, it is a game about killing people’ and the only reason of the antagonist doing that sick stuff is his deep-rooted hatred,&amp;ldquo; its makers state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Big Data Jukebox</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/allmusic-database-historic-importance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/allmusic-database-historic-importance/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Discovering new kinds of music is easier than ever, something we can credit Napster for—along with its later legal followers, particularly Spotify, Pandora, and Apple Music. (Oh, and eMusic. That site was great back in the day.) But having all this music at our fingertips was only part of the equation—we needed to be armed with information. I think I realized that point during the early 2000s, when I found myself in the music section of a Barnes &amp;amp; Noble store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lazies</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/the-razzies-lazy-nominations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/the-razzies-lazy-nominations/</guid>
      <description>[big]The Golden Raspberry Awards are one of our greatest homespun counterculture traditions, one that set the stage for appreciation of bad film on a mainstream scale. While it didn’t change the world, it’s certainly an important institution.[/big]
But the award ceremony, which has always been designed as a way to piggyback on the attention of the Academy Awards, may be at a point where it its relevance is hitting rock-bottom. It’s always gone for the low-hanging fruit—the raspberries, really—but this year felt particularly, well lazy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Millennium Blues</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/y2k-pop-culture-oddities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/y2k-pop-culture-oddities/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey all, Ernie here with another piece from contributor David J. Buck—who’s taking a break from covering outsider music to bring you a tale of twisted culture at the turn of the century … and the dawn of the new millennium.
[big]Today in Tedium: Remember the terrifying, tumultuous, insert-scary-adjective-here year leading up to the new millennium? Did the uncertainty of the what the future held keep you up at night?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>