<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Horse Ownership on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/horse-ownership/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Horse Ownership on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 07:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/horse-ownership/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>They Steal Horses, Don’t They?</title>
      <link>/2018/05/09/horse-thief-detective-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/09/horse-thief-detective-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Often, theft is something very much defined by its era. In the past decade, smartphone thefts have grown rampant (occasionally leading to cute stories that cross borders and cultures), and it wasn’t too long before that when objects like sneakers and car stereos were the targets of robbery. Perhaps the target of the criminal activity changes—perhaps someone’s taking aim at your cryptocurrency at the moment—but the basic concept (what’s yours is now mine) doesn’t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stable Rent</title>
      <link>/2017/09/20/horse-ownership-nyc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 05:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/20/horse-ownership-nyc/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Hey guys, Ernie here with the latest piece from Andrew Egan, who previously told us about going to the lobby and grabbing ourselves a treat. This time, he&amp;rsquo;s makin&amp;rsquo; hay.
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: People have powerful connections to their pets. They brighten our day and wrack us with worry when they get sick. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s dogs, cats, parrots, or snakes, people will go to extreme lengths to accommodate their pets.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>