<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Magazines on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/magazines/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Magazines on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 07:10:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/magazines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re Making A Zine</title>
      <link>/2018/09/19/tedium-zine-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/09/19/tedium-zine-announcement/</guid>
      <description>A while back, my friend Simon Owens wrote this piece in which he compared email newsletters to zines, and used good old Tedium as an example of the form.  It makes sense to a degree—there’s a DIY ethos that comes with any self-publishing project, and with newsletters as with zines, the weirder, the better.
That thought stuck with me and kind of got into my head as a thought monster, and as I was thinking about ways to do something fresh with the Tedium concept, the zine struck me as the perfect kind of vessel to do something a little different, while still in the spirit of this thing I’m already writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consumer Conflict</title>
      <link>/2018/02/16/consumer-reports-history-origin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 09:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/16/consumer-reports-history-origin/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Last year, a consumer advocate showed up in the most unlikely place: On YouTube, the home of the no-questions-asked unboxing channel. Cody Crouch, aka iTwe4kz, reviewed a set of earbuds from a company called Kanoa. In a Nike hat and a Puma sleeveless shirt, Crouch (who was clearly frustrated) trashed the earbuds at length and questioned the behavior of the company that was banking on him to give a good review.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down With Snippet View</title>
      <link>/2017/06/27/google-books-snippet-view-archival/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 03:29:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/27/google-books-snippet-view-archival/</guid>
      <description>You may or may not have noticed this, but Tedium relies pretty heavily on archival content to exist. This newsletter and publication is not just about offering up weird facts: It&amp;rsquo;s often about introducing facts that have otherwise been forgotten about by the public at large.  Sometimes, this takes me in some interesting directions. An example I regularly cite is my piece on lemon juice squeeze bottles. It was the rare piece I had the chance to mostly write ahead of time, and while there were some incredibly useful starting points on the issue from the Beach Packaging Design, I find it important that, even if an existing resource like this offers a starting point, I spend time doing some digging of my own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Talk Toner</title>
      <link>/2016/05/06/photocopiers-xerox-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 07:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/05/06/photocopiers-xerox-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In an era where paper is becoming less important than ever, it feels a bit bizarre at this point to go back in time just 35 years ago, when paper was perhaps having its greatest moment of all time. We were just a few years from the desktop publishing revolution, which expanded the sheer amount of stuff one could put on a page. The &amp;lsquo;zine movement was perhaps at its peak during this time, proving an important way to democratize content for the average person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Magazine You Can&#39;t Bend</title>
      <link>/2016/02/24/cd-rom-magazines-launch-blender/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 09:11:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/02/24/cd-rom-magazines-launch-blender/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The promise of multimedia technology led creators of all stripes to do particularly crazy things in an effort to seem hip and with the times. The CD-ROM, much like the sound card, was seen as the lynchpin for much of this innovation—as it could hold a large amount of data, making room for audio, video, and interactive features that no piece of paper, glossy or otherwise, could pull off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A phone book for computers</title>
      <link>/2015/08/12/computer-shopper-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 08:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/12/computer-shopper-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The phone book isn&amp;rsquo;t really anyone&amp;rsquo;s idea of an innovative product, but it definitely had its place on the shelf of many a home before the internet took over. In the late throes of the age of the white pages, however, an unusually large magazine stole the hearts of many a techie, and in the process became something of a bible for people looking to replace their 286 with a 486—and maybe buy a laser printer in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>