<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Security on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Security on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 09:11:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Smaller Airports, Lower Stakes</title>
      <link>/2016/12/14/municipal-regional-airports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/12/14/municipal-regional-airports/</guid>
      <description>Editor’s note: Hey all, our excellent contributor Andrew Egan is back again; apparently not sick of working with me just yet. Enjoy!
Today in Tedium: This is my third Tedium piece in as many months. Though previous articles placed figures on World War II tourism in Germany or the danger of a relatively new aerial sport, the revelations offered in this piece were the most ardently cautioned against by sources. One, who will go unnamed, practically begged me not to write about this while others reacted to the news by slowly sucking air through clenched teeth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security In Stereo</title>
      <link>/2016/11/30/car-stereo-security-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/11/30/car-stereo-security-lessons/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Car stereos play an important role in making traveling in vehicles bearable. They give radio a reason for continued existence. They help to downplay the dull noises of wheels hitting asphalt, to blunt out engine trouble when it arises. But for decades, car stereos have had a problematic feature: They often were the most obvious thing that could be stolen out of a vehicle. Thieves could break a window, pull out the stereo with some basic tools, and sell the device on the black market for a pretty penny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back That Thang Up</title>
      <link>/2016/04/01/physical-backup-antiques-3d-printing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/04/01/physical-backup-antiques-3d-printing/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It&amp;rsquo;s deeply ironic that World Backup Day comes just a day before April Fools Day. One day encourages people to be stoic, serious, and overly cautious because people are inherently clumsy or devious; the other is designed to encourage people to throw caution in the wind because people are just Joshin&amp;rsquo; you. So in honor of both days (and in an effort to counter-program against all the stupid April Fool&amp;rsquo;s emails you&amp;rsquo;re probably going to be getting in the next 24 hours), let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the nature of destruction—physical things that are valuable because they can&amp;rsquo;t be backed up, getting damaged, dinged up, or destroyed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>