<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Encyclopaedia Britannica on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/encyclopaedia-britannica/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Encyclopaedia Britannica on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 05:07:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/encyclopaedia-britannica/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reopening the Book</title>
      <link>/2017/08/08/encyclopaedia-britannica-cdrom-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 05:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/08/encyclopaedia-britannica-cdrom-update/</guid>
      <description>If you look at nearly every retelling of Encyclopaedia Britannica’s move away from the physical book, the story goes something like this: Britannica ran head-first into the digital revolution and nearly lost its head in the process. And, like a few other retellings of this story, that was the story arc of a recent piece of mine on the matter.  So it wasn’t the world’s greatest feeling to see someone claiming that I had gotten this story arc completely wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Killed The Encyclopedia?</title>
      <link>/2017/07/14/who-killed-the-encyclopedia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 07:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/14/who-killed-the-encyclopedia/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The CD-ROM was sold to the public and the world as a way to bring interactive multimedia experiences into our homes. (Certainly, that&amp;rsquo;s how the magazine world tried to sell it.) But beyond that, it was a sheer amount of storage for a price that was insane to consider at the time. And that meant that some of the earliest products produced for the CD-ROM format were of the reference variety.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>