<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Copy Editing on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/copy-editing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Copy Editing on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 07:53:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/copy-editing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bare-Metal Writing</title>
      <link>/2016/08/19/bare-metal-writing-word-processor-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 07:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/08/19/bare-metal-writing-word-processor-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: I&amp;rsquo;m writing these opening lines in Markdown, using a Mac app called Focused, one of many attempts to rethink the word processor as a minimalist exercise. Every one of my articles starts out in this app (or at least in John Gruber&amp;rsquo;s neglected gift to the world), and yet, I always find myself looking for another option, periodically launching into a Google deep dive that rarely leads to a better solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They Should Stop</title>
      <link>/2016/08/05/singular-they-grammar-copy-editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 07:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/08/05/singular-they-grammar-copy-editing/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Of all the turf wars that have complicated the landscape of grammar over the past few hundred years, the most complicated and frustrating may be that of the singular &amp;ldquo;they.&amp;rdquo; It may be the most controversial word use in the English language—because it highlights a hole in the language where a better-fitting word should go. It creates a conflict between writers and editors who want things to follow the natural symmetry of Latin, and people who find they the only logical option for referring to a single person without a gender attached.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>