<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shopping on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/shopping/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shopping on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 19:30:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/shopping/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Otis Nixon, the CD-i, and Me</title>
      <link>/2018/10/09/otis-nixon-the-cd-i-and-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 19:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/09/otis-nixon-the-cd-i-and-me/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Once I heard this story from my pal D. Frank Smith about America&amp;rsquo;s Team, the Atlanta Braves, and the worst console of a generation, I knew I had to share it with you guys. Enjoy!
&amp;nbsp;
“Is that Otis Nixon?” I asked my dad as we walked through an Atlanta mall in 1992.  It took a moment to adjust my eyes to reality, because Nixon was wearing a suit, not his traditional Atlanta Braves uniform, likely because he was doing an endorsement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching Labels</title>
      <link>/2017/11/14/retail-theft-ticket-switching/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/14/retail-theft-ticket-switching/</guid>
      <description>Recently I had two pretty good six-packs of beer for $3.99 each. I had scored a deal because I wasn’t picky—the beers were rebranded by a grocery store to celebrate a special event that happened months prior, but the tell was on the cap—these beers, despite the labels, had been brewed by a well-known local craft brewer, and were the same beers that were in the “beer cave” for seven dollars more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Running Out of Widgets</title>
      <link>/2017/09/13/barnes-noble-third-place-widgets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 05:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/13/barnes-noble-third-place-widgets/</guid>
      <description>Editor’s note: Apple’s revelation on Tuesday that it was rethinking its approach to stores into something akin to a “town square” got me thinking about an old piece I wrote a while back—one that I, ironically, was just interviewed about for Ozy. In lieu of a fresh one, here’s a lightly refreshed 2015 piece that still feels pretty relevant.
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: When physical objects can be turned into a series of bits and bytes and streamed over the airwaves, the result is that stores start running out of things to sell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Tech Hit Retail</title>
      <link>/2017/07/21/point-of-sale-retail-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 07:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/21/point-of-sale-retail-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: If it feels like the the “robots are trying to steal our jobs” meme is a new development, I have some news for you: It’s really not. For decades, automation has been implied to be the cause of—and solution to—all life’s problems. Nowhere is this more the case than in the halls of retail, where automation helped redefine our interaction with shopping in important ways. And those innovations are still happening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gifts For People You Don’t Like</title>
      <link>/2016/12/21/tedium-gift-guide-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/12/21/tedium-gift-guide-2016/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: You’ve already checked off the people you know and love. Maybe even the people you know and tolerate. But what about gifts for folks you have a distaste for? That’s where our end-of-season gift guide comes into play. It’s full of obscure stuff and absolute dreck that you may or may not care for. But it’s perfect for breaking off weak friendships, telling a long-lost relative that they probably shouldn’t have returned, or for lowering someone’s overall standard for living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;d Buy That for a Dollar</title>
      <link>/2016/01/20/dollar-stores-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 08:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/01/20/dollar-stores-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The dollar store is one of capitalism&amp;rsquo;s greatest gifts to itself, if you think about it. Here&amp;rsquo;s a business model that has, quite brilliantly, taken advantage of the ebbs and flows of supply and demand. It turns products that don&amp;rsquo;t cost a lot to produce into things that actually make money hand over fist, despite the seemingly tight margins. Like companies that turn the liquidation of products into a viable business model and the makers of generic products, dollar stores have their place in the pantheon of retail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stocking Stinkers: A Tedium Gift Guide</title>
      <link>/2015/12/21/stocking-stinkers-tedium-gift-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/21/stocking-stinkers-tedium-gift-guide/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Tedium is publishing on an different schedule this week—Monday and Wednesday mornings rather than Tuesday and Thursday evenings—so as to get in your inbox before the holiday rush of out-of-office replies and connecting flights.
Today in Tedium: If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this and still in need of gift ideas for your loved ones, it&amp;rsquo;s already too late. (Did you know that Christmas is on Friday?!) You will find nothing good in your inbox or elsewhere that will save you at this point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything Must Go</title>
      <link>/2015/11/25/liquidation-sales-everything-must-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 09:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/11/25/liquidation-sales-everything-must-go/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a great deal on athletic goods and live in a big city on the East Coast, your best option may perhaps be City Sports. The athletic chain, which has been around for more than 30 years, announced earlier this month that it was closing its doors, ensuring this Black Friday is a little bit more of a Bleak Friday for fans of italicized Helvetica type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generic Internet Article</title>
      <link>/2015/10/23/generic-products-private-labels/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 07:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/10/23/generic-products-private-labels/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In 1986, about a decade removed from his icon-setting days as lead singer of the Sex Pistols, British punk architect John Lydon released an album with his follow-up band, Public Image, Ltd., that had an extremely high-concept name. In fact, it didn&amp;rsquo;t technically have a name at all. If you bought the record on vinyl, it was called Album; if you bought it on CD, it was called Compact Disc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>