<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Federal Communications Commission on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/federal-communications-commission/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Federal Communications Commission on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 09:21:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/federal-communications-commission/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Next Annoying National Upgrade</title>
      <link>/2017/12/06/atsc-3-0-digital-television-standard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 09:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/06/atsc-3-0-digital-television-standard/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: With all the recent chatter about Ajit Pai’s aggressive attempt to roll back net neutrality standards, it’s easy for other parts of the Federal Communications Commission’s winding docket to get lost. But there are things that the FCC is doing beyond ruining your internet that are worth discussing. One of those things is the recent passage of a measure to allow the voluntary rollout of ATSC 3.0, a television transmission standard that could rejigger the way we watch the boob tube.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Invisible Puzzle</title>
      <link>/2017/05/12/wireless-spectrum-allocation-challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 07:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/12/wireless-spectrum-allocation-challenges/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Barring our constant debates on net neutrality, one of the places where the Federal Communications Commission has the largest footprint is with our wireless spectrum. It’s a spectrum that has to serve many minders, and there are constant complaints about the spectrum being crowded. But those complaints, despite feeling modern and up-to-date, are far from new—we’ve been dealing with them pretty much ever since there was spectrum regulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s All In The Cards</title>
      <link>/2017/01/27/pcmcia-pc-card-laptop-expansion-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/27/pcmcia-pc-card-laptop-expansion-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The problem with laptops has, at least in recent years, been one of expandability. Once you buy a machine, you’re generally stuck with it, unless you’re willing to take it apart with repairs that have more in common with surgery than mechanics. Part of this has to do with the complexity of our modern machines, but a bigger part is the fact that, simply, upgradability has become less of a concern for manufacturers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waaaaay Left of the Dial</title>
      <link>/2016/07/01/frankenfm-radio-fcc-analog-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/07/01/frankenfm-radio-fcc-analog-tv/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: TV on the Radio isn&amp;rsquo;t just the name of a really freaking good band. Instead, it&amp;rsquo;s a quirk of the design of analog television. But a funny thing happened on the way to obscurity: As analog TV gave way to digital, a handful of risk-taking broadcasters, sensing an opportunity, have started to run those analog TV stations as FM radio stations—big FCC plans be damned. The shift is surprisingly contentious in the world of broadcast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Annoying National Upgrade</title>
      <link>/2016/04/27/digital-television-upgrade-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 07:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/04/27/digital-television-upgrade-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The move of the television airwaves from analog to digital in 2009 was perhaps the most unusual case of planned obsolescence in the modern age. Here was a decision, mandated by the Telecommunications Act of 1996 and forced upon hundreds of millions of people at once, that threw lots of people out of their routine. Many folks weren&amp;rsquo;t ready, or maybe they didn&amp;rsquo;t care enough about their TV signal quality to upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fake Metal Trees</title>
      <link>/2015/08/05/cell-towers-nimby-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 07:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/05/cell-towers-nimby-trees/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Here&amp;rsquo;s a tough problem. People love their cell phones, but the they hate the towers necessary to make those phones function. In fact, they really piss many people off, leading to situations where unnecessary fear-mongering wins the day, or leading people to worry that the towers will become eyesores that destroy their property values—or worse. So how do we get around the issue of these useful-but-ugly devices, anyway?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ted Turner&#39;s Satellite Of Love</title>
      <link>/2015/05/08/ted-turner-tbs-superstation-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/08/ted-turner-tbs-superstation-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: For a brief moment in time, independent local television stations held an impressive level of power over the country as a whole. They could share regional messages with national audiences, advertise to millions more people than they ever could on their crusty UHF signals, and punch far above their potential. The era of the superstation is past, but it undeniably had a massive effect on cable television. Don&amp;rsquo;t change the dial, because we&amp;rsquo;re talking about cable TV&amp;rsquo;s turning point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evolution, Televised</title>
      <link>/2015/02/11/grown-folks-dancing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/11/grown-folks-dancing/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It may have been the greatest text message my wife had ever sent me. While I was in the middle of a deep sleep, she sent me a message informing me of the existence of a television show that raised the bar for quality late-night television on Saturday evenings. When I woke up and finally saw it, I knew that my life would never be the same, thanks to the fact that I know know that Grown Folks Dancing is a thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LOUD NOISES</title>
      <link>/2015/01/23/loudest-noises-ever-nuclear-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/23/loudest-noises-ever-nuclear-attack/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: This week, the Federal Communications Commission dropped the hammer on cable-TV giants ESPN and Viacom, fining them a combined $1.4 million for running an ad for the movie Olympus Has Fallen. The reason? The ad featured tones from the Emergency Alert System (EAS), and the FCC was not cool with allowing an advertiser to use the tones. They weren&amp;rsquo;t the only ones to face the fine—NBCUniversal got nailed by a $530,000 fine in 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>