<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wesley Willis on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/wesley-willis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wesley Willis on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 08:45:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/wesley-willis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock and Roll Remodel</title>
      <link>/2017/12/21/rock-and-roll-mcdonalds-remodel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 08:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/21/rock-and-roll-mcdonalds-remodel/</guid>
      <description>In the early 1990s, Chicago icon and outsider musician Wesley Willis wrote a tribute to one of his favorite dining establishments—McDonald&amp;rsquo;s. Dubbed &amp;ldquo;Rock and Roll McDonald&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; and set to a fun, keyboard-driven melody, the song extolls the virtues of the fast food haven. Willis once spent time both in and out of the McDonald&amp;rsquo;s and surrounding area, making and selling his beautiful drawings most days.  (via the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s Yelp page)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wesley Willis WinAmp Connection</title>
      <link>/2017/11/21/wesley-willis-winamp-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/21/wesley-willis-winamp-history/</guid>
      <description>Wesley Willis was a prolific musician and wonderful artist. Beloved by most folks he ran across, it’s no surprise his legacy would live on in an unlikely place—your computer.  Some may recognize Mike the llama as the mascot of legendary music software WinAmp. But did you know, there is a somewhat tenuous, but quite obvious connection to Wesley built into the software?
Windows users in the mid-to-late 90s are probably used WinAmp or know of it in some capacity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock On Chicago</title>
      <link>/2017/11/17/wesley-willis-remembrance-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 09:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/17/wesley-willis-remembrance-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with a fresh Tedium piece comes from outsider artist aficionado and newsletter contributor David J. Buck, who hit us up last time with a piece on Wild Man Fischer. By popular demand, here’s a piece on Wesley Willis!
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: People loved Wesley Willis. Despite a rough upbringing, struggles with mental illness, extreme poverty and an abusive family, he was friendly and lovable. Wesley became a Chicago icon, building a network of friends, fans, and followers along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>