<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Philosophy on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/philosophy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Philosophy on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 05:38:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/philosophy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Charmeleon Chaos Theory</title>
      <link>/2016/07/22/pokemon-go-spontaneity-charmeleon-chaos-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 05:38:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/07/22/pokemon-go-spontaneity-charmeleon-chaos-theory/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: There&amp;rsquo;s something wild about watching people play this game that everyone won&amp;rsquo;t shut up about. And I think it has a lot to do with how it shifts social order in an unexpected way. Here&amp;rsquo;s why: If you see a group of people standing in an otherwise empty park, all from different walks of life, brought together by this game, it looks spontaneous from a distance—totally unplanned, as if they all stumbled there independently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Literally Navel-Gazing</title>
      <link>/2015/05/13/were-literally-navel-gazing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/13/were-literally-navel-gazing/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It&amp;rsquo;s the one thing that separates humans from androids. Like the appendix, it&amp;rsquo;s functionally useless—minus the period before you&amp;rsquo;re actually born, when it&amp;rsquo;s pretty much the most important part of your body. Unlike the appendix, it&amp;rsquo;s visible and easy to spot. It, of course, is the belly button—one of the most-common but least-discussed parts of the human body. (Well, unless you&amp;rsquo;re Taylor Swift.) Innie or outie? The answer to that question could very well define your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Muppet Email</title>
      <link>/2015/01/09/great-muppet-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2015 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/09/great-muppet-email/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The Muppets sure are awesome, aren’t they? We agree. Clearly, Jim Henson—a man who originally thought of himself more as filmmaker than puppeteer—was on an awesome kick when he came up with the idea to convince ad execs that anthropomorphic foam and rubber could be used to sell coffee. With something as long-lasting and popular as the Muppets, there&amp;rsquo;s a good chance it&amp;rsquo;ll take you in some weird directions—like Scientology, Hebrew, and fans willing to take the Muppet legacy into their own hands.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>