<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Journalism on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/journalism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Journalism on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/journalism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Finish Line In Sight</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/tedium-trends-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/tedium-trends-2017/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Can you believe we’ve been publishing this newsletter for two full years now? (Our anniversary hits on New Year’s Day, just like with my last project, ShortFormBlog.) There’s a good chance that most of you might not be aware of this fact. See, it was only back in January of 2016 that we topped a thousand subscribers, a fact that we revealed in an issue about dollar stores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bare-Metal Writing</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/bare-metal-writing-word-processor-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/bare-metal-writing-word-processor-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: I&amp;rsquo;m writing these opening lines in Markdown, using a Mac app called Focused, one of many attempts to rethink the word processor as a minimalist exercise. Every one of my articles starts out in this app (or at least in John Gruber&amp;rsquo;s neglected gift to the world), and yet, I always find myself looking for another option, periodically launching into a Google deep dive that rarely leads to a better solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News In Small Bytes</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/online-news-history-compuserve-videotex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/online-news-history-compuserve-videotex/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Publishing words on a computer is not a difficult task these days. We have so many options to write words and distribute them through a computerized interface that we take the whole process for granted. (You probably published something in the time it took you to read the previous two sentences.) But there was a time when publishing through a computer was painful, cumbersome, and expensive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shorthand For No</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/scotland-journalism-cerebral-palsy-controversy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/scotland-journalism-cerebral-palsy-controversy/</guid>
      <description>[big]In an era when literally every rule of traditional journalism has been blown to shreds (case in point: the fact I can run a site and newsletter like this), it’s depressing to see how far some sticklers are willing to go in maintaining rules that make zero sense in 2017.[/big]
Case in point: It was revealed this week that a Scottish college wouldn’t let a journalism student with cerebral palsy pass a course to gain a journalism qualification … because he can’t write shorthand due to his out-of-his-control physical condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tear Down This Paywall</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/bloomberg-tear-down-this-paywall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/bloomberg-tear-down-this-paywall/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: I wrote this on Medium last night, but am also sharing here in hopes of giving this issue the attention it deserves.
[big]I write stuff that is driven on research. It’s an important part of what I do. That research takes me weird places—into patent filings, reading news stories that are decades old, diving into snippets of old books, hoping that something—anything—will get me closer to the end of the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Invention Of News</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/press-releases-invention-of-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/press-releases-invention-of-news/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Press releases are like chum for the enterprising marketer. For decades, these blurbs have been designed to draw in journalists looking for the next story, _something_ to fill the page or make hay for their audiences. Sometimes, they&amp;rsquo;re successful—such as Nintendo of America&amp;rsquo;s cheeky press release, released Wednesday, that pointed out their VP of sales has the last name Bowser. But a lot of the time, they&amp;rsquo;re full of irrelevant crap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There’s Always Next Year</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/tedium-trends-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/tedium-trends-2018/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: We’re near the start of the new year, and, as a result, I’m closing in on the third anniversary of launching this crazy newsletter. New Year’s Day is kind of an important day for me personally, as it’s the day that I’ve launched two of my projects, including this one. So I’d like to spend this time reflecting back a little bit … and looking forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They Stopped (Sorta)</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/singular-they-ap-stylebook-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/singular-they-ap-stylebook-update/</guid>
      <description>[big]Last summer, I wrote an impassioned plea in favor of embracing the singular “they,” which I called “the Rodney Dangerfield of grammar.”[/big]
Basically, this word use, which has no simple singular equivalent that doesn’t dive into awkward gender politics when the subject’s grammar hasn’t been revealed, has been written around for hundreds of years by newspapers and in other formalized grammar settings. The Associated Press, notably, had resisted changing its mind on this issue, even as the linguistic tide started to favor it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trimmed For Space</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/newspaper-newsprint-cuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/newspaper-newsprint-cuts/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
_Editor’s note: Tonight’s Tedium is an updated rerun of a classic issue about the stuff that newspapers get rid of when trying to slim down. Unspoken in this article: Usually, the final step of this process is people. And with the recent sagas of L.A. Weekly and (on the digital side of things) DNAinfo, now felt like a good time to revisit. (If you&amp;rsquo;ve read before, keep reading; there&amp;rsquo;s a new section on newsprint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Robots Can Write</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/robots-writing-algorithms-articoolo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/robots-writing-algorithms-articoolo/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: It seems like a constant refrain of the internet era–the robots are coming to steal our jobs, and they&amp;rsquo;re getting better by the day. So far, that has mostly meant that heavy industrial jobs have become increasingly automated and restaurants in San Francisco are basically making food without the added work of human hands. (And hey, if you think about it, vending machines are a very basic form of automation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>