<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Michelin Stars on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/michelin-stars/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Michelin Stars on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 05:24:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/michelin-stars/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>We Are All Made Of Stars</title>
      <link>/2017/09/21/michelin-chef-removal-request/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 05:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/21/michelin-chef-removal-request/</guid>
      <description>Honestly, it makes no sense why a company best known for manufacturing tires is such an important voice in the world of fine dining, but Michelin has embraced its gastronomic role with gusto for more than a century.  Now, it turns out that one of its most-decorated chefs isn’t feeling that gusto himself. Sébastien Bras, a French chef whose restaurant Le Suquet has been a three-star mainstay of the Michelin guide for close to two decades, made the first-ever request to be removed from the guide without a significant change to his model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t mess with the Michelin Man</title>
      <link>/2015/04/10/michelin-guide-unusual-side-businesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/04/10/michelin-guide-unusual-side-businesses/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The problem with giving anyone on the street the right to review a restaurant is that he or she can easily be influenced by the wider political or social climate in setting their review score. When it comes to Yelp, the way the wind blows has a ton of influence on the final rating, something Indiana&amp;rsquo;s Memories Pizza learned the hard way when they took a stance in favor of the state&amp;rsquo;s controversial religious freedom law.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>