<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Steak on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/steak/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Steak on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 07:51:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/steak/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Never A Dull Moment</title>
      <link>/2017/08/23/steak-knife-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 07:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/23/steak-knife-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Obviously, knives, with their sharp blades for cutting through things, have been around forever—they’re a key ingredient of any horror film, slasher flick, or murder mystery that’s ever been created. But here’s a question that I don’t think a lot of people have pondered (mainly because they aren’t expected to like I am): Why do steaks get their own dedicated knives, and why do we shove them into giant blocks of wood for storage?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Every Piece Count</title>
      <link>/2016/09/30/meat-science-flat-iron-steak-innovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/09/30/meat-science-flat-iron-steak-innovation/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: You may not like meat, but even if you do, you may not think of it in terms of innovation. It sounds like a concept incompatible with the idea of meat—we do so many things with cows, chicken, fish, and pigs that it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to consider these animals in terms of reinvention. We&amp;rsquo;ve already mashed these four types of animals into combinations more creative than Legos, taken their parts and turned them into products that don&amp;rsquo;t even fit into the same genre as dinner.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>