<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Movies on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/movies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Movies on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/movies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Between the Bars</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/movie-letterboxing-pan-scan-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/movie-letterboxing-pan-scan-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Taking an experience like going to the movies and converting it to your living room is a hugely controversial thing, despite the fact we&amp;rsquo;ve been doing it for decades. Rich guy and wannabe disruptor Sean Parker is learning this the hard way, thanks to his efforts to sell a product called Screening Room. The service would allow homes access to first-run movies through a set-top box for a price of $50 a pop—not cheap at all, but potentially cheaper than a night at the movies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Yourself A Treat</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/lets-all-go-lobby-movie-snipe-advertising/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/lets-all-go-lobby-movie-snipe-advertising/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Editor’s note: Hey all, Ernie here—just wanted to let you guys know I’m handing the reins over to Andrew Egan once again. (If you want some of my thoughts on things, I did a recent interview with LetterList.) Last time, he told us about a time-storing device; this time, he has a stalling tactic of sorts. Check it out!
[big]Today in Tedium: As we&amp;rsquo;ve noted before, long-running traditions in movies are slowly dying as media becomes digitized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep Your Composure</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/film-composition-subtle-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/film-composition-subtle-art/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey guys, Ernie here with a fresh piece from Andrew Egan, who last hit us with some chatter on sound design in film. This time, he talks about another aural element of the cinematic experience.
[big]Today in Tedium: There is no shortage of colloquialisms that advise you to chill out, take it easy, and don&amp;rsquo;t sweat the small stuff. But details matter. (Where else are you going to find the devil when you need him?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Comment</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/dvd-audio-commentary-decline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/dvd-audio-commentary-decline/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Back again for another round is Andrew Egan, who most recently brought us the story of Scatman John. Tonight, he tells us about his time digging in the menus on random DVDs. (By the way, a quick shout-out to Kenn Messman, who recently made a big donation to the site. Thanks!)
[big]Today in Tedium: As the formats hosting our favorite movies, music, and games change, some things will be lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shelf This Elf</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/elf-bowling-movie-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/elf-bowling-movie-review/</guid>
      <description>[big]**Last week’s article about the game Elf Bowling** really hit the sweet spot for a lot of folks. It’s a fun, maybe not groundbreaking game that is great to play for a few minutes—or based on your addiction level, a whole lot longer. (It should be remade for smartphones—the mechanics work really well for that medium.)[/big]
But by no means was the game, with its cheeky jokes, offbeat animation, and goofy concept, enough to carry a movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Before Netflix</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/first-streaming-service-itv-hong-kong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/first-streaming-service-itv-hong-kong/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Earlier this week, I got a little grumpy over at Product Hunt, due to an undercurrent of snark around the fact that Netflix still has a DVD service. The reason for this was that too many people were skeptical about whether such a service was still necessary. It absolutely, totally is, and I’ll give you one reason why: Netflix’s DVD service has roughly 93,000 options, while its streaming service (between shows and movies) has fewer than 8,000 options—ensuring that DVDs will have a reason to exist for quite a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lazarus Libraries</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/lost-and-found-film-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/lost-and-found-film-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey all, Ernie here with a piece from Andrew Egan, who is following his recent interest in film in a couple of new directions this time around. Check out what he found.
[big]Today in Tedium: Among the many pieces of dubious “evidence” cited by conspiracy theorists that say the moon landing was faked is the fact that the tapes of the original transmission were erased over. Surely, if America had actually landed on the moon those recordings would be an invaluable part of human history and not treated so carelessly as to be erased on accident years later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lazies</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/the-razzies-lazy-nominations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/the-razzies-lazy-nominations/</guid>
      <description>[big]The Golden Raspberry Awards are one of our greatest homespun counterculture traditions, one that set the stage for appreciation of bad film on a mainstream scale. While it didn’t change the world, it’s certainly an important institution.[/big]
But the award ceremony, which has always been designed as a way to piggyback on the attention of the Academy Awards, may be at a point where it its relevance is hitting rock-bottom. It’s always gone for the low-hanging fruit—the raspberries, really—but this year felt particularly, well lazy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Same Name Game</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/same-name-movie-review-locus-of-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/same-name-movie-review-locus-of-control/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey guys, Ernie here with a piece from Andrew Egan, who may have just invented a new kind of movie review with this piece. If you’re looking for a soundtrack for this issue, I recommend this one.
[big]Today in Tedium: The content explosion has had some strange side effects. Binge watching is altering our brains and decreasing production costs have nurtured YouTubers’ desire for mainstream success. But as Amazon, Netflix, and Hollywood in general prepare to spend billions on original content in the coming years, an even stranger phenomenon is happening in plain sight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sound and the Fury</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/indiana-jones-sound-design-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/indiana-jones-sound-design-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey all, Ernie here with a piece from Andrew Egan about a specific kind of movie magic—the kind you hear, whether during a dramatic fall or the crack of a whip. Enjoy!
[big]Today in Tedium: Returning to my sunny little Brooklyn apartment a few weeks ago, I heard a familiar sound coming from my living room. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t music or dialogue but the second I heard it, I knew exactly what one of my roommates was watching in our living room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tommy’s Back</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/best-friends-tommy-wiseau-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/best-friends-tommy-wiseau-review/</guid>
      <description>[big]Tommy Wiseau, the legendary auteur of The Room, may not be a great filmmaker in the traditional sense, but he has a pretty enthused fanbase—a base of which I admit being a part of. And that fanbase, which has stuck with Wiseau through unusual projects like his 2015 Hulu series The Neighbors, has gotten a lot of mileage out of a single film that has owned the midnight movie circuit for years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Copyright Goes Copywrong</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/public-domain-film-history-copyright/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/public-domain-film-history-copyright/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: When horror movie icon George A. Romero died earlier this year, it should have started a copyright expiration timeline for his most famous and influential work, the 1968 classic and Halloween icon Night of the Living Dead. But something really scary happened to the film before it became a hit: Due to a last-second title change and a distributor error, the former Night of the Flesh Eaters fell into the public domain upon its release.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>