<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Simpsons on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/the-simpsons/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Simpsons on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 07:20:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/the-simpsons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Ned</title>
      <link>/2017/04/18/okilly-dokilly-ned-flanders-metal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 07:20:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/04/18/okilly-dokilly-ned-flanders-metal/</guid>
      <description>If you haven’t been following the modern metal scene, you’ve apparently been missing out on a lot of bands pigging out on pop-culture references in the best way possible.  Last month, a trio of bands went on tour that make Tenacious D look like they’re not high-concept enough. The two co-headliners of the 2017 Mockstrosity Tour were weird enough: Metalachi, a mariachi-themed metal band, shared the stage with Mac Sabbath, a McDonald’s-themed Black Sabbath cover band.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A cromulent exercise</title>
      <link>/2015/02/27/a-cromulent-exercise/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2015 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/27/a-cromulent-exercise/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Language is constantly expanding in numerous ways—and in tends to make us uncomfortable to see a new bastardization of the language, even a good one. A recent study noted that the evolution of language has lots in common with the shifts in DNA throughout history, though with one major difference: As a society becomes more insular, the genetic makeup becomes more same-y, but the language becomes more interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genealogy for Fanbois</title>
      <link>/2015/01/14/ducktales-geneaology-fanbois/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 07:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/14/ducktales-geneaology-fanbois/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: When it comes to the internet, two particular topics are known for driving obsessiveness—genealogy and fandom. They require similar thought processes and skill sets—extreme knowledge of the subject, a willingness to dive deep into the subject matter, a lot of extra time on one&amp;rsquo;s hands—and, at times, they can work together. Most people don&amp;rsquo;t have time to do the heavy lifting to do a deep dive on this kind of fandom, so we&amp;rsquo;ve done the hard work for you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>