<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ibm Pc on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/ibm-pc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ibm Pc on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/ibm-pc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bare-Metal Writing</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/bare-metal-writing-word-processor-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/bare-metal-writing-word-processor-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: I&amp;rsquo;m writing these opening lines in Markdown, using a Mac app called Focused, one of many attempts to rethink the word processor as a minimalist exercise. Every one of my articles starts out in this app (or at least in John Gruber&amp;rsquo;s neglected gift to the world), and yet, I always find myself looking for another option, periodically launching into a Google deep dive that rarely leads to a better solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Command Line</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/dos-nostalgia-squirrel-monkey-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/dos-nostalgia-squirrel-monkey-interview/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey all, Ernie here with a fresh piece from David Buck, who has moved away from his NES for a while to tell you all about how awesome DOS is as a creative medium. Yeah, DOS.
[big]Today in Tedium: From the early 90s, up until 2005 or so, I did much of my computer gaming on an American Megatrends IBM PC, running MS-DOS and Windows 3.11. I even got online once using Netscape Communicator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life In Four Colors</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/igm-pc-cga-graphics-cards-legacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/igm-pc-cga-graphics-cards-legacy/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: In our 4K-televised world, in which things (usually) look good at 120 frames per second, it’s strange to think back to points in our history where the graphics weren’t nearly that good—where the visuals took something of a backseat to the graphics getting pumped out. But it wasn’t all that long ago when our graphics were crude, blocky, and very limited in resolution. And part of the reason for this can be pointed at IBM, which prioritized text over imagery on its early PCs, all in an effort to win over business users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Some Noise</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/creative-sound-blaster-sound-card-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/creative-sound-blaster-sound-card-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Before we embraced MP3s as the official noise of the internet (taking the place of screechy modems), it took a while before the synthesized notes of our musical past could be modulated through the inner-workings of a computer. Some of our earliest computers, for example, could only make very basic bleeps and bloops. But in 1989, everything changed when a Singaporean company called Creative Technology hit upon the perfect approach for synthesizing sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Some Noise</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/sound-blaster-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/sound-blaster-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey all, Ernie here with a classic (though lightly updated) Tedium piece about one of the defining pieces of ’90s computer technology: The Sound Blaster. Crank it up!
[big]Today in Tedium: Before we embraced MP3s as the official noise of the internet (taking the place of screechy modems), it took a while before the synthesized notes of our musical past could be modulated through the inner-workings of a computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Other Windows</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/geoworks-windows-3-1-competitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/geoworks-windows-3-1-competitor/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Back in the early &amp;lsquo;90s, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a sure thing that Microsoft Windows was going to take over the market, even though they had a clear lead over many of their competitors, thanks to MS-DOS. In fact, one of the iconic GUI-based experiences of the era, AOL, hedged its bets for a while, creating and maintaining a DOS version of its iconic pseudo-internet software using an GUI platform few were familiar with: GeoWorks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>