<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Drugs on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/drugs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Drugs on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 09:09:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/drugs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Brand Indigestion</title>
      <link>/2016/02/12/xifaxan-pharmaceutical-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 09:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/02/12/xifaxan-pharmaceutical-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Mascots can be great ways to promote a product, but sometimes they&amp;rsquo;re full of crap. The Xifaxan intestine, which I&amp;rsquo;ve been going on about for months now, fits into the latter category. Xifaxan, if you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar, is a medication for irritable bowel syndrome. Some marketing company somewhere got paid millions of dollars to create an animated character that runs around ready to lose its … y&amp;rsquo;know, every time it turns a corner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Drugs Don&#39;t Work</title>
      <link>/2016/01/27/alternative-medicine-interest/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2016 04:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/01/27/alternative-medicine-interest/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Does meditation make for a good replacement to, y&amp;rsquo;know, going to a doctor? That doctor may tell you that skipping the normal treatment isn&amp;rsquo;t a good idea, but those without health insurance have increasingly embraced alternative medicine as a replacement for the more expensive stuff. A new Centers for Disease Control and Prevention study found that people without insurance between 2002 and 2012 were more likely to give alternative medicine offerings a spin, while those with insurance were just as indifferent to alternative medicine as always.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>