<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blurb on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/blurb/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blurb on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/blurb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>90 Seconds of Failure</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/shooby-taylor-showtime-at-the-apollo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/shooby-taylor-showtime-at-the-apollo/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend—inspired by the forthcoming release of The Disaster Artist, a film about my favorite movie—I finally saw Ed Wood. It took me way too long.
Ed Wood is a great film about a terrible filmmaker, as well as a great story about the creative muse, and how it sometimes doesn’t hit the cues of the popular taste. Wood’s masterwork, Plan 9 From Outer Space, doesn’t need any more words written about it—but the origin story of its reputation as the “worst movie” is nearly as fascinating as its creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Beachside Mystery</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/rhode-island-weird-beach-mystery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/rhode-island-weird-beach-mystery/</guid>
      <description>[big]Sorry, guys: The unofficial end of summer gets us no closer to the solution of the summer’s great mystery. Yes, that’s right, there was a big mystery hiding in the sand this summer—and it would’ve been a kickass discovery using any average metal detector.[/big]
Here’s the deal: Beachgoers in Westerly, Rhode Island have been confused as heck about a large metal object that was jutting out of the ground on the city’s beach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Beautiful Neighborhood</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/ernest-hood-neighborhoods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/ernest-hood-neighborhoods/</guid>
      <description>[big]Back in 2004, the Arcade Fire released one of the greatest musical documents of our still-young 21st century, an album titled Funeral that was built around a series of four songs, each titled “Neighborhood.” Those songs, with their high tension and genuine pain, evoked something both local and emotional. They became huge. They moved far beyond neighborhoods, into the stratosphere.[/big]
Nearly three decades earlier, Portland, Oregon jazz musician Ernest Hood wasn’t aiming for the same kind of emotions with his album Neighborhoods, but he did hit on something very local and emotional in his own right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bigger, Better Tape</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/sony-elcaset-history-tape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/sony-elcaset-history-tape/</guid>
      <description>[big]Start the tape: Roughly a year and a half ago, I made a pitch that we were due for a magnetic-tape comeback similar to the one we’ve seen for vinyl. (I titled it after a Frank Turner album, because Frank Turner is cool.) Now, we haven’t seen that magnetic-tape comeback just yet, but it might help if I did my part by highlighting tape-format obscurities.[/big]
One of those obscurities worth a mention is the Elcaset, just one of Sony’s many attempts to create a new standard of some kind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Business Card With Impact</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/cd-rom-business-card-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/cd-rom-business-card-history/</guid>
      <description>[big]Back in 2010, Inc. contributor Josh Spiro made this point about the importance of business cards: “A snazzy card is no good if you hand it out left and right without an exchange of pleasantries and ideas, but a poor quality card can undermine even the best rapport or the most persuasive conversation.”[/big]
With this in mind, it only makes sense that someone had the idea of creating a business card that doubled as a CD-ROM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Love Letter to Gingko</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/gingko-experimental-word-processor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/gingko-experimental-word-processor/</guid>
      <description>[big]When it comes to writing, I think that the biggest problem for a lot of people is properly organizing their ideas. There&amp;rsquo;s just so much to put into a document, and without well-considered organization, it can get a little long, jumbled, and overly ranty. (Overly ranty is bad.)[/big]
But that doesn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily mean that there isn&amp;rsquo;t room to rethink the approach. Perhaps you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be writing in a totally linear format—perhaps you need to think in terms of a flow chart, one that is flexible to the whims of your prose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Coat of Paint</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/anthony-dortch-artist-stroke-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/anthony-dortch-artist-stroke-recovery/</guid>
      <description>[big]Last year, Anthony Dortch suffered a major personal setback—surviving a stroke at a young age.[/big]
This health struggle threatened to stop Dortch, a Washington, D.C.-based artist, from following his muse, a muse that he’s followed for years with a long-term creative project that’s taken on many layers. Quite literally, in fact.
See, Dortch’s art literally involves painting people to and making them, effectively, into comic book characters—each in different colors to represent different walks of life, with elements of his storytelling highlighting issues of race, gender and sexuality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Nod To Readability</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/a-nod-to-readability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/a-nod-to-readability/</guid>
      <description>[big]I have to admit, I kind of loved the idea of launching this site with a slab-serif font. Slab-serifs, with their hard edges and consistent widths, have a lot of character, and I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved the feel that they&amp;rsquo;ve given my work over the years. I loved using them when I still designed newspapers, and I love using them now. A while back, I found a good one, and it has treated me well—both at Tedium, and the last iteration of my old site ShortFormBlog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Screwy Straw Stat</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/plastic-straw-statistic-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/plastic-straw-statistic-questions/</guid>
      <description>[big]As you may or may not know, I often speak up against the way that sometimes, a “fact” will show up on Wikipedia, unchallenged, for years, only to stumble into books large and small over the next number of years, something I call “The Windex Problem.”[/big]
But what if the data point is something being shared not by an encyclopedia, but by a number of nonprofits looking to make the case for a bigger mission?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of Two Samoas</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/american-samoa-spanish-flu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/american-samoa-spanish-flu/</guid>
      <description>[big]For understandable reasons, Puerto Rico is perhaps the main U.S. territory on the minds of the American public at the moment. The island of 3.5 million has been utterly devastated by Hurricane Maria and it will likely be years before it’s back to a semblance of its normal self—a situation not being helped, to say the least, by the current president.[/big]
Tedium, of course, isn’t a news blog, but sometimes it helps to take news and highlight it through the frame of history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Warped Mindset</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/nintendo-times-warp-zone-nes-coverage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/nintendo-times-warp-zone-nes-coverage/</guid>
      <description>[big]What if we reported on the past like it was happening in the present day—not reflecting on it nostalgically like I do at Tedium, but literally trying to cover the past as if you had no knowledge of the future?[/big]
It sounds like an odd thought exercise, but in reality, it’s a whole lot of fun, based on the website Nintendo Times. Since 2015, the writer and blogger Craig Majaski, who cut his teeth at the long-running gaming site Gaming Age, has been editing and putting together a site in which 30-year-old discussions and interviews about the early days of the Nintendo Entertainment System are published as if they’re happening in real time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Weaponized Slogan</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/weird-scam-calls-verizon-slogan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/weird-scam-calls-verizon-slogan/</guid>
      <description>[big]A not-so-innocent question: For years, Verizon sold millions of people on the promise of solid cellular phone signals with a simple question. “Can you hear me now?” asked Paul Marcarelli, the living pitchman who spent years in anonymity because of his ties to the brand. (He’s much happier with Sprint.)[/big]
But that question, so innocent-seeming, has become weaponized in the hands of a bunch of scamming robocallers. The Better Business Bureau reported this week that scammers were calling unsuspecting people, asking people on the other end of the line if they can hear them, then hanging up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Addicted To Spectrum</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/addicted-to-spectrum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/addicted-to-spectrum/</guid>
      <description>[big]You know a tool that’s proved incredibly useful to the theater world? The wireless microphone. It sounds small, but it’s actually a really huge improvement over what they previously had.[/big]
These devices, which have come into their own over the past two decades, have helped to improve actors’ freedom of movement allowing their performances to be more natural while still remaining fairly easy to hear. But they haven’t always been perfect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Guano</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/minor-outlying-islands-guano-islands-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/minor-outlying-islands-guano-islands-act/</guid>
      <description>[big]No surprise to anyone, but large countries have this way of splaying out all over the world, with lots of their territories in unexpected areas.[/big]
The United States is no exception, with its array of minor outlying islands, mostly in the Pacific Ocean. But there&amp;rsquo;s something weird about how many of these islands, mostly uninhabited today or used as minor scientific or military outposts, came under ownership of the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amiga Appreciation</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/viva-amiga-documentary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/viva-amiga-documentary/</guid>
      <description>[big]Love your Amiga: If you’re a longish-time reader of Tedium, you’ll know that we have a lot of appreciation for the Amiga, the Commodore-produced platform, loved by Andy Warhol, that basically set the stage for the visually-graceful computing world we have now.[/big]
Which is why the new documentary about the computing platform, Zach Weddington’s Viva Amiga: The Story of a Beautiful Machine is very much on our list of things to watch right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Extra Serving</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/nesticle-history-extras-part-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/nesticle-history-extras-part-one/</guid>
      <description>[big]What a day! My article on Vice&amp;rsquo;s Motherboard this week about the history of NESticle—the Nintendo Entertainment System emulator whose early success paved the way for people to play vintage games on their computers whenever they want—took a while to get past the finish line, and came only after I gave the piece a haircut.[/big]
To augment the story, I’m gonna spend the next couple of Daily Tedium pieces highlighting things I hoped to get into the original piece but were trimmed out because the piece was getting a bit lengthy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Impurrfect History</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/cats-dot-com-domain-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/cats-dot-com-domain-history/</guid>
      <description>[big]Let’s face facts: Having an awesome domain name is no guarantee for success. This was proven just a couple of weeks ago in my piece about the failure of Pets.com. But it still highlights a whole lot of potential.[/big]
Which is why the recent domain sale of Cats.com—literally, an entire domain name for the internet’s favorite animal—is one that we should closely watch. The domain is currently sitting at $125,000 on the auction site Flippa, and will sell to the highest bidder in the next five days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Around the World</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/le-globe-radiooooo-online-radio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/le-globe-radiooooo-online-radio/</guid>
      <description>[big]When you find an outlet that creates a sense of adventure around something as pedestrian and overexposed as online music, you know it’s worth a bookmark.[/big]
The French website Radiooooo, an online time machine that combines a Mercator projection of the globe with a radio, feels like the modern version of the shortwave radio, in some ways—except with the added dimension of time.
In a New Yorker piece last year, founder Benjamin Moreau recalled that he had the idea based on an experience of listening to modern music in his 1966 Renault Caravelle, and finding the result fully unappealing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australian Rules Nintendo</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/nintendo-beam-software-australia-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/nintendo-beam-software-australia-history/</guid>
      <description>[big]Recently I found myself hanging out in a retro video game store, looking at the cheapo bin at the various titles for the NES and other systems. If you’ve done something similar in the recent past, you’ll know that the cheapo bin will inevitably be filled with lots of sports games. It doesn’t matter if the sports games are well-regarded or even iconic—for whatever reason gamers just don’t want to buy them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Behind By A Century</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/the-tragically-hip-appreciation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/the-tragically-hip-appreciation/</guid>
      <description>[big]My wife, for years, has had this tendency of deciding to watch some shows, usually dramas, only after their run has completed, which I’m sure that TV studios friggin’ love. Sometimes, though, there’s so much out there that it’s just functionally easier to tackle a body of work like Weeds in full, over the span of a week, rather than as a number of disparate, easily-forgotten pieces.[/big]
Music, which has always been more of my forte, often doesn’t have this problem—a song is usually self-contained in a theme, and an album usually stands on its own as a complete thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogging Before it Was Cool</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/rip-jerry-pournelle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/rip-jerry-pournelle/</guid>
      <description>[big]Of all the people it’s sucked to lose in 2017, Jerry Pournelle’s loss might quietly be the saddest.[/big]
Case in point: His final blog post, published Thursday. He noted the cold he was dealing with after attending a convention, wrote about immigration (Pournelle, an irreverent if hard-line conservative voice even at the height of his popularity, suggested that we let the “Dreamers” in after they serve seven years overseas in the military), and then overshared just a little bit before ending the post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COBOLed Together</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/cobol-programmers-cobol-cowboys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/cobol-programmers-cobol-cowboys/</guid>
      <description>[big]If you’re a regular reader of Y Combinator’s excellent mini-Reddit aggregator Hacker News (as I am), you start to see some trends arise. Programming languages and frameworks become incredibly popular (Ruby on Rails! Django! Node! Go!), but then start to lose their luster over time as programmers inevitably move onto the next coding innovation.[/big]
But the thing is, programming frameworks didn’t used to be this trendy, and some of the really old ones are becoming highly-sought-after in certain sectors because they’re becoming very uncommon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cashing In Early</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/digicash-ecash-bitcoin-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/digicash-ecash-bitcoin-history/</guid>
      <description>[big]Cryptocurrency is having a bit of a moment right now, thanks in no small part to bitcoin, the currency launched under unusual circumstances that has suddenly become really, really popular. (As I write this, it’s continuing its daylong flirtation with the $10,000 valuation mark.)[/big]
But of course, while cryptocurrency is growing in popularity, bitcoin and other blockchain-based currencies can’t come close to making the claim to being the first digital currency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catch The Sun</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/calculators-fake-solar-charging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/calculators-fake-solar-charging/</guid>
      <description>[big]Recently, a video has been making the rounds online that highlights a stunning fact: We so expect cheap calculators to have solar charging capabilities that manufacturers will go to the lengths of putting a fake solar cell onto those calculators to keep up the illusion.[/big]
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uLTDuGhqE2w
If you haven’t seen this video—strap in, it’s 18 minutes long—you will soon find yourself questioning everything you know about life, love, and technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas In Clay</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/claymation-christmas-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/claymation-christmas-celebration/</guid>
      <description>[big]The strange thing about holiday classics, whether TV or film, is the way that they get drilled into the canon of nostalgia, a mush of themed entertainment along the lines of A Charlie Brown Christmas or A Christmas Story. These pieces of entertainment get repeated in part because we build memories around them. I wrote a piece about this phenomenon a couple of years ago.[/big]
But what happens if you create a piece of art that seems destined for the Christmas nostalgia ringer, and … for whatever reason, it just doesn’t happen?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloth, Meet Plastic</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/3d-printing-t-shirt-designs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/3d-printing-t-shirt-designs/</guid>
      <description>[big]As I learned a few months ago, creating custom T-shirts is a somewhat-complicated, but often quite useful way of promoting a product or raising money for an endeavor. That’s in part because it’s something that can’t effectively be done in the comfort of one’s home. [/big]
Screen-printing is a complicated process, embroidery moreso. You generally need specialized equipment, and the result of doing it at home is usually obvious—you can tell when a shirt was the product of an iron-on design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Columbus The Enigma</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/christopher-columbus-appearance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/christopher-columbus-appearance/</guid>
      <description>Editor’s note: Last week, Daily Tedium took a week off, in large part because I felt icky about writing anything related to the news cycle in the wake of the tragic Las Vegas shooting. We’re slowly getting back into things today.
&amp;nbsp;
[big]Christopher Columbus wasn’t first. He misnamed entire swaths of people, entire ethnic groups, in part because he didn’t understand what was in front of him, which understandably didn’t stick well with those people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congratulations I’m Sorry</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/gin-blossoms-hey-jealousy-tragedy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/gin-blossoms-hey-jealousy-tragedy/</guid>
      <description>[big]“Do you think it’d be all right if I could just crash here tonight?” The introduction to “Hey Jealousy,” the 1992 song by the Gin Blossoms, introduces a lackadaisical ne’er-do-well, one who laments the loss of an old relationship while asking his ex for a place to ward off his hangover, because he has nowhere else to go.[/big]
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ah5gAkna3jI
Unlike Nirvana or Pearl Jam, the darkness of the lyrics wasn’t matched by a darkness in the melody—the tune, in fact, had more in common with a melodic tune from R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Countering the Counterculture</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/countering-the-counterculture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/countering-the-counterculture/</guid>
      <description>[big]When someone mentions the phrase “Christian music,” what comes to mind? Beyond hymnals, maybe DC Talk, Jars of Clay, Kirk Franklin, or Amy Grant? Those are all good answers—answers that highlight the fact that “Jesus music” has occasionally gone mainstream in the past few decades. Heck, sometimes bands that are mainstream but spiritual, like Lifehouse, go out of their way to avoid the “Christian band” label.[/big]
But there was a time when Christian rock was less about reaching broad audiences and more about speaking out against a disinterested public—think the visceral reaction to *Time Magazine*’s &amp;ldquo;Is God Dead?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Purple</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/purple-com-early-domain-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/purple-com-early-domain-website/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE (11/06/2017): He finally sold out to the hipster mattress giant. Read an update here.
[big]Can you build a brand while working around one of the oldest sites on the internet? The answer appears to be yes.[/big]
Since 1994, a guy named Jeff Abrahamson has run the website Purple.com, a domain name which lives up to its name—the site features a deep, rich hue of purple (originally #DD00FF, now #7D26CD), a link to an FAQ page, and an offer to advertise in a very minimal way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital TV’s Tiny Achilles Heel</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/portable-digital-television-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/portable-digital-television-problems/</guid>
      <description>[big]When it comes to technology, I have a lot of love for edge cases—situations where the march of innovation actually makes things a little bit worse.[/big]
Which means that I’ve become a pretty sizable fan of the YouTube channel Techmoan in recent months. Host Mat Taylor’s magical ability to drop matter-of-fact bits of knowledge about obscure AV equipment is unparalleled, and his clip this past weekend highlighting the way that the move to digital television (basically) killed the portable TV is no exception.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Not Trust</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/do-not-resuscitate-tattoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/do-not-resuscitate-tattoo/</guid>
      <description>[big]A tattoo probably isn’t a binding legal document, but it certainly seems like a convincing argument. Clearly you must believe what you tattoo on yourself if you’re willing to go to that level of permanence, right?[/big]
But a recent saga involving a patient at a Miami hospital proved that question is a little more fraught than it seems. Doctors at Jackson Memorial Hospital, located at the University of Miami, were presented with a unconscious 70-year-old man who had a “Do Not Resuscitate” tattoo, along with his apparent signature, emblazoned on his chest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doing It For Erma</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/let-erma-do-it-internet-archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/let-erma-do-it-internet-archive/</guid>
      <description>[big]Earlier this year, I got incredibly fascinated by a book. One that had fallen off of store shelves nearly 60 years ago. The problem was, I had no way of getting hold of that book without actually going to the trouble of buying it.[/big]
Perhaps that was a little annoying, but David O. Woodbury’s 1956 work Let Erma Do It, which is titled after one of the first automated check-sorting systems ever produced, was a worthy book at the front end of the era of automation that has brought us so many things since.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down With Snippet View</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/google-books-snippet-view-archival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/google-books-snippet-view-archival/</guid>
      <description>[big]You may or may not have noticed this, but Tedium relies pretty heavily on archival content to exist. This newsletter and publication is not just about offering up weird facts: It&amp;rsquo;s often about introducing facts that have otherwise been forgotten about by the public at large.[/big]
Sometimes, this takes me in some interesting directions. An example I regularly cite is my piece on lemon juice squeeze bottles. It was the rare piece I had the chance to mostly write ahead of time, and while there were some incredibly useful starting points on the issue from the Beach Packaging Design, I find it important that, even if an existing resource like this offers a starting point, I spend time doing some digging of my own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duck, Duck, Goose?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/duck-hunt-modern-mallard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/duck-hunt-modern-mallard/</guid>
      <description>[big]The NES Zapper holds a unique place in pop culture. A gaming gimmick with somewhat limited support, the light gun, which worked by responding to a flash of light on a screen, carries a very specific sense of nostalgia for many because it was a very common pack-in cart for the Nintendo device.[/big]
It would never be released in its current form today—its somewhat realistic gun shape would never fly in 2018, in no small part because of the Lazer Tag saga that partly did in Nintendo’s one-time partner Worlds of Wonder—but it’s an amazing piece of nostalgia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything You Want</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/vertical-horizon-verizon-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/vertical-horizon-verizon-theory/</guid>
      <description>[big]On April 3, 2000, one of the most prominent companies of the 21st century was born. That day, the name and logo for Verizon became known to the masses. The company, for better or worse, became a defining middleman, fundamental to the way we use our phones and access our internet.[/big]
The next day, a popular rock band released a physical single for what would become their biggest hit. “Everything You Want,” a song from Vertical Horizon&amp;rsquo;s first major label record, had already been on the radio for a few months by this point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facts Are Facts</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/fact-vs-factoid-accuracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/fact-vs-factoid-accuracy/</guid>
      <description>[big]Last week’s piece on disc rot drew a bunch of attention from a variety of media outlets, along with some online critics that weren’t convinced that discs actually rot, based on their personal experience. (I put up a response regarding that over on Twitter.) But one reader’s comment caught my attention …[/big]
“Dude, I don&amp;rsquo;t think the word ‘factoid’ means what you think it does,” writer 15 Percent Faster informed us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fake It ’Til You Make It</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/imitation-crab-fake-meat-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/imitation-crab-fake-meat-lessons/</guid>
      <description>The veggie meat space is an interesting place these days for all sorts of reasons.
For one thing, variations of meat analogues that once were stuck in the frozen section are finally making it to the meat aisle in Safeway stores around the country, thanks to a whole bunch of persistence from the CEO of Beyond Meat. Not to be outdone are the food scientists at the Silicon Valley firm Hampton Creek, which announced this week that it was plotting its own lab-grown meat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fishing For Checks</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/mail-fishing-theft-phenomenon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/mail-fishing-theft-phenomenon/</guid>
      <description>[big]When I described to my wife the nature of the story I’m about to tell you about, I called it a “phenomenon,” to which she responded asking whether or not it was too strong a word to describe what sounds like a truly bizarre form of theft.[/big]
But as it turns out, knuckleheads using strong glue and string to pull letters (or, let’s be honest, checks) out of mailboxes is a phenomenon called “mail fishing,” and it’s a phenomenon that highlights the weaknesses of a system that is already struggling to keep up with the modern day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Floating Fast Food</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/mcbarge-vancouver-floating-fast-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/mcbarge-vancouver-floating-fast-food/</guid>
      <description>[big]The other night, I took a bit of a swipe at McDonald’s for its poor track record in the Icelandic market. Ray Kroc and company, I apologize and admit that your sausage biscuits give me modest joy. After I write this piece, I may be forced to apologize again.[/big]
That’s because I’m about to bring up a bad memory for the fast-food giant.
In the late ‘80s, the World’s Fair was still a fairly Big Deal in North America, and Vancouver played host to one of the most notable World Expo galas, Expo ’86.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Nuts for Beer Nuts</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/beer-nuts-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/beer-nuts-history/</guid>
      <description>[big]If you’re a certain age or tend to watch TV shows from a certain time, you might remember the ubiquity of the humble beer nut. Almost any sitcom in the ’80s or early ’90s that involves a bar will mention beer nuts at some point. Here’s Norm Peterson using beer nuts in a clunky analogy about women:[/big]
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=weBbZ11d5LM
And of course, there are the mandatory Simpsons references, such as when Homer buys “Kwik-E-Mart No Name Brand Beer Nuts” or when a fake beer nuts can is spring loaded with snakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Soft</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/dial-up-soft-modem-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/dial-up-soft-modem-history/</guid>
      <description>[big]Dial-up modems were underpowered enough back in the days of AOL, but at the height of their popularity, manufacturers figured out a way to make them even worse.[/big]
During the late ‘90s, a spate of companies, including big name modem manufacturers like U.S. Robotics, Motorola, and PCtel, had the idea to replace hardware-based modems, which generally required a separate digital signal processor to manage the dial-up connection, with software-based equivalents, which took this task and put it on top of the CPU already being used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Ned</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/okilly-dokilly-ned-flanders-metal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/okilly-dokilly-ned-flanders-metal/</guid>
      <description>[big]If you haven’t been following the modern metal scene, you’ve apparently been missing out on a lot of bands pigging out on pop-culture references in the best way possible.[/big]
Last month, a trio of bands went on tour that make Tenacious D look like they’re not high-concept enough. The two co-headliners of the 2017 Mockstrosity Tour were weird enough: Metalachi, a mariachi-themed metal band, shared the stage with Mac Sabbath, a McDonald’s-themed Black Sabbath cover band.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I See This Dog Everywhere</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/chico-stock-photo-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/chico-stock-photo-dog/</guid>
      <description>[big]If there’s a fact you probably don’t know about me yet but should, it’s this: I friggin’ love stock photos. Stock photos are air in my life, a way to express emotion vicariously through someone else’s ideas, a way to express a basic idea with just a few pictures, and a way to simply add elements to any photoillustration idea that comes to mind.[/big]
And to me, the greatest stock photo resource ever created is a wonderful dog named Chico.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Trademark Things All Night</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/gene-simmons-trademark-devil-horns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/gene-simmons-trademark-devil-horns/</guid>
      <description>[big]Gene Simmons, love him or hate him, has a history of trademarking very common things.[/big]
As any fan of the Scottish power-pop group Teenage Fanclub knows, the band’s label, Geffen, had to send a check to Simmons because the cover of the alternative rock band’s Bandwagonesque (which is a stellar album) featured a sack of money with a dollar sign on it—an image that Gene Simmons has long owned the trademark for, as it was the logo of his label, Simmons Records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Cream Fakery</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/breyers-frozen-dairy-dessert-not-ice-cream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/breyers-frozen-dairy-dessert-not-ice-cream/</guid>
      <description>[big]A couple of months ago, I was scooping myself a bowl of ice cream, when I discovered something interesting and a little disturbing: Nowhere on the label did the ice cream describe itself as “ice cream.”[/big]
The label was for Breyers, a brand that has a long, lengthy history in the ice cream manufacturing game and a pledge to use “high quality ingredients.” But this pledge had been put into doubt by the fact that Breyers couldn’t describe what it was selling as ice cream, but rather “frozen dairy dessert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland’s Latest And Greatest</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/iceland-airlines-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/iceland-airlines-history/</guid>
      <description>[big]Iceland is one of my favorite countries. Always has been, always will be, and not because I’m a Björk-head, really. Really, I think it’s because of its beautiful simplicity, relatively isolated location, and ease of travel from the United States. (It’s certainly not because of the fermented shark.)[/big]
So it warmed my heart that over the weekend, I ran into not one, but two fascinating stories about Iceland and the outside world—one from the distant past, and the other from the present day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ink-Stained Headlines</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/printer-ink-criminal-activity-theft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/printer-ink-criminal-activity-theft/</guid>
      <description>[big]You know what’s a terrible racket? Printer ink. Driven up by artificial markets and complex, incompatible cartridge systems, printers have become one of the most depressing parts of any computing experience—especially if you own one at home.[/big]
And they bring out the worst behavior in companies. Hewlett-Packard last year had a scandal on its hands after it added digital rights management to its printers, then turned it off after people complained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Blogging Dead?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/is-blogging-dead-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/is-blogging-dead-2018/</guid>
      <description>[big]Is a newsletter a blog? And if it is, does that make what I do with Tedium blogging? And if so, is that practice in decline as we enter 2018?[/big]
That’s not exactly how I approach this process, certainly, but I think it’s worth discussing at length at the moment, as the culture of blogging evolves away from what it once was. Over at JSTOR’s excellent daily news site, author Farah Mohammed analyzes blogging in the past tense, pondering whether the medium is in broader decline, as big-name bloggers like Nicholas Kristof leave the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s A Duck Blur</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/ducktales-revival-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/ducktales-revival-history/</guid>
      <description>[big]In the past couple of weeks, a bit of DuckTales-mania has hit the internet in a way that could best be described as giddy-ing. It’s understandable. It’s not every day Disney gives the fans what they want—and it ’s not every day that the results of that are pretty amazing.[/big]
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EURi91Eb6I8
And it’s worth that level of nostalgia, because it’s reviving what perhaps was the most important cartoon of the ‘80s—both culturally and from an economic standpoint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kodak Krypto</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/kodak-cryptocurrency-gimmick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/kodak-cryptocurrency-gimmick/</guid>
      <description>[big]Let’s admit that a long time ago, Kodak was a hugely important company. In fact, it was a Hugely Important Company, on a level rivaled in influence by perhaps only Ford and General Electric in the mainstream.[/big]
Everyone takes pictures, and Kodak catered to the masses, iterating repeatedly based on consumer needs.
But, eventually, the company made a bad bet, choosing to protect film at a time when everything was going digital (even though its engineers helped invent some of the basic technology), and that bad bet cost it that lofty position as an important company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Be Frank</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/frank-sidebottom-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/frank-sidebottom-story/</guid>
      <description>[big]Behind the Mask: It takes a certain kind of human being to create a persona for yourself, and—by all accounts—Chris Sievey was very much that person.[/big]
The British musician made his name in the ‘80s with an oddball comic persona named Frank Sidebottom, who was noted for both the giant mask he wore and his ability to rewrite classic pop songs into comic odes about Frank’s hometown, the Manchester suburb of Timperley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Like A Rock</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/bob-seger-digital-holdout/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/bob-seger-digital-holdout/</guid>
      <description>[big]Music executive Tim Quirk is best known for his band Too Much Joy, but his big problem these days is that there’s not enough joy—at least when it comes to the music of Bob Seger.[/big]
Last week, Quirk made a lengthy case in an NPR article as to why Seger, who is barely represented on any digital music platforms at all, should make his back catalog available on services like iTunes and Spotify.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Literal Dad Rock</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/adrian-belew-oh-daddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/adrian-belew-oh-daddy/</guid>
      <description>[big]It doesn’t get nearly as much attention as, say, 1992, but 1989 may have been the most interesting year for modern rock.[/big]
The reason for this was that the creation of Billboard’s Modern Rock Tracks chart the year prior created a context for people in the music industry who never would have had a chance at having a mainstream hit otherwise. And MTV, with its 120 Minutes franchise going strong, was ready to push the songs, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lucky Tickets</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/lottery-error-south-carolina/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/lottery-error-south-carolina/</guid>
      <description>[big]If a lottery system screws up, should the winners who benefited from that screwup win the prize they unwittingly earned?[/big]
That’s the question that officials from the South Carolina Education Lottery are currently grappling with after last month producing a whole lot of winning tickets by accident through its Holiday Cash Add-A-Play game. On Christmas day, the game produced thousands of tickets over a two-hour period that produced a winner for each game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lurking In Your Bed</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/hipster-mattress-online-sales-practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/hipster-mattress-online-sales-practices/</guid>
      <description>[big]As you guys may or may not know, my first really big piece on Tedium was a takedown of sorts on hipster mattresses. It pondered the idea of how the companies came to prominence, as well as what it would take to start up a company just like this. It was absurd, but it was fun to write. It’s currently the top-ranking item on Google for the term “hipster mattress.”[/big]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modem Madness</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/video-game-modem-experiments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/video-game-modem-experiments/</guid>
      <description>[big]A couple of months ago, I gave a little notice to Sega’s early attempt to tie cable connections with video games, the Sega Channel. Certainly, it was the most interesting communications-related experiment that Sega had formulated that year. But as it turns out, it was probably not Sega’s most interesting experiment involving communications. Far from it.[/big]
Now, to start off, Sega is famously a company that, during the Genesis/Mega Drive era at least, was not opposed to add-ons for this device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moore R. Stevie Moore</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/r-stevie-moore-starting-points/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/r-stevie-moore-starting-points/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: This is a companion piece to yesterday&amp;rsquo;s newsletter issue on R. Stevie Moore, by David Buck. Read that first, then come back here.
&amp;nbsp;
[big]R. Stevie Moore&amp;rsquo;s vast body of work may intimidate some and may delight others. I&amp;rsquo;ve taken the liberty of curating a list of my top R. Stevie Moore songs that will entertain, amuse and otherwise. They also serve as a great introduction to the man and his work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Meat</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/char-meck-a-nator-meatloaf-sandwich/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/char-meck-a-nator-meatloaf-sandwich/</guid>
      <description>[big]If you know anything about school lunches, it’s this: Trying new things on the menu isn’t always the best idea.[/big]
But that didn’t stop the Charlotte-Mecklenburg School District from introducing a new product called the “Char-Meck-A-Nator.” What’s a “Char-Meck-A-Nator” you ask? Well, it’s a sandwich with a ground beef patty, with cheese mixed in, and tomato ketchup baked on the top of the burger patty.
If that sounds like meatloaf on a bun, that’s because it’s freakin&amp;rsquo; meatloaf on a bun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mystic Knights of the Movie Soundtrack</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/oingo-boingo-pop-culture-appearances/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/oingo-boingo-pop-culture-appearances/</guid>
      <description>[big]Before Danny Elfman became the go-to guy for scoring great films, his band Oingo Boingo was a mid-&amp;lsquo;80s go-to for soundtrack contributions. This ensured that, even as Elfman moved away from the band, Oingo Boingo would carry a massive pop-culture footprint.[/big]
&amp;ldquo;I think Oingo&amp;rsquo;s music is good for the audience for those films; the people will relate to it,&amp;rdquo; Elfman said of the phenomenon, according to the Encyclopedia of Pop, Rock &amp;amp; Soul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Thanks, Spammers</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/seo-spammers-ruining-open-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/seo-spammers-ruining-open-web/</guid>
      <description>[big]Tedium has a decent number of readers, but when it comes down to it, it’s a small blip on the larger internet—a small professional publisher at a time when so many of our publishers are large and centralized.[/big]
As a result of this relatively unique status, I get a lot of messages on a fairly regular basis asking me to do one of a few things:
 Update a link on a story I’ve already written to get in a business I didn’t previously mention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Older Than Ever</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/manute-bol-age-discrepancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/manute-bol-age-discrepancy/</guid>
      <description>[big]Manute Bol, a literal giant on the NBA court as the league&amp;rsquo;s second-tallest player ever, was certainly an epic defender, but in some ways, he stood out because he was probably one of the most interesting player stories in NBA history.[/big]
And his story got more interesting this week after the college basketball coach who first discovered him laid out a surprising detail about the 7-foot-7 Sudanese player who became one of the best shot-blockers in the league’s history: Apparently, when Bol played basketball in the NBA, he was possibly 20 years older than his teammates—minimum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Memedom</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/every-headline-on-the-internet-meme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/every-headline-on-the-internet-meme/</guid>
      <description>[big]On Monday, something happened which I feel the need to address. I found a picture of a particularly depressing piece of pizza on Twitter. I saw a couple other folks making jokes about this pizza. And I decided to make a joke about something I’m very familiar with: Journalism.[/big]
Little did I know that I would be responsible for creating a tweet so viral that it had the potential to crash my phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Otis Nixon, the CD-i, and Me</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/otis-nixon-the-cd-i-and-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/otis-nixon-the-cd-i-and-me/</guid>
      <description>*Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Once I heard this story from my pal D. Frank Smith about America&amp;rsquo;s Team, the Atlanta Braves, and the worst console of a generation, I knew I had to share it with you guys. Enjoy!*
&amp;nbsp;
[big]“Is that Otis Nixon?” I asked my dad as we walked through an Atlanta mall in 1992.[/big]
It took a moment to adjust my eyes to reality, because Nixon was wearing a suit, not his traditional Atlanta Braves uniform, likely because he was doing an endorsement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Lives In Fabric</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/t-shirt-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/t-shirt-history/</guid>
      <description>[big]When Amory Blaine decided to pack a T-shirt before heading to boarding school, he set in place a piece of literary history. Amory, the protagonist of F. Scott Fitzgerald’s This Side of Paradise, was the first literary character to use a T-shirt, ever.[/big]
“So early in September Amory, provided with ‘six suits summer underwear, six suits winter underwear, one sweater or T shirt, one jersey, one overcoat, winter, etc.,’ set out for New England, the land of schools,” the passage states.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pass Over The Beer</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/hummus-flavored-beer-israel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/hummus-flavored-beer-israel/</guid>
      <description>[big]I&amp;rsquo;m not a very good cook, though I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten better over the years. One of the best examples of my culinary struggles involved an infamous attempt to create a concoction I called &amp;ldquo;French toast hummus,&amp;rdquo; an idea that started as an inside joke with my friends that I for some reason attempted to follow through with in an attempt to make the joke even funnier. Problem was, the joke was on me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plotting A Takeover</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/desmos-ti-graphing-calculator-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/desmos-ti-graphing-calculator-competition/</guid>
      <description>[big]Of all the artificial monopolies created by government and standards bodies, the one created for the graphing calculator by standardized testing bodies is perhaps the most disappointing.[/big]
If the TI-84+ calculator that has become a fact of life for many students were used as a way to teach teens basic programming skills through a technical-but-ultimately-harmless interface, perhaps in the way that the Raspberry Pi has gained currency in the education world, it would be a great tool for education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press Your Luck</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/button-pressing-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/button-pressing-study/</guid>
      <description>[big]Nearly a year ago, I bought a mechanical keyboard in an attempt to understand a phenomenon that I had been hearing about for a long time—the fact that many people really freaking love the heft of these old-style keys, which don’t get nearly as much love as they probably should. What I found was that I never wanted to use my full-sized Apple keyboard ever again. Burn that thing with fire!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reopening the Book</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/encyclopaedia-britannica-cdrom-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/encyclopaedia-britannica-cdrom-update/</guid>
      <description>[big]If you look at nearly every retelling of Encyclopaedia Britannica’s move away from the physical book, the story goes something like this: Britannica ran head-first into the digital revolution and nearly lost its head in the process. And, like a few other retellings of this story, that was the story arc of a recent piece of mine on the matter.[/big]
So it wasn’t the world’s greatest feeling to see someone claiming that I had gotten this story arc completely wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Funny Page</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/newspaper-funny-pages-rethink-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/newspaper-funny-pages-rethink-2018/</guid>
      <description>[big]At the beginning of 2018, we’re on the cusp of something that might arguably be one of the biggest changes to newspapers in generations: Comic strips, one of the newspaper’s great standbys, are starting to “age out.”[/big]
This took quite a long time, but two major things have happened in recent weeks that suggest a major sea change is on the way: the January death of Mort Walker, who was responsible for creating Beetle Bailey and co-creating Hi and Lois, and the decision by cartoonist Guy Gilchrist (who has plenty of years in front of him) to stop doing Nancy, whose final edition published on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock and Roll Remodel</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/rock-and-roll-mcdonalds-remodel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/rock-and-roll-mcdonalds-remodel/</guid>
      <description>[big]In the early 1990s, Chicago icon and outsider musician Wesley Willis wrote a tribute to one of his favorite dining establishments—McDonald&amp;rsquo;s. Dubbed &amp;ldquo;Rock and Roll McDonald&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; and set to a fun, keyboard-driven melody, the song extolls the virtues of the fast food haven. Willis once spent time both in and out of the McDonald&amp;rsquo;s and surrounding area, making and selling his beautiful drawings most days.[/big]
(via the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s Yelp page)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rough Edges</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/ceramic-coffee-cups-rough-spots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/ceramic-coffee-cups-rough-spots/</guid>
      <description>[big]This sounds strange to think about, but when it comes down to it, there’s often a reason for everything, even if you’ve never even pondered it before.[/big]
Case in point: Have you ever wondered why traditional ceramic coffee cups, which are smooth around the edges, have that rough circular spot on the bottom? That was not a happy accident—it was a design choice.
See, that squat ceramic coffee cup, the one you’ve seen millions of times, in diners and living rooms, sometimes with brass-knuckle designs, came from somewhere—specifically Victor, New York, a town that initially made its name building porcelain insulators in the late 19th century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search By Text</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/google-sms-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/google-sms-history/</guid>
      <description>[big]Back in college, some friends and I found ourselves dealing with a pre-mobile Internet problem. After engaging in activity that is now legal for recreational use in four states, we desperately needed to order pizza. No one knew the number for Domino’s or any other place from memory. And we weren’t immediately near a computer with internet access. Through the disappointment and haze, my friend suddenly remembered, &amp;ldquo;Hey, we can text Google!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seaweed: The Next Kale?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/kale-seaweed-mainstream-consumption/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/kale-seaweed-mainstream-consumption/</guid>
      <description>[big]In Tuesday’s issue, I briefly noted how a Maine man was looking to revive straws made from rye—a practice that had fallen out of favor thanks to the invention of the paper straw.[/big]
It appears that rye straws aren’t the only unusual food-related item coming out of the Pine Tree State. Another entrepreneur, a guy named Josh Rogers, is attempting to make the case for tea made from seaweed.
“A lot of people don’t think it’s weird anymore,” Rogers told the Portland Press-Herald late last month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sega, In Channel Form</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/sega-channel-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/sega-channel-history/</guid>
      <description>[big]If you’re a fan of Nintendo today, odds are you’ve been getting a bit of an earful about the company’s botched voice chat, which is a key element of the company’s online service for the Switch.[/big]
But video game companies failing to properly roll out online features is a problem that’s anything but new—in fact, it’s been happening for decades, a mixture of failing to understand the audience and failing to properly use the technology in the right context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai&#39;s Untold Story</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/mahjong-shanghai-brodie-lockard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/mahjong-shanghai-brodie-lockard/</guid>
      <description>[big]It’s hard to track the history of mahjong solitaire, a Chinese game that came to America sometime in the 1920s, but one thing is for sure: More than 30 years ago, an electronic version of the game quietly took the computing world by storm.[/big]
Less known is the truly impressive feat that game represented. Originally built on the PLATO computing platform by Brodie Lockard in 1981, the computer game was groundbreaking both on a technical basis—the educational platform PLATO, as I wrote recently for Motherboard, inspired a lot broken ground—but also a personal one for Lockard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shelf This Elf</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/elf-bowling-movie-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/elf-bowling-movie-review/</guid>
      <description>[big]**Last week’s article about the game Elf Bowling** really hit the sweet spot for a lot of folks. It’s a fun, maybe not groundbreaking game that is great to play for a few minutes—or based on your addiction level, a whole lot longer. (It should be remade for smartphones—the mechanics work really well for that medium.)[/big]
But by no means was the game, with its cheeky jokes, offbeat animation, and goofy concept, enough to carry a movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shorthand For No</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/scotland-journalism-cerebral-palsy-controversy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/scotland-journalism-cerebral-palsy-controversy/</guid>
      <description>[big]In an era when literally every rule of traditional journalism has been blown to shreds (case in point: the fact I can run a site and newsletter like this), it’s depressing to see how far some sticklers are willing to go in maintaining rules that make zero sense in 2017.[/big]
Case in point: It was revealed this week that a Scottish college wouldn’t let a journalism student with cerebral palsy pass a course to gain a journalism qualification … because he can’t write shorthand due to his out-of-his-control physical condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solved</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/unsolved-mysteries-modern-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/unsolved-mysteries-modern-updates/</guid>
      <description>[big]More than 30 years ago, onetime Eliot Ness stand-in Robert Stack found a way to embellish his legacy in the modern era.[/big]
The solution was through a show named Unsolved Mysteries, one of the first reality-based shows of the modern era, mixing scripted plots with true stories. First appearing as a special in 1987, it became a full-fledged series not long after the success of a similar program, America’s Most Wanted on Fox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special Delivery</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/unique-pizza-delivery-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/unique-pizza-delivery-methods/</guid>
      <description>[big]As I highlighted recently, Amtrak trains are rife with delays—which can be blamed on a combination of failing infrastructure and a lack of track ownership.[/big]
We can’t solve the problem of Amtrak very easily, but pizza is a pretty nice salve.
On Sunday, a mechanical failure knocked out a train on the way to Washington from New York City, eventually leading passengers to have to switch trains. While they were stuck waiting in the Wilmington, Delaware, area, someone stuck on the underfunded transit medium got the idea to call a local pizza place for nourishment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stating The Seemingly Obvious</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/utah-bar-restaurant-sign-regulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/utah-bar-restaurant-sign-regulation/</guid>
      <description>[big]Utah is a great state, but with its historic ties to the Mormon religion (and that religion’s hard-to-ignore political clout), it occasionally runs into some head-scratching situations—especially when it comes to alcohol.[/big]
The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints prohibits its members from consuming alcohol, and that has informed the state’s laws on the issue over the years.
Beer is sold at bars and some restaurants, but at an alcohol level that barely even counts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stone Stooges</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/three-stooges-gravestone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/three-stooges-gravestone/</guid>
      <description>[big]There was once a time when The Three Stooges ruled the late-night roost with a series of TV marathons that ensured the Vaudeville-era comedians would have a longer reach than many of their contemporaries. For decades, TBS owned this little niche.[/big]
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C_pN1eqjMWw
Even now, cable networks like IFC and AMC run the Stooges at odd times, in the middle of the night, mostly on weekends, as fillers between other movies. In some ways, their broad brand of slapstick humor has grown into a niche endeavor in the modern day—in part because more sophisticated takes on physical humor (think the eyerolls and subtle cringeiness of The Office and its variants, or Paul Rudd’s cafeteria scene from Wet Hot American Summer) have made the pokes and prods of Moe Howard and his second bananas seem a little dull.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strung Out</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/banana-peel-string-phloem-bundles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/banana-peel-string-phloem-bundles/</guid>
      <description>[big]Perhaps you’ve seen them and assumed that you weren’t really good at taking the peel off the banana—the equivalent of banana lint. Perhaps you’ve eaten one, unsure of what it was, and wondered why it wasn’t as sweet as the rest of the banana.[/big]
I’m talking, of course, about the little string inside of the banana, which is often in the peel, but sometimes on the banana itself. It’s a curio that few people discuss for some reason.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super FX Turbo Mode</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/star-fox-super-fx-overclocking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/star-fox-super-fx-overclocking/</guid>
      <description>[big]I’m going to come right out and say it: I want a Super NES Classic. I wanted an NES Classic, but that sold out too quickly and the variations on the market cost way too much money, so I have my finger on the trigger for potential pre-orders of the new device, expected to hit this week. I, like most of my other fellow retro geeks, can at least embrace the fact that we still have as much of a shot at getting these mini-consoles right now as we did Pearl Jam tickets circa 1994.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swearing In Code</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/pearls-before-swine-morse-code-swearing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/pearls-before-swine-morse-code-swearing/</guid>
      <description>[big]Unless you’re listening to a numbers station for work reasons, odds are that you aren’t going to need Morse Code for any good reason. Which means that, if you want to take advantage of the lack of general knowledge of Morse Code, you absolutely can.[/big]
The folk group Pearls Before Swine, a modest psychedelic phenomenon in 1967, thought they were pulling a fast one on their audience when they recorded the tune “Oh Dear (Miss Morse),” the most popular song from the band’s hit album One Nation Underground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching Labels</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/retail-theft-ticket-switching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/retail-theft-ticket-switching/</guid>
      <description>[big]Recently I had two pretty good six-packs of beer for $3.99 each. I had scored a deal because I wasn’t picky—the beers were rebranded by a grocery store to celebrate a special event that happened months prior, but the tell was on the cap—these beers, despite the labels, had been brewed by a well-known local craft brewer, and were the same beers that were in the “beer cave” for seven dollars more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Symbiotic Infringement</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/consumer-john-oliver-copyright-infringement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/consumer-john-oliver-copyright-infringement/</guid>
      <description>[big]On a day when the news is utterly saturated with stories about a famous YouTube user getting blocked from the service, I’d like to spend some time writing about another YouTube user who was blocked from the service today.[/big]
You don’t know him, but you’ve likely seen the videos he uploaded—because news sites linked those videos pretty religiously.
The user, named “consumer,” played a small but important role in the YouTube ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tear Down This Paywall</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/bloomberg-tear-down-this-paywall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/bloomberg-tear-down-this-paywall/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: I wrote this on Medium last night, but am also sharing here in hopes of giving this issue the attention it deserves.
[big]I write stuff that is driven on research. It’s an important part of what I do. That research takes me weird places—into patent filings, reading news stories that are decades old, diving into snippets of old books, hoping that something—anything—will get me closer to the end of the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech’s Biggest Racket</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/apple-magsafe-charger-racket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/apple-magsafe-charger-racket/</guid>
      <description>[big]Over at the New York Times, John Herrman has given voice to a certain kind of obsolescence that we’ve come to see a lot—that created not by the technology itself, but by the constant forward thrust of technology that has forced a device that technically still has a lot of years left in it into the dumpster.[/big]
“If my old iPad could talk, it might ask me what has changed,” he wrote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Difficult Second Album</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/daily-tedium-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/daily-tedium-announcement/</guid>
      <description>[big]Testing 1, 2, 3: Two years ago, Tedium got its start based on what I like to call the &amp;ldquo;difficult second album&amp;rdquo; theory. &amp;ldquo;The cliche that you have a lifetime to make your first album and only a year or two to make your second holds true,&amp;rdquo; The Guardian&amp;rsquo;s Dorian Lynskey wrote back in 2003 of this basic concept, in the context of The Strokes, whose second album wasn&amp;rsquo;t actually all that difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Four-Minute Villain</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/batman-tv-show-commercial-length/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/batman-tv-show-commercial-length/</guid>
      <description>One of the best parts of the streaming era is that you can avoid watching a ton of commercials if you don’t want to.
And in some ways, TV is responding to this change. Last year, Turner announced it was cutting back on commercials on its cable channels, and Fox—currently the market leader in commercial clutter—is trying to do the same. These days, 15 minutes of commercials in a single hour, give or take a couple of minutes, is about average.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Fringe</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/chris-carlson-puppeteer-fringe-candidate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/chris-carlson-puppeteer-fringe-candidate/</guid>
      <description>[big]I’ve mentioned this before, but one of my favorite old magazines of all time is a dead-tree tome called Internet Underground that did a pretty good job of covering early internet culture thoughtfully, and perhaps with a little edge.[/big]
Of their many articles from back in the day, one that sticks with me is from their third issue, in which writer Alex Gordon highlighted the way that third-party “fringe” presidential candidates were using the Web to help draw attention to their unlikely-but-still-valid campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Game Of Life</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/nbc-the-wall-cultural-importance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/nbc-the-wall-cultural-importance/</guid>
      <description>[big]There isn’t a better explanation for the current state of the American psyche than the impressive success of The Wall, which just had its season finale last night. It has a name that evokes a certain political football without ever actually referencing it. It counts perhaps the world’s most famous basketball player as an executive producer. It counts perhaps the busiest man in the world— the CEO of a freaking media empire—as its host.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Gnome Fad</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/gnomes-1977-literary-fad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/gnomes-1977-literary-fad/</guid>
      <description>[big]Quick: Four decades ago, back in 1977, what was the biggest pop-culture phenomena around? You probably said disco, maybe Star Wars. Fleetwood Mac was big that year. Maybe you thought of Laverne &amp;amp; Shirley, the top-rated show of that year.[/big]
But one surprisingly forgotten but unappreciated piece of pop culture that hit in a big way that year was the Gnome fad. The 1977 kid’s book, published in English in October of that year, became a massive phenomenon, one that was a mainstay on the New York Times bestseller list for more than a year after its release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Platform Problem</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/youtube-demonetization-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/youtube-demonetization-problem/</guid>
      <description>[big]Yesterday afternoon, I admit, was a bit rough. In a good way, but still rough. A piece from months ago by Andrew Egan, my regular contributor to the site, hit the Reddit front page completely unexpectedly, bringing my server to its knees. It was not exactly how I saw myself spending a Tuesday afternoon, but I got things worked out. Bump up the specs on the cloud server a little bit, change some server settings to make sure it&amp;rsquo;s working to the best of its abilities, and back in business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Late-Career Recovery</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/john-fahey-late-career-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/john-fahey-late-career-recovery/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I re-watched the movie Hugo, a truly dazzling 2011 Martin Scorsese film about a young boy who, in the process of running the clocks inside a 1930s-era train station, helps an old shop owner realize that he’s not a failure, but a living legend.
It’s a story, based on a book, that’s rooted in pure fantasy—I mean, obviously it’s unlikely that a young child could get away with the scheme suggested in the film—but Georges Méliès is a real guy, best known for his inventive early films, most notably A Trip to the Moon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lazies</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/the-razzies-lazy-nominations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/the-razzies-lazy-nominations/</guid>
      <description>[big]The Golden Raspberry Awards are one of our greatest homespun counterculture traditions, one that set the stage for appreciation of bad film on a mainstream scale. While it didn’t change the world, it’s certainly an important institution.[/big]
But the award ceremony, which has always been designed as a way to piggyback on the attention of the Academy Awards, may be at a point where it its relevance is hitting rock-bottom. It’s always gone for the low-hanging fruit—the raspberries, really—but this year felt particularly, well lazy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Other Browser War</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/opera-omnibar-adware-booking-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/opera-omnibar-adware-booking-com/</guid>
      <description>Update: Opera has claimed that this was an unintentional error and is fixing it on their end. The point about paying for browsers still stands, however, and as a result, I&amp;rsquo;ll keep this post up for posterity.
&amp;nbsp;
[big]I find it fascinating that, of all the pieces of software we use on a daily basis, the one we literally use the most, our web browser, is one that we do not pay for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Purple Unicorn</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/purple-com-domain-sold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/purple-com-domain-sold/</guid>
      <description>[big]For more than 23 years, the Purple.com domain reflected one guy’s simple, colorful vision. But last week, the man who owned what was secretly becoming the internet’s most valuable domain finally sold it. To … wait for it … a mattress company.[/big]
Per Domain Investing, Purple Innovations LLC, the company that owns the hipster mattress giant worth an estimated $1.1 billion, purchased the domain from Jeff Abrahamson, who spent more than two decades pledging that he would never sell the domain—instead suggesting he’d rather hold onto the URL and license it out to an interested party for a six-digit sum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Seeds Are Better</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/osage-orange-edible-seeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/osage-orange-edible-seeds/</guid>
      <description>[big]Of the many strange niches one can find on YouTube, the most interesting might be that spearheaded by Jared Rydelek, a man who has gained some notice on YouTube for tracking down rare kinds of fruit to try out. His channel, Weird Explorer, features him mostly talking about the weird fruits he’s eaten over the years, often while traveling. (It’s a very specific niche.)[/big]
Clearly, this takes him a lot of strange directions, including in the direction of one of the most unusual-yet-common fruits you might find in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wesley Willis WinAmp Connection</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/wesley-willis-winamp-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/wesley-willis-winamp-history/</guid>
      <description>[big]Wesley Willis was a prolific musician and wonderful artist. Beloved by most folks he ran across, it’s no surprise his legacy would live on in an unlikely place—your computer.[/big]
Some may recognize Mike the llama as the mascot of legendary music software WinAmp. But did you know, there is a somewhat tenuous, but quite obvious connection to Wesley built into the software?
Windows users in the mid-to-late 90s are probably used WinAmp or know of it in some capacity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Windex Problem</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/information-literacy-students-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/information-literacy-students-problem/</guid>
      <description>[big]If you’ve been a longtime reader of Tedium, you’ve probably noticed that my byline shows up most of the time. Maybe 80 to 90 percent of the time.[/big]
In part, this is because this is my project, and I limit the number of things we publish every month. Also in part, it&amp;rsquo;s because I feel uncomfortable with having writers work for me for free. (The one person I do have writing outside pieces, Andrew Egan, has actually been getting paid for them!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They Stopped (Sorta)</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/singular-they-ap-stylebook-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/singular-they-ap-stylebook-update/</guid>
      <description>[big]Last summer, I wrote an impassioned plea in favor of embracing the singular “they,” which I called “the Rodney Dangerfield of grammar.”[/big]
Basically, this word use, which has no simple singular equivalent that doesn’t dive into awkward gender politics when the subject’s grammar hasn’t been revealed, has been written around for hundreds of years by newspapers and in other formalized grammar settings. The Associated Press, notably, had resisted changing its mind on this issue, even as the linguistic tide started to favor it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things That Make You Go Hmmmm …</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/everybody-dance-now-car-singing-fine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/everybody-dance-now-car-singing-fine/</guid>
      <description>[big]As early-‘90s dance music icons go, C+C Music Factory is no KLF, though in many ways, they’ve managed to hold onto a small smidgen of cultural relevance thanks to the 1990 dance-pop classic &amp;ldquo;Gonna Make You Sweat (Everybody Dance Now),” which at the time of release drew more notoriety for full-sized Martha Wash being hidden from the group’s music video—one of two videos where that took place that year.[/big]
These days, however, it’ll be known as the song that will get you fined by the Montreal police for yelling in your car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is My Top Secret Room</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/zelda-chris-houlihan-secret-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/zelda-chris-houlihan-secret-room/</guid>
      <description>[big]These days, The Legend of Zelda is getting a whole lot of well-deserved extra attention as a franchise, thanks to Breath of the Wild being one of the Nintendo Switch’s launch titles.[/big]
(Side note: We totally covered Bitrex months before Nintendo started covering its Switch cartridges with it. Yes, we’re ahead of the curve.)
But as interesting as Breath of the Wild is, I wanted to spend a minute talking about one of the weirdest things ever to appear on a Nintendo cartridge, ever, let alone a Legend of Zelda game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Van Could Change Your Life</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/the-shins-van-giveaway-heartworms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/the-shins-van-giveaway-heartworms/</guid>
      <description>[big]On the grand scale of rock-band gimmicks, the move by The Shins to give away their old van to a deserving up-and-coming artist is pretty noble, despite the fact that, well, James Mercer is the only current member of the band that actually rode in it when it was in regular use.[/big]
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wa9cWoKQyoA
The band, which is giving its freshly refurbished 1990 Ford 350 Clubwagon to the band that records the best cover of a song on the indie pop act’s new album Heartworms, has the best intentions in mind for this van, which has probably seen a lot of big cities and small towns over the years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Throwing Muses</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/granny-free-throw-comeback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/granny-free-throw-comeback/</guid>
      <description>[big]Throughout his entire 15-year playing career, NBA legend Rick Barry was a man without shame.[/big]
He won a lot of accolades for his play, and was a massively successful star. But he won that success, strangely, by using a style of shot that most people throw out before they reach middle school. See, Barry was an underhand free-throw shooter, and it worked really well for him: For every 10 free throw shots he attempted during his career in the ABA and NBA, he made about nine of them, a rate that was extremely impressive for its time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Data</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/ibm-port-a-punch-card-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/ibm-port-a-punch-card-device/</guid>
      <description>[big]These days, we have a whole lot of options for portably collecting information that needs to be put in a computer. But in 1960, that wasn’t always easy.[/big]
Usually, this meant paper—but considering they barely even had working OCR at the time, it also meant a lot of manual entry after the fact.
Fortunately, IBM had a solution to this problem: A portable device called the Port-A-Punch, which allowed workers in the field to create their own punch cards by hand to use for later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toilet Duck Dynasty</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/toilet-duck-design-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/toilet-duck-design-history/</guid>
      <description>[big]It’s not easy to come up with a product that’s built around a completely, utterly unique design. Especially involving a topic as unflattering as cleaning a toilet.[/big]
But in the early 1980s, a man named Walter Düring had such a moment. The Swiss man’s company, Düring AG, had made a name for itself with the concept of decalcification, based on a formula his mother, Maria, came up with. But it was in the early 1980s that the firm had come up with something truly successful on a mainstream stage: A uniquely shaped nozzle that could spray decalcifiers into obscure crevices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tommy’s Back</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/best-friends-tommy-wiseau-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/best-friends-tommy-wiseau-review/</guid>
      <description>[big]Tommy Wiseau, the legendary auteur of The Room, may not be a great filmmaker in the traditional sense, but he has a pretty enthused fanbase—a base of which I admit being a part of. And that fanbase, which has stuck with Wiseau through unusual projects like his 2015 Hulu series The Neighbors, has gotten a lot of mileage out of a single film that has owned the midnight movie circuit for years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total Eclipse Of The Counterfeit</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/amazon-counterfeit-solar-eclipse-glasses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/amazon-counterfeit-solar-eclipse-glasses/</guid>
      <description>[big]If you bought a pair of eclipse glasses from Amazon recently, you probably received a shock when the company informed you that it was selling solar eclipse glasses that weren’t certified to be used to watch the forthcoming eclipse—and that you would be getting a refund.[/big]
See, here’s what happened: A lot of major science and optical associations have been working with NASA on a campaign to ensure that people are buying glasses verified to be used during the solar eclipse happening in North America over the next few days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U Can’t Touch This</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/apple-touch-bar-north-carolina-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/apple-touch-bar-north-carolina-bar/</guid>
      <description>[big]Our computers are becoming so sophisticated that they might just include built-in cheating functionality—even if it’s not really intended. Which should make life pretty interesting for teachers and assessment boards.[/big]
Today’s example involves Apple’s modestly useful Touch Bar, which was met with a modest level of derision when it was first announced in September. Sensing a problem, the Board of Law Examiners of the State of North Carolina recently announced that it would require people taking the bar to turn off the Touch Bar, out of concern that it would allow users to cheat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unsettled</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/ticketmaster-live-nation-free-ticket-settlement-boycott/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/ticketmaster-live-nation-free-ticket-settlement-boycott/</guid>
      <description>[big]Nearly a quarter-century ago, Pearl Jam—which had become the biggest band in the world around this time effectively by ignoring the music industry orthodoxy of the time—decided to take on live music’s biggest middleman.[/big]
It probably hurt their career to take aim at Ticketmaster, which had become known for charging expensive service fees on every ticket it sold. But the politically minded band did, going so far as to file a complaint with the Justice Department and speak in front of Congress about the problem, something rock bands don’t usually do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Are All Made Of Stars</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/michelin-chef-removal-request/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/michelin-chef-removal-request/</guid>
      <description>[big]Honestly, it makes no sense why a company best known for manufacturing tires is such an important voice in the world of fine dining, but Michelin has embraced its gastronomic role with gusto for more than a century.[/big]
Now, it turns out that one of its most-decorated chefs isn’t feeling that gusto himself. Sébastien Bras, a French chef whose restaurant Le Suquet has been a three-star mainstay of the Michelin guide for close to two decades, made the first-ever request to be removed from the guide without a significant change to his model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Can Dance If We Want To</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/nyc-dancing-regulation-repeal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/nyc-dancing-regulation-repeal/</guid>
      <description>[big]New York City has long been known as a fairly progressive place, one known as welcoming to ethnic and cultural groups long marginalized by society. So it’s surprising that the city’s laws regarding dancing are more appropriate for a small town in an ‘80s movie.[/big]
The city’s long, strange aversion to dancing is finally expected to come to an end on October 31st when a prohibition-era law is expected to be repealed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebTV’s Greatest Celebrity User</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/r-stevie-moore-webtv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/r-stevie-moore-webtv/</guid>
      <description>[big]R. Stevie Moore is an extraordinary archivist of his own material. Recently, the online short film series Great Big Story released a superb mini documentary about Stevie and on April 6, 2018, R. Stevie Moore was featured on the front page of Wikipedia.[/big]
The page asked “Did you know R. Stevie Moore pioneered modern indie rock, earning him the sobriquet ‘the godfather of home recording?’”
Yes, Wikipedia. I believe we already knew that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weirdest Ransom Note Ever</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/joseph-l-popp-aids-ransomware/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/joseph-l-popp-aids-ransomware/</guid>
      <description>[big]Back in the ’80s, it was a big deal when a frustrated satellite dish operator overrode the HBO feed for a few minutes on a Saturday night. But late last year, a saga involving a programmer whose family member’s TV set had fallen victim to ransomware shows we haven’t even scratched the surface of TV hacking.[/big]
https://twitter.com/darrencauthon/status/813096722989809665
Ransomware has a long and sordid history, though it’s relatively new to television. (But not too new.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weirdly Honest</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/weird-wally-smith-nebraska-obit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/weird-wally-smith-nebraska-obit/</guid>
      <description>[big]Located smack dab in the middle of flyover country, Weird Wally—born Wally Rex Smith—never earned the notoriety of Crazy Eddie, his East Coast contemporary on the oddball advertising front.[/big]
But while Crazy Eddie Antar’s entire electronics business was built around getting one over on the IRS and the public, Smith’s Lincoln, Nebraska used car lot was built on bluntness. He was honest—almost to a fault. And that&amp;rsquo;s why his story matters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’ll Send Him Cheesy Movies</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/mst3k-revival-joel-hodgson-creative-redo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/mst3k-revival-joel-hodgson-creative-redo/</guid>
      <description>[big]Recently, I had a reader send me a zip file full of old ideas I had for a website I worked on nearly 20 years ago. It was an unusual bit of digital archaeology, in part because I didn’t actually remember the project until after I had seen the end results. Then, it all came back to me—a revival of ideas, good and bad, the reflection that I’ve been building sites like the one I&amp;rsquo;m typing on now since before I was even in college.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re Making A Zine</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/tedium-zine-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/tedium-zine-announcement/</guid>
      <description>[big]A while back, my friend Simon Owens wrote this piece in which he compared email newsletters to zines, and used good old Tedium as an example of the form.[/big]
It makes sense to a degree—there’s a DIY ethos that comes with any self-publishing project, and with newsletters as with zines, the weirder, the better.
That thought stuck with me and kind of got into my head as a thought monster, and as I was thinking about ways to do something fresh with the Tedium concept, the zine struck me as the perfect kind of vessel to do something a little different, while still in the spirit of this thing I’m already writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What if Tedium … Had Lyrics?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/brentalfloss-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/brentalfloss-interview/</guid>
      <description>As our readers are now undoubtedly aware, there are two things I’m incredibly interested in—unique types of music and the history/technical aspects/playing the games of the original Nintendo Entertainment System (I’m also really into miniatures, FWIW). Knowing this, it was only a matter of time before I discovered someone who combined these two interests into one. Unlike U2, circa 1987, I found what I was looking for almost a decade ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why “Zombie” Lingers</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/cranberries-zombie-legacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/cranberries-zombie-legacy/</guid>
      <description>[big]It&amp;rsquo;s painful every time we lose a major rock star, especially one who still had a lot of years left in front of them, as Irish singer and Cranberries frontwoman Dolores O’Riordan did. She hadn’t even hit age 50 yet, and her career was such that her biggest successes came and went before she had hit the age of 30. “Linger” and “Zombie” were sizable hits before she had even turned 24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You’re Wearing An Antenna</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/headphones-fm-radio-antenna/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/headphones-fm-radio-antenna/</guid>
      <description>[big]As it turns out, the release of the iPhone 7 last fall likely closed the door on something the broadcast industry has long crossed its fingers for.[/big]
My piece last week on FMX, the discarded radio technology that faded from view, drew a comment from reader Conrad Kramer, who was drawn to one of the side elements, where I discussed efforts by the broadcasting industry to get FM radio functionality enabled in smartphones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a lowercase controversy</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/quinnipiac-university-lowercase-logo-controversy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/quinnipiac-university-lowercase-logo-controversy/</guid>
      <description>the thing with uppercase letters is that if they aren’t there, you start to miss them after a while. they tend to carry a certain weight about them, one that speaks to a certain authority.
(IT’S AN AUTHORITY LOST WHEN EVERY SINGLE LETTER IS UPPERCASE.)
recently, this became an issue for the students of Quinnipiac university, because their school decided to change its logo without uppercasing the u.
angry petitions were filed, and complaints on social media followed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“It&#39;s Weird That it Didn&#39;t Seem Weirder”</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/nesticle-history-extras-part-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/nesticle-history-extras-part-two/</guid>
      <description>[big]“A Bloodlust game was clearly a Bloodlust game,” Bloodlust visual artist Ethan Petty told me. “Some people loved it. Some people thought it was visual torture. I was with the second group, but hey—we had to keep creating. It was what we loved.”[/big]
Of the many fascinating things about Bloodlust Software and its emulators—NESticle in particular, but also Genecyst and Callus—was that there was a distinctive visual style that went along with them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>