<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Computer Games on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/computer-games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Computer Games on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/computer-games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall Of Voodoo</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/3dfx-history-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/3dfx-history-failure/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Today’s startup companies seem to have a certain arc to them—they get some seed funding, they launch, they draw some interest for their good idea, they keep growing, and maybe they become a part of the fabric of our lives … or a part of the fabric of a significantly larger company. Strangely, 3Dfx didn’t so much draw interest as blow the lid off of a trend that redefined how we think of video games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai&#39;s Untold Story</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/mahjong-shanghai-brodie-lockard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/mahjong-shanghai-brodie-lockard/</guid>
      <description>[big]It’s hard to track the history of mahjong solitaire, a Chinese game that came to America sometime in the 1920s, but one thing is for sure: More than 30 years ago, an electronic version of the game quietly took the computing world by storm.[/big]
Less known is the truly impressive feat that game represented. Originally built on the PLATO computing platform by Brodie Lockard in 1981, the computer game was groundbreaking both on a technical basis—the educational platform PLATO, as I wrote recently for Motherboard, inspired a lot broken ground—but also a personal one for Lockard.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>