<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Software Industry on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/software-industry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Software Industry on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 02:43:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/software-industry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Other Browser War</title>
      <link>/2018/06/22/opera-omnibar-adware-booking-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 02:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/22/opera-omnibar-adware-booking-com/</guid>
      <description>Update: Opera has claimed that this was an unintentional error and is fixing it on their end. The point about paying for browsers still stands, however, and as a result, I&amp;rsquo;ll keep this post up for posterity.
&amp;nbsp;
I find it fascinating that, of all the pieces of software we use on a daily basis, the one we literally use the most, our web browser, is one that we do not pay for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fake Elf News</title>
      <link>/2017/12/22/elf-bowling-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/22/elf-bowling-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: I know this sounds pretty crazy and dangerous, but there was once a time when we sent one another executable files via email. It was kinda like playing Russian Roulette with our operating systems, but we still did it. (No executables in this message. Promise.) And one of these executable files that was distributed over this medium that’s infamously prone to security problems is basically a goofy holiday-themed game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Painting Outside The Lines</title>
      <link>/2017/02/10/paint-shop-pro-shareware-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/02/10/paint-shop-pro-shareware-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The dream of shareware, as previously discussed, was simply this: As long as you could put a good taste of a product onto a floppy disk, you could theoretically compete with companies ten times your size. Or bigger. It leveled the playing field for distribution, and that meant even if you were building an app in your living room on your night off while eating the cheapest ramen you could find, you could still feasibly take on giant software companies that can afford to promote themselves on television.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>