<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nesticle on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/nesticle/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nesticle on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 07:43:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/nesticle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>“It&#39;s Weird That it Didn&#39;t Seem Weirder”</title>
      <link>/2017/05/04/nesticle-history-extras-part-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 07:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/04/nesticle-history-extras-part-two/</guid>
      <description>“A Bloodlust game was clearly a Bloodlust game,” Bloodlust visual artist Ethan Petty told me. “Some people loved it. Some people thought it was visual torture. I was with the second group, but hey—we had to keep creating. It was what we loved.”  Of the many fascinating things about Bloodlust Software and its emulators—NESticle in particular, but also Genecyst and Callus—was that there was a distinctive visual style that went along with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Extra Serving</title>
      <link>/2017/05/02/nesticle-history-extras-part-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 06:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/02/nesticle-history-extras-part-one/</guid>
      <description>What a day! My article on Vice&amp;rsquo;s Motherboard this week about the history of NESticle—the Nintendo Entertainment System emulator whose early success paved the way for people to play vintage games on their computers whenever they want—took a while to get past the finish line, and came only after I gave the piece a haircut.  To augment the story, I’m gonna spend the next couple of Daily Tedium pieces highlighting things I hoped to get into the original piece but were trimmed out because the piece was getting a bit lengthy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>