<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Google on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/google/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Google on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 07:42:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/google/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Googling</title>
      <link>/2018/10/03/google-20th-anniversary-culture-importance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 07:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/03/google-20th-anniversary-culture-importance/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Love, hate, or criticize them, Google is just a part of life these days. (They’re marginally less evil than Facebook, which helps.) Silicon Valley’s algorithmic gift to the world is now two decades old, having celebrated its 20th birthday with a doodle just last week, one that came a few weeks after its actual birthday—the September 4, 1998 incorporation of the company. It’s strange to consider that a company so fundamental to our world is still so relatively young.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google’s Zombie</title>
      <link>/2017/11/15/google-feedburner-rss-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/15/google-feedburner-rss-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Google may be the internet’s greatest murderer of ideas. Between its numerous acquihires, its aggressive approach to launching (and discarding) moonshots, and its tendency to build impressive products only to kill them months later, Google may be the greatest example of a cold-blooded idea killer in history. But one product under the search giant’s lineup strikes my fancy in particular, because Google never killed it, even though everyone thought it would.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search By Text</title>
      <link>/2017/08/01/google-sms-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 05:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/01/google-sms-history/</guid>
      <description>Back in college, some friends and I found ourselves dealing with a pre-mobile Internet problem. After engaging in activity that is now legal for recreational use in four states, we desperately needed to order pizza. No one knew the number for Domino’s or any other place from memory. And we weren’t immediately near a computer with internet access. Through the disappointment and haze, my friend suddenly remembered, &amp;ldquo;Hey, we can text Google!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Windex Problem</title>
      <link>/2017/07/18/information-literacy-students-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 03:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/18/information-literacy-students-problem/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve been a longtime reader of Tedium, you’ve probably noticed that my byline shows up most of the time. Maybe 80 to 90 percent of the time.  In part, this is because this is my project, and I limit the number of things we publish every month. Also in part, it&amp;rsquo;s because I feel uncomfortable with having writers work for me for free. (The one person I do have writing outside pieces, Andrew Egan, has actually been getting paid for them!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down With Snippet View</title>
      <link>/2017/06/27/google-books-snippet-view-archival/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 03:29:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/27/google-books-snippet-view-archival/</guid>
      <description>You may or may not have noticed this, but Tedium relies pretty heavily on archival content to exist. This newsletter and publication is not just about offering up weird facts: It&amp;rsquo;s often about introducing facts that have otherwise been forgotten about by the public at large.  Sometimes, this takes me in some interesting directions. An example I regularly cite is my piece on lemon juice squeeze bottles. It was the rare piece I had the chance to mostly write ahead of time, and while there were some incredibly useful starting points on the issue from the Beach Packaging Design, I find it important that, even if an existing resource like this offers a starting point, I spend time doing some digging of my own.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>