<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Frozen Foods on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/frozen-foods/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Frozen Foods on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 07:47:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/frozen-foods/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Not Delivery, It’s …</title>
      <link>/2018/04/18/frozen-pizza-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 07:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/18/frozen-pizza-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Have you heard the good news? Frozen food is back, baby! After years on the sidelines, Healthy Choice is seen as a healthy choice again; people looking to put on a home banquet are looking towards Banquet; hungry men are choosing Hungry Man. The future is frozen, and if you’re not warming up to cold foods, you’re not cool. With tonight’s Tedium, I’d like to focus on one specific kind of food put on ice, the frozen pizza, and why it’s become an icon of prepared American food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Cream Fakery</title>
      <link>/2017/01/16/breyers-frozen-dairy-dessert-not-ice-cream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 22:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/16/breyers-frozen-dairy-dessert-not-ice-cream/</guid>
      <description>A couple of months ago, I was scooping myself a bowl of ice cream, when I discovered something interesting and a little disturbing: Nowhere on the label did the ice cream describe itself as “ice cream.”  The label was for Breyers, a brand that has a long, lengthy history in the ice cream manufacturing game and a pledge to use “high quality ingredients.” But this pledge had been put into doubt by the fact that Breyers couldn’t describe what it was selling as ice cream, but rather “frozen dairy dessert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hot Pocket Diaspora</title>
      <link>/2016/05/27/hot-pocket-history-iran-jewish-diaspora/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 07:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/05/27/hot-pocket-history-iran-jewish-diaspora/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Laugh all you want, but Hot Pockets are the ultimate modern food. Incredibly easy to eat and simple to cook, they cleverly were designed to be easy to microwave and completely, utterly portable. Less known about the Hot Pocket, however, is its origins, which are the product of a duo of Iranian-born Jewish immigrants who arguably popularized the concept of microwavable frozen meals. Jim Gaffigan hates these things, but we admit something of a respect for them as a bottom-up success story (that just happens to be incredibly unhealthy).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>