<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prince on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/prince/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Prince on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 07:46:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/prince/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I’ll Do Something Innovative When I Die</title>
      <link>/2017/10/27/funeral-technology-innovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/27/funeral-technology-innovation/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Death is a weird thing. Everyone does it eventually (unless they’re immortal), and we don’t always have control over when it happens. (If you’re reading this right now, you’ve confirmed that I did not die in the production of this issue.) But the problem is that death is a very sensitive thing, it’s loaded with emotions, it’s expensive, and it’s hard to get right. Perhaps that’s why “death” and “innovation” don’t tend to be so closely associated with one another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purple Copyright Eater</title>
      <link>/2016/04/22/prince-troubled-relationship-with-copyright/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 04:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/04/22/prince-troubled-relationship-with-copyright/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In losing Prince Rogers Nelson, we&amp;rsquo;re losing a lot more than a idiosyncratic pop star who defined an entire New Power Generation. We&amp;rsquo;re losing the last link between our current remix-heavy culture (which, let&amp;rsquo;s face it, this newsletter wouldn&amp;rsquo;t exist without) and an era when ownership of creative work was treated as an end-all-be-all. Here was a guy who started the internet era sporting a name that literally could not be searched, who forced lawsuits over barely-noticeable renditions of his songs in YouTube clips, and who made a lot of creative stuff that nobody will likely ever see.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>