<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dog Models on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/dog-models/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dog Models on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 07:39:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/dog-models/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Super (Small) Models</title>
      <link>/2018/09/28/scale-model-hobby-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 07:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/09/28/scale-model-hobby-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey all, Ernie here with a piece from resident enthusiast David Buck, who is enthused about building things at small sizes. Read on to see his scale-model insights.
Today in Tedium: From classic cars, aircraft and starships to movie vehicles and beyond, scale modeling has long been a popular hobby in the United States. As a child, I participated in several 4-H courses based on model craft and I even won first prize for one of mine at the county fair one year for a Revell snap-together Jeep I built for the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I See This Dog Everywhere</title>
      <link>/2018/01/30/chico-stock-photo-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/30/chico-stock-photo-dog/</guid>
      <description>If there’s a fact you probably don’t know about me yet but should, it’s this: I friggin’ love stock photos. Stock photos are air in my life, a way to express emotion vicariously through someone else’s ideas, a way to express a basic idea with just a few pictures, and a way to simply add elements to any photoillustration idea that comes to mind.  And to me, the greatest stock photo resource ever created is a wonderful dog named Chico.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>