<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Canada on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/canada/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Canada on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/canada/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Behind By A Century</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/the-tragically-hip-appreciation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/the-tragically-hip-appreciation/</guid>
      <description>[big]My wife, for years, has had this tendency of deciding to watch some shows, usually dramas, only after their run has completed, which I’m sure that TV studios friggin’ love. Sometimes, though, there’s so much out there that it’s just functionally easier to tackle a body of work like Weeds in full, over the span of a week, rather than as a number of disparate, easily-forgotten pieces.[/big]
Music, which has always been more of my forte, often doesn’t have this problem—a song is usually self-contained in a theme, and an album usually stands on its own as a complete thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Floating Fast Food</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/mcbarge-vancouver-floating-fast-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/mcbarge-vancouver-floating-fast-food/</guid>
      <description>[big]The other night, I took a bit of a swipe at McDonald’s for its poor track record in the Icelandic market. Ray Kroc and company, I apologize and admit that your sausage biscuits give me modest joy. After I write this piece, I may be forced to apologize again.[/big]
That’s because I’m about to bring up a bad memory for the fast-food giant.
In the late ‘80s, the World’s Fair was still a fairly Big Deal in North America, and Vancouver played host to one of the most notable World Expo galas, Expo ’86.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximum Cargo</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/combi-planes-cargo-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/combi-planes-cargo-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Earlier this year, when the CEO of United Airlines was put in front of a Senate panel and asked to defend his company’s notably shoddy treatment of a passenger, Sen. Bill Nelson (D-FL) described his interactions with air passengers as such: “[They] feel like they’re being treated as self-loading cargo rather than as valued consumers.&amp;rdquo; That’s an interesting comparison point. If an airline isn’t shipping passengers from one side of the country or world to another, it’s shipping cargo that may be inanimate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Scrolling Orb</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/trackball-input-device-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/trackball-input-device-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Ever find yourself in a bar with a single arcade machine, and the machine is inevitably not targeting gamers? Like, rather than, say, a fighting game or something iconic like NBA Jam or even Donkey Kong, it’s either a variation of Big Buck Hunter, a bowling game like Silver Strike Bowling, or a golf game like Golden Tee. These games, of course, aim for a wide audience, quite literally in the case of Big Buck Hunter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>