<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R. Stevie Moore on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/r.-stevie-moore/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R. Stevie Moore on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 04:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/r.-stevie-moore/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WebTV’s Greatest Celebrity User</title>
      <link>/2018/05/16/r-stevie-moore-webtv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/16/r-stevie-moore-webtv/</guid>
      <description>R. Stevie Moore is an extraordinary archivist of his own material. Recently, the online short film series Great Big Story released a superb mini documentary about Stevie and on April 6, 2018, R. Stevie Moore was featured on the front page of Wikipedia.  The page asked “Did you know R. Stevie Moore pioneered modern indie rock, earning him the sobriquet ‘the godfather of home recording?’”
Yes, Wikipedia. I believe we already knew that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moore R. Stevie Moore</title>
      <link>/2017/08/31/r-stevie-moore-starting-points/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 05:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/31/r-stevie-moore-starting-points/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: This is a companion piece to yesterday&amp;rsquo;s newsletter issue on R. Stevie Moore, by David Buck. Read that first, then come back here.
&amp;nbsp;
R. Stevie Moore&amp;rsquo;s vast body of work may intimidate some and may delight others. I&amp;rsquo;ve taken the liberty of curating a list of my top R. Stevie Moore songs that will entertain, amuse and otherwise. They also serve as a great introduction to the man and his work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Man With 400 Albums</title>
      <link>/2017/08/30/r-stevie-moore-outsider-music-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 06:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/30/r-stevie-moore-outsider-music-history/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Hey all, Ernie from Tedium here! So I&amp;rsquo;m happy to introduce David Buck, a first-time writer for the newsletter who&amp;rsquo;s a massive fan of a guy you&amp;rsquo;re probably not even aware of. He makes me excited about the guy, to be honest. Read on—tonight&amp;rsquo;s piece is a total treat. And be sure to check out his list for newbies!
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: Many great artists exist outside the mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>