<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food History on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/food-history/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food History on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 07:47:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/food-history/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Not Delivery, It’s …</title>
      <link>/2018/04/18/frozen-pizza-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 07:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/18/frozen-pizza-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Have you heard the good news? Frozen food is back, baby! After years on the sidelines, Healthy Choice is seen as a healthy choice again; people looking to put on a home banquet are looking towards Banquet; hungry men are choosing Hungry Man. The future is frozen, and if you’re not warming up to cold foods, you’re not cool. With tonight’s Tedium, I’d like to focus on one specific kind of food put on ice, the frozen pizza, and why it’s become an icon of prepared American food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Nuts for Beer Nuts</title>
      <link>/2018/01/18/beer-nuts-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 04:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/18/beer-nuts-history/</guid>
      <description>If you’re a certain age or tend to watch TV shows from a certain time, you might remember the ubiquity of the humble beer nut. Almost any sitcom in the ’80s or early ’90s that involves a bar will mention beer nuts at some point. Here’s Norm Peterson using beer nuts in a clunky analogy about women:  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=weBbZ11d5LM
And of course, there are the mandatory Simpsons references, such as when Homer buys “Kwik-E-Mart No Name Brand Beer Nuts” or when a fake beer nuts can is spring loaded with snakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What The Hellmann</title>
      <link>/2017/12/15/condiment-sauces-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 09:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/15/condiment-sauces-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: There have been many instances in my life that I’ve been told I’m a sauce obsessive. Maybe I pour a little too much A1 on a steak, a too-aggressive dip of a fry into a side of ranch dressing, a little too much salsa on the side of an omelet. I’m sure if I ran into Gordon Ramsay somewhere and he saw how much sauce I used, he would scold me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smashing Potatoes</title>
      <link>/2017/11/22/mashed-potato-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 09:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/22/mashed-potato-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: If one was forced by the twisting of the arm to choose one item to get rid of on their Thanksgiving plate on Thursday, some people might choose turkey (mostly the vegetarians), and some others might choose cranberries (which aren’t hip anymore), but I promise you nobody—and I mean nobody—would choose the mashed potatoes. They are the glue of our thanksgiving meal, the most essential element, the only thing that must be served in some form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Internet of Food</title>
      <link>/2017/04/07/internet-early-food-delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 07:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/04/07/internet-early-food-delivery/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: You know something you can’t get through the internet’s wires, at least not on its own? Food. We’ve been working on it for years, but no, we’re not at the point where we can deliver nourishment directly via the series of tubes. But food has always been something of a means to an end—a way of driving the internet forward, making it something people would actually like to use.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>