<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/windows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Windows on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 07:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/windows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Double Trouble</title>
      <link>/2018/09/05/disk-compression-stacker-doublespace-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 07:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/09/05/disk-compression-stacker-doublespace-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: As anyone who has ever owned a smartphone with the minimum amount of flash storage knows, space runs out fast, and once you realize you need more than you’ve allocated yourself, it’s way too late. In computing, this is a story that goes back decades, to a time when giant platters walked (OK, rolled) the Earth. But while running out of storage space on a 16-gig iPhone is annoying, it’s at least reasonable; you can put stuff on the cloud, and if the space drives you nuts, you can always upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Window Dressing</title>
      <link>/2018/05/23/windows-fake-osx-macos-interface-skins-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 07:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/23/windows-fake-osx-macos-interface-skins-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: There’s something about the macOS operating system that kind of drives people wild. (Heck, even the original Mac OS has its strong partisans.) In the 17 years since Apple first launched the first iteration of the operating system based on its Darwin Unix variant, something fairly curious started to happen: People without Macs suddenly wanted the operating system, if not the hardware it ran on. This phenomenon is somewhat common today—I personally just set up a Hackintosh of my own recently—but I’d like to highlight a different kind of “Hackintosh,” the kind that played dress-up with Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Window Into Windex</title>
      <link>/2017/06/14/windex-glass-cleaning-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 07:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/14/windex-glass-cleaning-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: For centuries, the average home had windows, but not necessarily glass covering those windows—in part, because glass was really expensive at first, and the flat pane variety that we’re used to didn’t exist at first. But as glass evolved as part of the modern home, it suddenly became important to keep those panes of glass clean. And that meant there was an opportunity for a manufacturer to come about and make it easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Painting Outside The Lines</title>
      <link>/2017/02/10/paint-shop-pro-shareware-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/02/10/paint-shop-pro-shareware-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The dream of shareware, as previously discussed, was simply this: As long as you could put a good taste of a product onto a floppy disk, you could theoretically compete with companies ten times your size. Or bigger. It leveled the playing field for distribution, and that meant even if you were building an app in your living room on your night off while eating the cheapest ramen you could find, you could still feasibly take on giant software companies that can afford to promote themselves on television.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons From The Video Professor</title>
      <link>/2016/11/16/video-professor-infomercial-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 08:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/11/16/video-professor-infomercial-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Home computers and infomercials were always meant to go together. Here were these devices, arguably the most complex products ever to enter homes in Middle America, and they needed a lot of explaining at first. (Not complicated explanations, mind you. Simple ones.) Enter Video Professor. For two decades, John Scherer made millions by selling educational products to the public, mostly through late-night infomercials and on home-shopping networks like QVC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Other Windows</title>
      <link>/2016/04/29/geoworks-windows-3-1-competitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/04/29/geoworks-windows-3-1-competitor/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Back in the early &amp;lsquo;90s, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a sure thing that Microsoft Windows was going to take over the market, even though they had a clear lead over many of their competitors, thanks to MS-DOS. In fact, one of the iconic GUI-based experiences of the era, AOL, hedged its bets for a while, creating and maintaining a DOS version of its iconic pseudo-internet software using an GUI platform few were familiar with: GeoWorks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>