<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Computer Superstores on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/computer-superstores/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Computer Superstores on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 07:54:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/computer-superstores/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Booting Up The Cash Register</title>
      <link>/2017/08/04/early-computer-retailers-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 07:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/04/early-computer-retailers-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The modern computer store, as I&amp;rsquo;ve argued in the past, is a bit of a mess. It’s all about the hard sell (in a gigantic box) at the cost of any personality whatsoever. It was so bad that Apple (and later, Microsoft) had to create its own self-branded stores to ensure their products were seen in the proper light. This is kind of painful, of course, because personal computers were really the domain of the hobbyist at first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Were Selling Computers All Wrong</title>
      <link>/2016/10/12/big-box-retail-computers-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 07:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/10/12/big-box-retail-computers-problems/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The big-box technology store isn&amp;rsquo;t dead yet—and in the case of Best Buy, it&amp;rsquo;s actually doing pretty well, beating financial estimates by a country mile. But as a whole, the concept of the sprawling electronics chain is far from its peak. In fact, it&amp;rsquo;s sort of another shade of the office-supply store. Despite that, investors keep trying to revive this idea. Right now, an investor named Ronny Shmoel is trying to bring Circuit City back to life as a physical presence, roughly seven years after the brand was mothballed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>