<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Radio Technology on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/radio-technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Radio Technology on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/radio-technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Around the World</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/le-globe-radiooooo-online-radio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/le-globe-radiooooo-online-radio/</guid>
      <description>[big]When you find an outlet that creates a sense of adventure around something as pedestrian and overexposed as online music, you know it’s worth a bookmark.[/big]
The French website Radiooooo, an online time machine that combines a Mercator projection of the globe with a radio, feels like the modern version of the shortwave radio, in some ways—except with the added dimension of time.
In a New Yorker piece last year, founder Benjamin Moreau recalled that he had the idea based on an experience of listening to modern music in his 1966 Renault Caravelle, and finding the result fully unappealing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back To The Shack</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/radio-shack-bankruptcy-auction-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/radio-shack-bankruptcy-auction-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: For many reasons, largely related to a shifting business model incompatible with modern tech needs, a whole generation of people saw RadioShack as less a store for tinkerers and more a place to buy commodity tech products. It was a business model that fell out of sync with the enthusiast community that once championed its products, and the twice-bankrupt RadioShack has been paying the price for that pivot ever since.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Copy?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/walkie-talkie-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/walkie-talkie-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: It seems so quaint now, but there was a time when the walkie-talkie was the coolest possible toy you could own (barring, perhaps, Power Wheels). But the invention of the walkie-talkie, which is often used by consumers as either a fun tool or a simple communications device, is a great reminder that this technology used to be so much more fundamental for both businesses and the military.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Touch That Dial</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/radio-technology-upgrades-fmx-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/radio-technology-upgrades-fmx-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Recently, the Norwegian government—which has helped the country become first-movers on the electric car front—decided that it wanted to be ahead of another kind of curve. It was a curve that not everyone was ready for, however. Norway recently decided to drop FM radio, in favor of a modern equivalent, digital audio broadcasting (DAB). This early move comes with a lot of risks, as does every other attempt to mess with the technology that drives the airwaves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Invisible Puzzle</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/wireless-spectrum-allocation-challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/wireless-spectrum-allocation-challenges/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Barring our constant debates on net neutrality, one of the places where the Federal Communications Commission has the largest footprint is with our wireless spectrum. It’s a spectrum that has to serve many minders, and there are constant complaints about the spectrum being crowded. But those complaints, despite feeling modern and up-to-date, are far from new—we’ve been dealing with them pretty much ever since there was spectrum regulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You’re Wearing An Antenna</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/headphones-fm-radio-antenna/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/headphones-fm-radio-antenna/</guid>
      <description>[big]As it turns out, the release of the iPhone 7 last fall likely closed the door on something the broadcast industry has long crossed its fingers for.[/big]
My piece last week on FMX, the discarded radio technology that faded from view, drew a comment from reader Conrad Kramer, who was drawn to one of the side elements, where I discussed efforts by the broadcasting industry to get FM radio functionality enabled in smartphones.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>