<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christmas on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/christmas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Christmas on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/christmas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas In Clay</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/claymation-christmas-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/claymation-christmas-celebration/</guid>
      <description>[big]The strange thing about holiday classics, whether TV or film, is the way that they get drilled into the canon of nostalgia, a mush of themed entertainment along the lines of A Charlie Brown Christmas or A Christmas Story. These pieces of entertainment get repeated in part because we build memories around them. I wrote a piece about this phenomenon a couple of years ago.[/big]
But what happens if you create a piece of art that seems destined for the Christmas nostalgia ringer, and … for whatever reason, it just doesn’t happen?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas on Repeat</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/christmas-nostalgia-psychology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/christmas-nostalgia-psychology/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: This is a special Wednesday morning issue, in an effort to get ahead of your holiday travel. We&amp;rsquo;ll be back to our normal Tuesday/Thursday schedule next week.
[big]Today in Tedium: Every year, I have a tradition that I&amp;rsquo;ve followed pretty religiously for more than a decade. Whether in its original form or in its Mystery Science Theater 3000 send-up, I&amp;rsquo;ll watch the junk-culture film Santa Claus Conquers the Martians, despite knowing that the movie is perhaps one of the worst of all time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gifts For People You Don’t Like</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/tedium-gift-guide-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/tedium-gift-guide-2016/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: You’ve already checked off the people you know and love. Maybe even the people you know and tolerate. But what about gifts for folks you have a distaste for? That’s where our end-of-season gift guide comes into play. It’s full of obscure stuff and absolute dreck that you may or may not care for. But it’s perfect for breaking off weak friendships, telling a long-lost relative that they probably shouldn’t have returned, or for lowering someone’s overall standard for living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gifts For Total Strangers</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/tedium-2017-gift-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/tedium-2017-gift-guide/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: We’re nearing the part of the holiday shopping season when it’s do or die time. If you didn’t do something already, you’re likely scrambling to figure out a Plan B, or maybe even a Plan Q. The gift, no matter the quality, needs to show up by, like, Friday to count as a decent gift for Christmas. Maybe you can swing Saturday—if UPS is willing to swing it for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stocking Stinkers: A Tedium Gift Guide</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/stocking-stinkers-tedium-gift-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/stocking-stinkers-tedium-gift-guide/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Tedium is publishing on an different schedule this week—Monday and Wednesday mornings rather than Tuesday and Thursday evenings—so as to get in your inbox before the holiday rush of out-of-office replies and connecting flights.
[big]Today in Tedium: If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this and still in need of gift ideas for your loved ones, it&amp;rsquo;s already too late. (Did you know that Christmas is on Friday?!) You will find nothing good in your inbox or elsewhere that will save you at this point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweating the Ugly Truth</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/ugly-christmas-sweater-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/ugly-christmas-sweater-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey all, Ernie here with another issue of Tedium by Andrew Egan. Last time he showed up on Tedium, he broke down NYC&amp;rsquo;s now-repealed dancing ban, and before that, he told us about professional cornhole. Now, he&amp;rsquo;s talking sweaters.
[big]Today in Tedium: Some simple inventions took a surprising amount of time to create. Case in point: The can opener was invented 45 years after the can. Reasons for these delays tended to result from technological gaps rather than a lack of Ingenuity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>