<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Retro on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/retro/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Retro on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/retro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>8-Bit Archaeology</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/8-bit-archaeology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/8-bit-archaeology/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox][big]
Today in Tedium: Here&amp;rsquo;s something you probably don&amp;rsquo;t know about me. For a couple years in the late-&amp;lsquo;90s and early 2000s, I got my sea legs in writing from a little site called Zophar&amp;rsquo;s Domain, a console emulation enthusiast site. At the time, ZD held a kind of legendary status among retro gamers, and though it&amp;rsquo;s aged some, it&amp;rsquo;s still around. (Here&amp;rsquo;s what it looked like when I was there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Warped Mindset</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/nintendo-times-warp-zone-nes-coverage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/nintendo-times-warp-zone-nes-coverage/</guid>
      <description>[big]What if we reported on the past like it was happening in the present day—not reflecting on it nostalgically like I do at Tedium, but literally trying to cover the past as if you had no knowledge of the future?[/big]
It sounds like an odd thought exercise, but in reality, it’s a whole lot of fun, based on the website Nintendo Times. Since 2015, the writer and blogger Craig Majaski, who cut his teeth at the long-running gaming site Gaming Age, has been editing and putting together a site in which 30-year-old discussions and interviews about the early days of the Nintendo Entertainment System are published as if they’re happening in real time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COBOLed Together</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/cobol-programmers-cobol-cowboys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/cobol-programmers-cobol-cowboys/</guid>
      <description>[big]If you’re a regular reader of Y Combinator’s excellent mini-Reddit aggregator Hacker News (as I am), you start to see some trends arise. Programming languages and frameworks become incredibly popular (Ruby on Rails! Django! Node! Go!), but then start to lose their luster over time as programmers inevitably move onto the next coding innovation.[/big]
But the thing is, programming frameworks didn’t used to be this trendy, and some of the really old ones are becoming highly-sought-after in certain sectors because they’re becoming very uncommon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Command Line</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/dos-nostalgia-squirrel-monkey-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/dos-nostalgia-squirrel-monkey-interview/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey all, Ernie here with a fresh piece from David Buck, who has moved away from his NES for a while to tell you all about how awesome DOS is as a creative medium. Yeah, DOS.
[big]Today in Tedium: From the early 90s, up until 2005 or so, I did much of my computer gaming on an American Megatrends IBM PC, running MS-DOS and Windows 3.11. I even got online once using Netscape Communicator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall Of Voodoo</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/3dfx-history-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/3dfx-history-failure/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Today’s startup companies seem to have a certain arc to them—they get some seed funding, they launch, they draw some interest for their good idea, they keep growing, and maybe they become a part of the fabric of our lives … or a part of the fabric of a significantly larger company. Strangely, 3Dfx didn’t so much draw interest as blow the lid off of a trend that redefined how we think of video games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s New To You</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/funcoland-history-used-video-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/funcoland-history-used-video-games/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: In an era when digital storage is basically unlimited and space is running out by the second, there’s still a basic charm to physical objects that we’ve yet to really lose. Video games are a great example of this. Despite the fact that you can literally download any game under the sun and play it instantly, there is a quite healthy business online and elsewhere for physical product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Still Rocks</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/nintendo-nes-chiptune-music-scene/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/nintendo-nes-chiptune-music-scene/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey all, Ernie here with another piece from David Buck, who&amp;rsquo;s currently in the midst of following his Nintendo muse. Feel free to follow along with him!
[big]Today in Tedium: Gamers of a certain age may remember the opening notes of Super Mario Bros as well—or perhaps better than—any other song from their childhoods. As the pack-in title for the original Nintendo Entertainment System, the game was likely the first exposure to video games many of us had outside of arcades and Atari.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Persistence</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/sgi-collector-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/sgi-collector-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey all, Ernie here with a recent piece of mine that also showed up in Motherboard. In case you haven&amp;rsquo;t read it yet, it&amp;rsquo;s a good one and highlights both SGI and the the excellent community IRIX.cc. Read on, and hope you dig!
[big]Today in Tedium: Recently, I was faced with an unusual question about a piece of hardware that very few people have ever used. The question: What makes a giant workstation, one that once cost as much as a house when it was first produced in the early ‘90s and makes as much noise as a vacuum, so appealing to a 16-year-old?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super FX Turbo Mode</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/star-fox-super-fx-overclocking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/star-fox-super-fx-overclocking/</guid>
      <description>[big]I’m going to come right out and say it: I want a Super NES Classic. I wanted an NES Classic, but that sold out too quickly and the variations on the market cost way too much money, so I have my finger on the trigger for potential pre-orders of the new device, expected to hit this week. I, like most of my other fellow retro geeks, can at least embrace the fact that we still have as much of a shot at getting these mini-consoles right now as we did Pearl Jam tickets circa 1994.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV’s Hidden Math</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/tv-programming-quirks-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/tv-programming-quirks-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: It’s often said about the current era of television that it’s an embarrassment of riches, one of the best eras of television of all time, in part because the floodgates have bumped up the quality quotient. Netflix creates so much stuff (some great, much average) that we’re unaware of nearly all of it! It’s weird to think about, but both cable TV and local syndication had a similar effect on television in the ’80s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tales Of The Interwebs</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/early-internet-history-tales/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/early-internet-history-tales/</guid>
      <description>[big]
Today in Tedium: Last week, one of the men who created the internet as we know it sounded the alarms on its future. Vinton Cerf, a Google executive and one of the architects of ARPANET, noted that decades of files could be lost to history, with no way to access the documents, due to lacking digital preservation efforts. “When you think about the quantity of documentation from our daily lives that is captured in digital form, like our interactions by email, people’s tweets, and all of the world wide web, it’s clear that we stand to lose an awful lot of our history,” he said, according to The Guardian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ballad of Yo! Noid</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/video-games-advertising-mascots-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/video-games-advertising-mascots-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey guys, Ernie here with a piece from the Tedium archives about Madison Avenue’s infiltration of classic video games, which is legitimately a thing that happened.
[big]Today in Tedium: Here&amp;rsquo;s a challenge for you: Take your favorite video game of the &amp;lsquo;90s and don&amp;rsquo;t think about it in terms of the quality of the game, its graphical quality, or its replayability—especially if it&amp;rsquo;s a game based on an existing license.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ballad of Yo! Noid</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/video-games-advertising-mascots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/video-games-advertising-mascots/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Here&amp;rsquo;s a challenge for you: Take your favorite video game of the &amp;lsquo;90s and don&amp;rsquo;t think about it in terms of the quality of the game, its graphical quality, or its replayability—especially if it&amp;rsquo;s a game based on an existing license. Instead, think of that game in terms of it merely being a vessel to market another product: say, a movie like Terminator 2, a toy like a Barbie doll, or a musical act like Aerosmith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The History of Internet Explorer Hatred</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/the-history-of-internet-explorer-hatred/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/the-history-of-internet-explorer-hatred/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Your browser says a lot about you. It highlights your socioeconomic class, your knowledge of computing, your inherent biases, and even the likelihood that you’re a failure at just about everything. For many people, using Internet Explorer was a sign that your relative or co-worker didn’t “get it,” and their resistance to changing browsers was a sign that they never would. Developers, without knowing your name or your circumstances, would curse you under your breath, because your clicking on their website made their job harder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Keys To Success</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/video-games-keyboards-intellivision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/video-games-keyboards-intellivision/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Of all the reasons for the video game crash of 1983, perhaps the most unappreciated might be the fact that computers were finally starting to gain a place in many households—and they could do a lot more than play games. (Jack Tramiel knew how to price a computer.) Game console manufacturers understood this ahead of time—in fact, they seemed to design their entire business models around the idea that the machines could eventually be upgraded to full-fledged computers, or at least into something more useful than what was seen as a toy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lost (And Found) Levels</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/hidden-content-video-games-cutting-room-floor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/hidden-content-video-games-cutting-room-floor/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: It took a while for us to culturally admit it, but video games are a form of art on the level of many films—and that means that game developers are very much auteurs in the way that film directors are. (Or, depending on the game, schlockmeisters.) But as anyone who has ever used a Game Genie could tell you, there are things that developers don&amp;rsquo;t want you to see, at a basic level far removed from a mere easter egg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Many Lives of Packard Bell</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/packard-bell-multiple-brand-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/packard-bell-multiple-brand-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Let’s go back in time about 20 years, to two days after Christmas, 1996. On this day, as I was becoming accustomed to Bush’s second album, millions of families around the United States were unpacking and setting up their first home computers. For those who skipped the Commodore and Apple II eras, who didn’t have a Videotex installed in their televisions, and had no idea who Commander Keen even was, this was the moment in time when they joined the internet revolution, brandishing their their AOL or Hotmail addresses for all the world to see.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>