<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Design on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CMYK All The Way</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/color-printing-lithography-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/color-printing-lithography-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: In the 1990s, after much delay, the newspaper industry’s largest and most prominent newspapers finally started printing most of their pages in color on a regular basis. It was a much delayed phenomenon, driven less by a lack of technology and more by a mixture of cost and tradition. In 1993, The New York Times printed its first page in color, far later than most of the rest of the newspaper industry, and the only other big holdouts at that point were The Wall Street Journal and The Washington Post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outside-the-Bottle Thinking</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/bottle-design-outside-the-bottle-thinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/bottle-design-outside-the-bottle-thinking/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: It may be the most famous hard-to-read bottle in history. For generations, Dr. Bronner&amp;rsquo;s 18-in-1 Pure Castile Soap has become an essential tool for many looking to stay clean without the extra chemicals they throw into more main-line soaps. But all the benefits that come with the soap (it&amp;rsquo;s highly concentrated, it&amp;rsquo;s effective at getting you clean) are joined by Emanuel Bronner&amp;rsquo;s unusual opinions about just about everything—particularly his unique take on religion called the &amp;ldquo;Moral ABC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toilet Duck Dynasty</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/toilet-duck-design-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/toilet-duck-design-history/</guid>
      <description>[big]It’s not easy to come up with a product that’s built around a completely, utterly unique design. Especially involving a topic as unflattering as cleaning a toilet.[/big]
But in the early 1980s, a man named Walter Düring had such a moment. The Swiss man’s company, Düring AG, had made a name for itself with the concept of decalcification, based on a formula his mother, Maria, came up with. But it was in the early 1980s that the firm had come up with something truly successful on a mainstream stage: A uniquely shaped nozzle that could spray decalcifiers into obscure crevices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When It Rains, It Pours</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/umbrella-patents-innovation-challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/umbrella-patents-innovation-challenges/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Umbrellas are a good way to protect your head in case of inclement weather. Problem is, they’re not a perfect way. And that is made obvious by the fact that you’re sometimes hit by at least a little of the wet stuff even after you use such a device. If it gets windy (or even if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t), their structural integrity breaks down easily, exposing users to rain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Code Is Junky</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/microsoft-frontpage-history-web-design-wysiwyg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/microsoft-frontpage-history-web-design-wysiwyg/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: As I’ve covered a few times in the past, the hard part about any budding technology—whether it’s delivering packages, driving down interstate highways, or beaming satellite signals to homes around the country—is the infrastructure, how easy that infrastructure is to use. The internet is obviously a pretty key example of this issue in action, with products like WebTV and CompuServe imagining a specific direction for reading content online.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>