<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Creativity on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/creativity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Creativity on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/creativity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Coat of Paint</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/anthony-dortch-artist-stroke-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/anthony-dortch-artist-stroke-recovery/</guid>
      <description>[big]Last year, Anthony Dortch suffered a major personal setback—surviving a stroke at a young age.[/big]
This health struggle threatened to stop Dortch, a Washington, D.C.-based artist, from following his muse, a muse that he’s followed for years with a long-term creative project that’s taken on many layers. Quite literally, in fact.
See, Dortch’s art literally involves painting people to and making them, effectively, into comic book characters—each in different colors to represent different walks of life, with elements of his storytelling highlighting issues of race, gender and sexuality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In front of the music</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/worst-album-covers-analyzed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/worst-album-covers-analyzed/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Nearly as long as there has been the internet, there have been lists of terrible album covers—many of which predate the internet and are looked at using modern standards for humor and kitsch. But the problem with these images is that there&amp;rsquo;s often no story behind them, because they&amp;rsquo;re often not shared with any information to speak of. They&amp;rsquo;re historic memes, but they never seem to have any attached history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Livin&#39; on the Edge</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/art-decency-shocking-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/art-decency-shocking-content/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: That sound you hear is Tipper Gore&amp;rsquo;s eyes bulging out. On June 1, a new video game called Hatred aims for the absolute edge of decency and taste, with a plot line that essentially involves killing innocent people en masse for no good reason other than to push forth the destruction of society. &amp;ldquo;We say ‘yes, it is a game about killing people’ and the only reason of the antagonist doing that sick stuff is his deep-rooted hatred,&amp;ldquo; its makers state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Air of Superiority</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/air-conditioning-architecture-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/air-conditioning-architecture-problems/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: The 1902 invention of air conditioning has long been hailed as one of the most important inventions of the 20th century, one that has forever changed the way we live. But as we hit an era when robots become more human than ever and try to steal our jobs, I find myself wondering—what can we learn from the additional freedom that air conditioning gave us? Sure, it improved our society by making temperature something that we can control, but what about the problems that came with this cool breeze?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vulcan creativity</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/leonard-nimoy-vulcan-creativity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/leonard-nimoy-vulcan-creativity/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox] [big]Today in Tedium: William Shatner got all the weirdo pop attention back in the 1960s, but his _Star Trek_ co-star deserved just as much of it—if not more. The just-departed Leonard Nimoy (God rest his half-Vulcan soul) recorded a number of pop albums in the 1960s, including his own renditions of &amp;ldquo;I Walk the Line&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Proud Mary.&amp;rdquo; But the career highlight to top them all was a bizarro pop tune about a fantasy character who sported ears nearly as pointy as Spock&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>