<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gift Guide on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/gift-guide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gift Guide on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 09:16:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/gift-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gifts For Total Strangers</title>
      <link>/2017/12/20/tedium-2017-gift-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 09:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/20/tedium-2017-gift-guide/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: We’re nearing the part of the holiday shopping season when it’s do or die time. If you didn’t do something already, you’re likely scrambling to figure out a Plan B, or maybe even a Plan Q. The gift, no matter the quality, needs to show up by, like, Friday to count as a decent gift for Christmas. Maybe you can swing Saturday—if UPS is willing to swing it for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gifts For People You Don’t Like</title>
      <link>/2016/12/21/tedium-gift-guide-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/12/21/tedium-gift-guide-2016/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: You’ve already checked off the people you know and love. Maybe even the people you know and tolerate. But what about gifts for folks you have a distaste for? That’s where our end-of-season gift guide comes into play. It’s full of obscure stuff and absolute dreck that you may or may not care for. But it’s perfect for breaking off weak friendships, telling a long-lost relative that they probably shouldn’t have returned, or for lowering someone’s overall standard for living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stocking Stinkers: A Tedium Gift Guide</title>
      <link>/2015/12/21/stocking-stinkers-tedium-gift-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/21/stocking-stinkers-tedium-gift-guide/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Tedium is publishing on an different schedule this week—Monday and Wednesday mornings rather than Tuesday and Thursday evenings—so as to get in your inbox before the holiday rush of out-of-office replies and connecting flights.
Today in Tedium: If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this and still in need of gift ideas for your loved ones, it&amp;rsquo;s already too late. (Did you know that Christmas is on Friday?!) You will find nothing good in your inbox or elsewhere that will save you at this point.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>