<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bbs on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/bbs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bbs on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 09:57:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/bbs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Free As In Internet</title>
      <link>/2018/01/05/internet-free-net-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 09:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/05/internet-free-net-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The internet has not exactly lived its best life in the past twelve months. Between the tribalism and the stress of online culture we’ve seen of late, it’s understandable if even some of the internet’s biggest fans are having second thoughts on where things are headed. (And that’s not even counting the drama of the FCC’s net neutrality repeal.) Last week, The Verge made the case that 2017 was a year in which we wanted our internet to be smaller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wires Barely Reach</title>
      <link>/2016/09/02/internet-bbs-global-expansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 06:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/09/02/internet-bbs-global-expansion/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: We take so much of our online connections for granted. You probably visit hundreds of pages a day on a device fast enough to melt fabric, gobbling up gigabytes of data without even thinking about it. And there&amp;rsquo;s a good chance that if you didn&amp;rsquo;t have a connection, you would be mildly annoyed. But those connections were not a given in many parts of the world for years after the internet became commonplace in developed countries.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>