<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Plastic on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/plastic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Plastic on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/plastic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Screwy Straw Stat</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/plastic-straw-statistic-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/plastic-straw-statistic-questions/</guid>
      <description>[big]As you may or may not know, I often speak up against the way that sometimes, a “fact” will show up on Wikipedia, unchallenged, for years, only to stumble into books large and small over the next number of years, something I call “The Windex Problem.”[/big]
But what if the data point is something being shared not by an encyclopedia, but by a number of nonprofits looking to make the case for a bigger mission?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ban The Box</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/compact-disc-longbox-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/compact-disc-longbox-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Thirty years ago, the record industry decided it didn’t want to be the record industry anymore. It wanted to be the CD industry, with maybe some cassettes on the side. It was getting rid of all that vinyl! This situation, oddly enough, may just repeat in 2018—except, this time, not by choice. Best Buy is about to throw out its record racks entirely; Target is making the idea of selling physical CDs less financially advantageous for record labels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bend, Don’t Break</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/unbreakable-combs-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/unbreakable-combs-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Modern hair combs are unusually simple tools—perhaps our simplest. Their single row of bristles, usually black, are designed to do one thing—separate and organize your hair follicles into a more attractive format. They do this effectively, without the need of any electricity. And they’re cheap, too—you never have one when you need one, but you can buy a pack of 72 of them for eight bucks, or 11 cents each.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloth, Meet Plastic</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/3d-printing-t-shirt-designs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/3d-printing-t-shirt-designs/</guid>
      <description>[big]As I learned a few months ago, creating custom T-shirts is a somewhat-complicated, but often quite useful way of promoting a product or raising money for an endeavor. That’s in part because it’s something that can’t effectively be done in the comfort of one’s home. [/big]
Screen-printing is a complicated process, embroidery moreso. You generally need specialized equipment, and the result of doing it at home is usually obvious—you can tell when a shirt was the product of an iron-on design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genuine Imitation Leather</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/genuine-imitation-leather/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/genuine-imitation-leather/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: As any cursory watch of an episode of Happy Days will tell you, we&amp;rsquo;re obsessed with the look of leather—but perhaps not fans of the way leather is produced. Much like a meal at McDonald&amp;rsquo;s or a fur coat, we&amp;rsquo;re more impressed with the final result without any worries about where it came from—because thinking about where it came from potentially raises some heavy ethical questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Not Styrofoam</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/expanded-polystyrene-foam-not-styrofoam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/expanded-polystyrene-foam-not-styrofoam/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: In the age of instant takeout, there may be no greater scourge than polystyrene, a necessary evil of many a food delivery. New York City, famously, tried to ban the foamy substance before a judge struck down the ban. And lots of other cities have tried to follow suit—most aggressively San Francisco, and most recently Bangor, Maine. Heck, the entire state of Maryland is considering a big ban.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lemony Fresh</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/lemon-juice-squeeze-bottles-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/lemon-juice-squeeze-bottles-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Plastic, barring all the environmental problems and health concerns that might come with it, is awesome as a moldable product. It shows up in all sorts of places, from laptop cases, to CDs, to bottles. Today, I want to talk about a common, but relatively obscure use for plastic: As a way to sell lemon juice. Someone had the idea to sell lemon juice inside a squeezable container that looks exactly like a lemon, and it’s been something of a hit product ever since.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Still Grasping At Straws</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/plastic-straw-replacement-controversy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/plastic-straw-replacement-controversy/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey all, with all the recent chatter about straws in the news of late, we thought it would be a good idea to bring back this piece on the topic—with some sizable updates, of course. Cheers!
[big]Today in Tedium: The plastic straw is a simple invention with relatively modest value: For a few moments, the device helps make beverages easier to drink. And then, due to reasons of sanitation and ease of use, the straws are thrown away, never to be seen again.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>