<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>British on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/british/</link>
    <description>Recent content in British on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 09:26:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/british/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Distinguished Panel</title>
      <link>/2018/02/09/panel-show-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/09/panel-show-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with another piece from Andrew Egan about something nerdy and televised, two things we do well here at Tedium. (His last piece was a daily one about Beer Nuts.) Read on for more!
Today in Tedium: Television programming has long been a rotating series of common staples. Talk shows, games shows, court shows, and soap operas air during the day. Sitcoms, dramas, and reality competitions (which are somehow distinct from game shows) dominate prime time hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of Creative Destruction</title>
      <link>/2015/08/07/a-tale-of-creative-destruction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/07/a-tale-of-creative-destruction/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The early Counting Crows hit &amp;ldquo;Mr. Jones&amp;rdquo; was a lie. Take that back—the incident was real, and Adam Duritz did hang out with a guy with the last name Jones, but the song&amp;rsquo;s whole plotline about how they were gonna be happier when they were famous didn&amp;rsquo;t come to pass. If you go to a Counting Crows show these days, in fact, the lyric is now &amp;ldquo;we all wanna be big, big stars, yeah, but then we get second thoughts about that.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>