<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 07:42:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Googling</title>
      <link>/2018/10/03/google-20th-anniversary-culture-importance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 07:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/03/google-20th-anniversary-culture-importance/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Love, hate, or criticize them, Google is just a part of life these days. (They’re marginally less evil than Facebook, which helps.) Silicon Valley’s algorithmic gift to the world is now two decades old, having celebrated its 20th birthday with a doodle just last week, one that came a few weeks after its actual birthday—the September 4, 1998 incorporation of the company. It’s strange to consider that a company so fundamental to our world is still so relatively young.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything You Want</title>
      <link>/2018/08/02/vertical-horizon-verizon-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/02/vertical-horizon-verizon-theory/</guid>
      <description>On April 3, 2000, one of the most prominent companies of the 21st century was born. That day, the name and logo for Verizon became known to the masses. The company, for better or worse, became a defining middleman, fundamental to the way we use our phones and access our internet.  The next day, a popular rock band released a physical single for what would become their biggest hit. “Everything You Want,” a song from Vertical Horizon&amp;rsquo;s first major label record, had already been on the radio for a few months by this point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Internet&#39;s Final Frontier</title>
      <link>/2018/07/06/smart-bathroom-technology-toilets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 07:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/06/smart-bathroom-technology-toilets/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Thanks to the ever-shrinking nature of our electronics, the internet can go literally anywhere. I mean anywhere. It fits in your bag, appears on your television set, shows up on your desk, it makes a great window into your fridge, and even appears in your pocket. And since it fits in your pocket, that means you can take it inside the bathroom, making it a worthy replacement for a certain series of books we covered earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall Of Voodoo</title>
      <link>/2018/02/14/3dfx-history-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 16:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/14/3dfx-history-failure/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Today’s startup companies seem to have a certain arc to them—they get some seed funding, they launch, they draw some interest for their good idea, they keep growing, and maybe they become a part of the fabric of our lives … or a part of the fabric of a significantly larger company. Strangely, 3Dfx didn’t so much draw interest as blow the lid off of a trend that redefined how we think of video games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free As In Internet</title>
      <link>/2018/01/05/internet-free-net-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 09:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/05/internet-free-net-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The internet has not exactly lived its best life in the past twelve months. Between the tribalism and the stress of online culture we’ve seen of late, it’s understandable if even some of the internet’s biggest fans are having second thoughts on where things are headed. (And that’s not even counting the drama of the FCC’s net neutrality repeal.) Last week, The Verge made the case that 2017 was a year in which we wanted our internet to be smaller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google’s Zombie</title>
      <link>/2017/11/15/google-feedburner-rss-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/15/google-feedburner-rss-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Google may be the internet’s greatest murderer of ideas. Between its numerous acquihires, its aggressive approach to launching (and discarding) moonshots, and its tendency to build impressive products only to kill them months later, Google may be the greatest example of a cold-blooded idea killer in history. But one product under the search giant’s lineup strikes my fancy in particular, because Google never killed it, even though everyone thought it would.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Lock Information Down</title>
      <link>/2017/08/25/drm-history-intertrust-contentguard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/25/drm-history-intertrust-contentguard/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Digital rights management seemingly came out of nowhere to define our relationship with technology in the modern day. Popularly, it seemed like its birth had come as a direct response to the growth of piracy in the film and music industries, but what’s interesting—and perhaps not properly contextualized—is that it existed for years prior to Napster, and had a technical component before the Digital Millennium Copyright Act gave it a legal component.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Checkmate Yourself</title>
      <link>/2017/07/28/yahoo-games-failure-classicgames/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/28/yahoo-games-failure-classicgames/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: This week, the world (for a brief moment) lost its collective mind after learning that Microsoft was planning to retire its legendary Paint software, which has a lineage that dates all the way back to Windows 1.0 in 1985. People calmed down some after learning that the company was creating an upgraded version of the app called Paint 3D, but make no mistake: As I hinted recently, big tech companies kill things people like all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back To The Shack</title>
      <link>/2017/06/09/radio-shack-bankruptcy-auction-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 04:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/09/radio-shack-bankruptcy-auction-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: For many reasons, largely related to a shifting business model incompatible with modern tech needs, a whole generation of people saw RadioShack as less a store for tinkerers and more a place to buy commodity tech products. It was a business model that fell out of sync with the enthusiast community that once championed its products, and the twice-bankrupt RadioShack has been paying the price for that pivot ever since.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COBOLed Together</title>
      <link>/2017/04/11/cobol-programmers-cobol-cowboys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 06:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/04/11/cobol-programmers-cobol-cowboys/</guid>
      <description>If you’re a regular reader of Y Combinator’s excellent mini-Reddit aggregator Hacker News (as I am), you start to see some trends arise. Programming languages and frameworks become incredibly popular (Ruby on Rails! Django! Node! Go!), but then start to lose their luster over time as programmers inevitably move onto the next coding innovation.  But the thing is, programming frameworks didn’t used to be this trendy, and some of the really old ones are becoming highly-sought-after in certain sectors because they’re becoming very uncommon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Air of Superiority</title>
      <link>/2016/06/29/air-conditioning-architecture-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2016 07:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/06/29/air-conditioning-architecture-problems/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The 1902 invention of air conditioning has long been hailed as one of the most important inventions of the 20th century, one that has forever changed the way we live. But as we hit an era when robots become more human than ever and try to steal our jobs, I find myself wondering—what can we learn from the additional freedom that air conditioning gave us? Sure, it improved our society by making temperature something that we can control, but what about the problems that came with this cool breeze?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Talk Toner</title>
      <link>/2016/05/06/photocopiers-xerox-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 07:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/05/06/photocopiers-xerox-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In an era where paper is becoming less important than ever, it feels a bit bizarre at this point to go back in time just 35 years ago, when paper was perhaps having its greatest moment of all time. We were just a few years from the desktop publishing revolution, which expanded the sheer amount of stuff one could put on a page. The &amp;lsquo;zine movement was perhaps at its peak during this time, proving an important way to democratize content for the average person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back That Thang Up</title>
      <link>/2016/04/01/physical-backup-antiques-3d-printing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/04/01/physical-backup-antiques-3d-printing/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It&amp;rsquo;s deeply ironic that World Backup Day comes just a day before April Fools Day. One day encourages people to be stoic, serious, and overly cautious because people are inherently clumsy or devious; the other is designed to encourage people to throw caution in the wind because people are just Joshin&amp;rsquo; you. So in honor of both days (and in an effort to counter-program against all the stupid April Fool&amp;rsquo;s emails you&amp;rsquo;re probably going to be getting in the next 24 hours), let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the nature of destruction—physical things that are valuable because they can&amp;rsquo;t be backed up, getting damaged, dinged up, or destroyed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Format War Footnotes</title>
      <link>/2015/09/04/format-wars-laserdisc-hitclips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2015 08:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/09/04/format-wars-laserdisc-hitclips/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: They say that history is written by the people who win—a standard that translates to wars and land grabs of all types. But it also translates pretty effectively to format wars. Generally, when we reminisce about old-school formats, we tend to focus on vinyl records, tape decks, and floppy disks, but those only really scratch the surface of the kind of bizarre formats out there to grab content from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fake Metal Trees</title>
      <link>/2015/08/05/cell-towers-nimby-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 07:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/05/cell-towers-nimby-trees/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Here&amp;rsquo;s a tough problem. People love their cell phones, but the they hate the towers necessary to make those phones function. In fact, they really piss many people off, leading to situations where unnecessary fear-mongering wins the day, or leading people to worry that the towers will become eyesores that destroy their property values—or worse. So how do we get around the issue of these useful-but-ugly devices, anyway?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give us some credit</title>
      <link>/2015/06/10/credit-card-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/10/credit-card-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The payment card as we know it is both more popular than ever and, well, dying. According to a 2013 Federal Reserve study, the number of credit card payments in the United States passed the number of check-based payments for the first time, and debit cards passed that mark way back in 2004. But the magnetic swipe isn&amp;rsquo;t long for this world—the industry is switching to a chip-based system this year, and mobile payments threaten to put cards out to pasture soon after that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s a bright idea</title>
      <link>/2015/03/25/bright-idea-lighting-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/25/bright-idea-lighting-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Not many light bulbs can say that they&amp;rsquo;ve managed to survive two World Wars and then some, but the fire department in Livermore, California has managed to keep a life of its own far beyond many of the firefighters that have stayed on call over the past 114 years. The bulb, which the department calls &amp;ldquo;The Centennial Bulb,&amp;rdquo; has only been shut off a few times in its history, and remains working to this day essentially because they go out of their way to never turn the light bulb off.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>