<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Television Industry on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/television-industry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Television Industry on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 03:26:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/television-industry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Solved</title>
      <link>/2018/06/20/unsolved-mysteries-modern-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 03:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/20/unsolved-mysteries-modern-updates/</guid>
      <description>More than 30 years ago, onetime Eliot Ness stand-in Robert Stack found a way to embellish his legacy in the modern era.  The solution was through a show named Unsolved Mysteries, one of the first reality-based shows of the modern era, mixing scripted plots with true stories. First appearing as a special in 1987, it became a full-fledged series not long after the success of a similar program, America’s Most Wanted on Fox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Not HBO, It’s UHF</title>
      <link>/2018/04/25/uhf-subscription-channels-descrambler-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/25/uhf-subscription-channels-descrambler-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: I’m going to say it right now—we totally got lucky with our acquisition of the Genesis Storytime video earlier this month, which, while it didn’t bring in millions of views, may be the most impressive thing we’ve ever done. (Nice work, Andrew!) More likely, a hunt for an obscure video will end in tears, possibly a dead end. (We were not the first people to hunt for video of that channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Case Of The Missing Channel</title>
      <link>/2018/04/06/genesis-storytime-cable-channel-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 06:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/06/genesis-storytime-cable-channel-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with an epic find from Andrew Egan. He worked really hard on this one and I wanna give him a ton of credit here. Strap in for an epic piece.
Today in Tedium: Permanence and importance are at the center of Percy Shelley&amp;rsquo;s classic poem Ozymandias. &amp;ldquo;Look upon my works ye mighty and despair,&amp;rdquo; an ancient king extols from a crumbling statue before the poem concludes. &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; the long and level sands stretch far away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Institute You Can’t Disparage</title>
      <link>/2018/03/28/married-with-children-terry-rakolta/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 07:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/28/married-with-children-terry-rakolta/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The culture wars never really went away, but in an era when gun violence and online censorship are once again becoming hot topics in the news, now feels like a great time to discuss one of the greatest sources of controversy of the past 30 years—Married … With Children, an edge-busting TV sitcom that predated the Streisand Effect but may have been one of its earliest examples. And it all came about thanks to a Michigan homemaker with a few ties to a political dynasty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Distinguished Panel</title>
      <link>/2018/02/09/panel-show-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/09/panel-show-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with another piece from Andrew Egan about something nerdy and televised, two things we do well here at Tedium. (His last piece was a daily one about Beer Nuts.) Read on for more!
Today in Tedium: Television programming has long been a rotating series of common staples. Talk shows, games shows, court shows, and soap operas air during the day. Sitcoms, dramas, and reality competitions (which are somehow distinct from game shows) dominate prime time hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Invisible Puzzle</title>
      <link>/2017/05/12/wireless-spectrum-allocation-challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 07:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/12/wireless-spectrum-allocation-challenges/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Barring our constant debates on net neutrality, one of the places where the Federal Communications Commission has the largest footprint is with our wireless spectrum. It’s a spectrum that has to serve many minders, and there are constant complaints about the spectrum being crowded. But those complaints, despite feeling modern and up-to-date, are far from new—we’ve been dealing with them pretty much ever since there was spectrum regulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Four-Minute Villain</title>
      <link>/2017/05/11/batman-tv-show-commercial-length/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 07:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/11/batman-tv-show-commercial-length/</guid>
      <description>One of the best parts of the streaming era is that you can avoid watching a ton of commercials if you don’t want to.
And in some ways, TV is responding to this change. Last year, Turner announced it was cutting back on commercials on its cable channels, and Fox—currently the market leader in commercial clutter—is trying to do the same. These days, 15 minutes of commercials in a single hour, give or take a couple of minutes, is about average.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Too Terrible For Television</title>
      <link>/2017/01/20/weird-unsold-television-pilots/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 09:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/20/weird-unsold-television-pilots/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The idea that there should be limits on the quality of what ends up on or TV screens is a common one that’s been around for ages. Hell, that’s why one of the defining shows of the 1980s is called You Can’t Do That On Television. Which is why, in a weird way, it kind of makes sense that many of the new shows actually getting on the air in 2017 are actually revivals of successful ones—including, as was just announced, Will and Grace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Before Netflix</title>
      <link>/2017/01/06/first-streaming-service-itv-hong-kong/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/06/first-streaming-service-itv-hong-kong/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Earlier this week, I got a little grumpy over at Product Hunt, due to an undercurrent of snark around the fact that Netflix still has a DVD service. The reason for this was that too many people were skeptical about whether such a service was still necessary. It absolutely, totally is, and I’ll give you one reason why: Netflix’s DVD service has roughly 93,000 options, while its streaming service (between shows and movies) has fewer than 8,000 options—ensuring that DVDs will have a reason to exist for quite a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Many Lives of Packard Bell</title>
      <link>/2016/12/28/packard-bell-multiple-brand-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/12/28/packard-bell-multiple-brand-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Let’s go back in time about 20 years, to two days after Christmas, 1996. On this day, as I was becoming accustomed to Bush’s second album, millions of families around the United States were unpacking and setting up their first home computers. For those who skipped the Commodore and Apple II eras, who didn’t have a Videotex installed in their televisions, and had no idea who Commander Keen even was, this was the moment in time when they joined the internet revolution, brandishing their their AOL or Hotmail addresses for all the world to see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Internet Will Be Televised</title>
      <link>/2016/09/14/webtv-history-20th-anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 07:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/09/14/webtv-history-20th-anniversary/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Terrible product ideas are a dime a dozen, but what about ideas that are fascinating, and perhaps executionally sound, but conceptually flawed? How often do they come about? And how often is it that they stick around the market for 17 years, despite fairly limited public interest? Such is the case of WebTV, the set-top device that allowed you to surf a television-optimized version of the web. On September 18, 1996—20 years ago this week—a startup firm released a device that meant to bring the internet to the living room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waaaaay Left of the Dial</title>
      <link>/2016/07/01/frankenfm-radio-fcc-analog-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/07/01/frankenfm-radio-fcc-analog-tv/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: TV on the Radio isn&amp;rsquo;t just the name of a really freaking good band. Instead, it&amp;rsquo;s a quirk of the design of analog television. But a funny thing happened on the way to obscurity: As analog TV gave way to digital, a handful of risk-taking broadcasters, sensing an opportunity, have started to run those analog TV stations as FM radio stations—big FCC plans be damned. The shift is surprisingly contentious in the world of broadcast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Destroy the White House … Again</title>
      <link>/2016/06/24/white-house-independence-day-explosion-scene/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2016 06:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/06/24/white-house-independence-day-explosion-scene/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It was an explosion that only the aliens saw coming. Almost exactly 20 years ago, the film Independence Day hit theaters and featured perhaps the single most iconic visual effect of the 1990s—a short, but effective shot of The White House getting destroyed by a gigantic alien mothership. The scene is memorable for a lot of reasons, one of which is that it looked pretty realistic. If you&amp;rsquo;re like me, you probably are wondering: How did they get that set to look so, uh, White House-y?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Annoying National Upgrade</title>
      <link>/2016/04/27/digital-television-upgrade-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 07:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/04/27/digital-television-upgrade-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The move of the television airwaves from analog to digital in 2009 was perhaps the most unusual case of planned obsolescence in the modern age. Here was a decision, mandated by the Telecommunications Act of 1996 and forced upon hundreds of millions of people at once, that threw lots of people out of their routine. Many folks weren&amp;rsquo;t ready, or maybe they didn&amp;rsquo;t care enough about their TV signal quality to upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Secret Amiga</title>
      <link>/2016/03/30/cable-prevue-channel-secret-amiga/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 07:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/03/30/cable-prevue-channel-secret-amiga/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In terms of finding out what&amp;rsquo;s on the boob tube at any given time, we&amp;rsquo;ve come a long way from the overly condensed pages of TV Guide. In fact, the magazine was already looking awful obsolete in the 1980s and 1990s, when cable systems around the country began dedicating entire channels to listing TV schedules. Eventually, the approach led to the rise of the set-top box, the power-sucking block that serves as the liaison between you and your cable company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Nobody Knows Your Name</title>
      <link>/2016/01/13/tv-show-theme-song-composers-anonymous/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 10:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/01/13/tv-show-theme-song-composers-anonymous/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: One of the last acts of David Bowie, supreme rock star of the past 50 years who died Monday morning, was the release of his album, Blackstar. One of the ways Bowie promoted the closing chapter of his work was by doing something that he hadn&amp;rsquo;t done much of over the years: he gave the title track to the album to the producers of The Last Panthers, a new TV show in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s Your Gimmick?</title>
      <link>/2015/12/04/television-history-gimmicks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/04/television-history-gimmicks/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: These days, it seems like TV is all about gimmicks: Think reality shows, TV shows that recap the TV shows that literally just aired, limited series designed to recycle old hit shows, and even live theatre productions like The Wiz. TV executives are like P.T. Barnum-style hucksters, willing to try anything to keep us watching. And it&amp;rsquo;s always been that way, honestly—if they can make watching your boob tube into an &amp;ldquo;event,&amp;rdquo; they know they&amp;rsquo;ve sucked you in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Dish</title>
      <link>/2015/08/28/early-satellite-dish-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 07:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/28/early-satellite-dish-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: As a whole, the most interesting time for television was the late 1970s and early 1980s. It was an era when most networks were still willing to experiment and the technology wasn’t so locked down that an enthusiast couldn’t get around it. Comcast existed back then, but it wasn’t the juggernaut it is now; DirecTV and Dish Network hadn’t yet taken their current forms. The result was that satellite dishes—which were really freaking massive back then—were only starting to take off, and there was nothing really stopping people willing to buy a dish from investing once and getting all their shows for free after that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Education</title>
      <link>/2015/07/10/bad-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/07/10/bad-education/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The life of a child actor is anything but traditional. Between long stays on sets and a formative experience in the public spotlight, it’s no wonder that some former child stars resort to using drugs, going crazy on reality shows, or licking donuts. On the plus side, you still get to go to school—but even there, the experience is anything but traditional. There may be some really good on-set teachers, but sometimes it’s just a drunk guy trying to freeload on a movie set rather than teach kids algebra.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worst. Birthday. Ever.</title>
      <link>/2015/05/27/happy-birthday-copyright-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/27/happy-birthday-copyright-case/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: 80 years ago, the nature of one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most popular tunes changed forever. It&amp;rsquo;s a song you&amp;rsquo;ve probably sung before, about a bajillion times. &amp;ldquo;Happy birthday to you, happy birthday …&amp;rdquo; you know the rest. In 1935, &amp;ldquo;Happy Birthday&amp;rdquo; was copyrighted, and as a result, it&amp;rsquo;s rare to hear the song performed in any film or concert. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re gonna talk about copyright, traditional songs, and the ways in which people who had no role in creating those songs are making big bucks off of the unwitting public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ted Turner&#39;s Satellite Of Love</title>
      <link>/2015/05/08/ted-turner-tbs-superstation-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/08/ted-turner-tbs-superstation-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: For a brief moment in time, independent local television stations held an impressive level of power over the country as a whole. They could share regional messages with national audiences, advertise to millions more people than they ever could on their crusty UHF signals, and punch far above their potential. The era of the superstation is past, but it undeniably had a massive effect on cable television. Don&amp;rsquo;t change the dial, because we&amp;rsquo;re talking about cable TV&amp;rsquo;s turning point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.) Learn About Lists 2.) See Item 1</title>
      <link>/2015/05/06/learn-about-lists/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 05:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/06/learn-about-lists/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: David Letterman is retiring soon, and while he didn&amp;rsquo;t invent the list, he probably did more to ensure its pop-culture legacy than anything _BuzzFeed_ could ever hope. Author and Death and Taxes editor-in-chief Brian Abrams, who wrote a book about Letterman&amp;rsquo;s NBC career last year, noted that the idea for Letterman&amp;rsquo;s Top Ten list came as a satire of the then-current obsession with lists in the mass media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell it to the judge</title>
      <link>/2015/04/22/court-shows-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2015 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/04/22/court-shows-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Courtroom drama may be one of our greatest televised resources. Reality-based shows that take place in a courtroom—of the actual kind, the high concept kind, and the heavily plotted kind—have proven one of the easiest ways to draw a consistent audience since television entered American lives in the 1950s. Last week, two things happened that highlighted this: The trial of former NFL player Aaron Hernandez, who was found guilty of first-degree murder charges; and, more colorfully, the discovery that political strategist James Carville last year made a pilot for a court show of his own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Can&#39;t Do That On The Internet</title>
      <link>/2015/04/01/you-cant-do-that-on-the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 03:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/04/01/you-cant-do-that-on-the-internet/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Talk about the ultimate after-school job: Back in 1979, an Ottawa television station decided to create a children&amp;rsquo;s television show basically because they were contractually obligated to as part of an agreement with the Canadian government. Their solution to this problem was to create a sketch comedy show, hiring local teenagers, nearly all of whom had no acting experience, to recreate the magic of _Monty Python_ and Saturday Night Live, without a matching budget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>House of product cards</title>
      <link>/2015/03/06/house-of-product-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/06/house-of-product-cards/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Last weekend, you may have been like me and binged on House of Cards. Along the way, you may have spotted a few direct references to big-name brands … many of which may have paid for the chance to be on screen with Frank Underwood and SPOILER ALERT. But the nature of products on screen and elsewhere have become so prevalent that they just bleed into the action after a while—subliminally influencing us along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re a Winner</title>
      <link>/2015/02/20/awards-shows-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/20/awards-shows-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: A few weeks back, one of our readers, Greg Pace, had an idea for a Tedium issue: One where we highlight the most random and obscure awards we can possibly find. The idea was fascinating enough, but his reasoning for us doing so was what sold us on the idea. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m too lazy to find interesting information about awards, so I thought maybe you would for me,&amp;rdquo; he wrote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evolution, Televised</title>
      <link>/2015/02/11/grown-folks-dancing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/11/grown-folks-dancing/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It may have been the greatest text message my wife had ever sent me. While I was in the middle of a deep sleep, she sent me a message informing me of the existence of a television show that raised the bar for quality late-night television on Saturday evenings. When I woke up and finally saw it, I knew that my life would never be the same, thanks to the fact that I know know that Grown Folks Dancing is a thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LOUD NOISES</title>
      <link>/2015/01/23/loudest-noises-ever-nuclear-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/23/loudest-noises-ever-nuclear-attack/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: This week, the Federal Communications Commission dropped the hammer on cable-TV giants ESPN and Viacom, fining them a combined $1.4 million for running an ad for the movie Olympus Has Fallen. The reason? The ad featured tones from the Emergency Alert System (EAS), and the FCC was not cool with allowing an advertiser to use the tones. They weren&amp;rsquo;t the only ones to face the fine—NBCUniversal got nailed by a $530,000 fine in 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genealogy for Fanbois</title>
      <link>/2015/01/14/ducktales-geneaology-fanbois/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 07:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/14/ducktales-geneaology-fanbois/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: When it comes to the internet, two particular topics are known for driving obsessiveness—genealogy and fandom. They require similar thought processes and skill sets—extreme knowledge of the subject, a willingness to dive deep into the subject matter, a lot of extra time on one&amp;rsquo;s hands—and, at times, they can work together. Most people don&amp;rsquo;t have time to do the heavy lifting to do a deep dive on this kind of fandom, so we&amp;rsquo;ve done the hard work for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Muppet Email</title>
      <link>/2015/01/09/great-muppet-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2015 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/09/great-muppet-email/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The Muppets sure are awesome, aren’t they? We agree. Clearly, Jim Henson—a man who originally thought of himself more as filmmaker than puppeteer—was on an awesome kick when he came up with the idea to convince ad execs that anthropomorphic foam and rubber could be used to sell coffee. With something as long-lasting and popular as the Muppets, there&amp;rsquo;s a good chance it&amp;rsquo;ll take you in some weird directions—like Scientology, Hebrew, and fans willing to take the Muppet legacy into their own hands.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>