<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Internet History on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/internet-history/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Internet History on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 07:42:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/internet-history/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Googling</title>
      <link>/2018/10/03/google-20th-anniversary-culture-importance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 07:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/03/google-20th-anniversary-culture-importance/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Love, hate, or criticize them, Google is just a part of life these days. (They’re marginally less evil than Facebook, which helps.) Silicon Valley’s algorithmic gift to the world is now two decades old, having celebrated its 20th birthday with a doodle just last week, one that came a few weeks after its actual birthday—the September 4, 1998 incorporation of the company. It’s strange to consider that a company so fundamental to our world is still so relatively young.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nothing But Net (And Ads)</title>
      <link>/2018/08/08/juno-netzero-free-dialup-internet-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/08/juno-netzero-free-dialup-internet-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: People want an improbable deal, no matter how unlikely that deal might actually be. Hence the strong interest in MoviePass, a company with a model so doomed that people were suggesting it would initially fail not long after it started offering free daily tickets at $9.99 per month. (Instead, its fast decline took about a year, even with a high burn rate, and now the company is changing its model because it has no other choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebTV’s Greatest Celebrity User</title>
      <link>/2018/05/16/r-stevie-moore-webtv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/16/r-stevie-moore-webtv/</guid>
      <description>R. Stevie Moore is an extraordinary archivist of his own material. Recently, the online short film series Great Big Story released a superb mini documentary about Stevie and on April 6, 2018, R. Stevie Moore was featured on the front page of Wikipedia.  The page asked “Did you know R. Stevie Moore pioneered modern indie rock, earning him the sobriquet ‘the godfather of home recording?’”
Yes, Wikipedia. I believe we already knew that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Oracle That Spoke Too Soon</title>
      <link>/2018/04/13/larry-ellison-network-computer-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 07:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/13/larry-ellison-network-computer-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Oracle has a few reasons to hate Google. The search company built a significant chunk of its empire, the Android operating system, based on Java, a programming language created by one of Oracle’s largest acquisitions, Sun Microsystems. As a result, the two companies have been going at it in court for years now. Google won a few rounds, but Oracle, more importantly, won the latest, likely ensuring a Supreme Court showdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free As In Internet</title>
      <link>/2018/01/05/internet-free-net-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 09:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/05/internet-free-net-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The internet has not exactly lived its best life in the past twelve months. Between the tribalism and the stress of online culture we’ve seen of late, it’s understandable if even some of the internet’s biggest fans are having second thoughts on where things are headed. (And that’s not even counting the drama of the FCC’s net neutrality repeal.) Last week, The Verge made the case that 2017 was a year in which we wanted our internet to be smaller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Blogging Dead?</title>
      <link>/2018/01/02/is-blogging-dead-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 03:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/02/is-blogging-dead-2018/</guid>
      <description>Is a newsletter a blog? And if it is, does that make what I do with Tedium blogging? And if so, is that practice in decline as we enter 2018?  That’s not exactly how I approach this process, certainly, but I think it’s worth discussing at length at the moment, as the culture of blogging evolves away from what it once was. Over at JSTOR’s excellent daily news site, author Farah Mohammed analyzes blogging in the past tense, pondering whether the medium is in broader decline, as big-name bloggers like Nicholas Kristof leave the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Picking Up The Slack</title>
      <link>/2017/10/18/irc-vs-slack-chat-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 07:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/18/irc-vs-slack-chat-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Love it or hate it, the business-focused chat platform Slack clearly has done something right in its four years of existence. (Case in point: It’s worth $5 billion somehow, based on a recent investment by SoftBank.) It’s particularly strange for many users in the context of what it does. Breaking down all its integrations and emoji, and it’s basically a smart chat client. Chat clients, of course, have been around forever—particularly in the form of Internet Relay Chat, or IRC, and while it was pretty successful, it never crossed into pop culture the way Slack has.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Encoded, Decoded</title>
      <link>/2017/10/04/usenet-binaries-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/04/usenet-binaries-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: As I pointed out earlier this year, people love free stuff when it comes to the internet. Beyond communication, it may be the most popular use of the internet around. But what happens when a platform intended for communication becomes overwhelmed by free stuff? To put it simply, that’s what Usenet is. The protocol, with a history that goes back nearly 40 years, evolved from its arcane roots as a place for technically minded college students and sysops to communicate into a newbie-overrun protocol, then into a major hub for file sharing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Eulogy for Eudora</title>
      <link>/2017/09/29/eudora-email-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 07:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/29/eudora-email-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Email is such a pain in the butt. (Hopefully not this specific email.) We’ve been doing everything in our power to fight the influence it has on our lives, to minimize the spam, the marketing, the burden. That burden leads lots of folks to fruitlessly hunt for the perfect email client like I hunt for the perfect word processor. Others have followed the path of least resistance: Either Gmail or Outlook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Internet On Dead Trees</title>
      <link>/2017/06/30/90s-internet-books-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 07:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/30/90s-internet-books-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Here&amp;rsquo;s the thing about the internet that is striking from the position of a crate-digger: The crate never ends. It always keeps growing just a little bigger every single second. But that crate has a hole at the bottom. Stuff is falling out just as quickly, and pieces of history that would stick around in meatspace disappear in an instant online. So as a result, there aren&amp;rsquo;t a lot of websites from 1995 that made it through to the present day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burrowing A Gopher Hole</title>
      <link>/2017/06/23/modern-day-gopher-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 07:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/23/modern-day-gopher-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Every time I use pieces of the early internet, I get this warm feeling in my chest. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to describe, but I imagine it&amp;rsquo;s a feeling not unlike the feeling that went through the crowd during the Sex Pistols concert at Manchester&amp;rsquo;s Lesser Free Trade Hall on June 4, 1976. There&amp;rsquo;s a sense of purity and simplicity there that is hard to recapture through other means—the sense that I&amp;rsquo;m witnessing something culturally important that, in its own way, could change the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Internet of Food</title>
      <link>/2017/04/07/internet-early-food-delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 07:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/04/07/internet-early-food-delivery/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: You know something you can’t get through the internet’s wires, at least not on its own? Food. We’ve been working on it for years, but no, we’re not at the point where we can deliver nourishment directly via the series of tubes. But food has always been something of a means to an end—a way of driving the internet forward, making it something people would actually like to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Were Promised Skynet</title>
      <link>/2017/03/31/satellite-internet-challenges-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 07:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/31/satellite-internet-challenges-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: As the recent vote in Congress over online privacy rules reminded us, people tend to hate their internet service providers. Case in point: Offbeat rocker Todd Rundgren once wrote and performed a poorly-aged song called “I Hate My Frickin’ ISP,” in which he railed against the anonymous loser that was preventing him from getting online, along with the service that promised him 20 free, addiction-starting hours. (It’s a bad entryway into his catalog, by the way; you’re way better off with “I Saw The Light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Code Is Junky</title>
      <link>/2017/03/03/microsoft-frontpage-history-web-design-wysiwyg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 09:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/03/microsoft-frontpage-history-web-design-wysiwyg/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: As I’ve covered a few times in the past, the hard part about any budding technology—whether it’s delivering packages, driving down interstate highways, or beaming satellite signals to homes around the country—is the infrastructure, how easy that infrastructure is to use. The internet is obviously a pretty key example of this issue in action, with products like WebTV and CompuServe imagining a specific direction for reading content online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Impurrfect History</title>
      <link>/2017/01/25/cats-dot-com-domain-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 21:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/25/cats-dot-com-domain-history/</guid>
      <description>Let’s face facts: Having an awesome domain name is no guarantee for success. This was proven just a couple of weeks ago in my piece about the failure of Pets.com. But it still highlights a whole lot of potential.  Which is why the recent domain sale of Cats.com—literally, an entire domain name for the internet’s favorite animal—is one that we should closely watch. The domain is currently sitting at $125,000 on the auction site Flippa, and will sell to the highest bidder in the next five days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News In Small Bytes</title>
      <link>/2016/11/04/online-news-history-compuserve-videotex/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 07:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/11/04/online-news-history-compuserve-videotex/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Publishing words on a computer is not a difficult task these days. We have so many options to write words and distribute them through a computerized interface that we take the whole process for granted. (You probably published something in the time it took you to read the previous two sentences.) But there was a time when publishing through a computer was painful, cumbersome, and expensive. It also had little in common with the free-for-all that allows for the creation of all sorts of terrible/fascinating content online by random folks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Internet&#39;s First Election</title>
      <link>/2016/10/19/1992-election-internet-influence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 07:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/10/19/1992-election-internet-influence/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: For the past 20 years, a familiar trend has exposed itself with the turn of every U.S. presidential election cycle: Each one is ever-slightly more defined (heck, even redefined) by technology, particularly online trends that have come along in the three years prior. In 1996, it was a coming-out party for the web. In 2000, the growth of online news began to have an impact on how we researched candidates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting The Next Word In</title>
      <link>/2016/10/05/word-processors-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 07:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/10/05/word-processors-future/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Word processors are generally kind of boring—they do their job, and that&amp;rsquo;s about it. Most people don&amp;rsquo;t put a ton of second thought into their word processors. As you might have noticed from my rant from a couple of months ago, I&amp;rsquo;m not that kind of person. That rant drew up a lot of conversation, most of it good and interesting. (It did have its critics, but even their comments were interesting!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Internet Will Be Televised</title>
      <link>/2016/09/14/webtv-history-20th-anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 07:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/09/14/webtv-history-20th-anniversary/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Terrible product ideas are a dime a dozen, but what about ideas that are fascinating, and perhaps executionally sound, but conceptually flawed? How often do they come about? And how often is it that they stick around the market for 17 years, despite fairly limited public interest? Such is the case of WebTV, the set-top device that allowed you to surf a television-optimized version of the web. On September 18, 1996—20 years ago this week—a startup firm released a device that meant to bring the internet to the living room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wires Barely Reach</title>
      <link>/2016/09/02/internet-bbs-global-expansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 06:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/09/02/internet-bbs-global-expansion/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: We take so much of our online connections for granted. You probably visit hundreds of pages a day on a device fast enough to melt fabric, gobbling up gigabytes of data without even thinking about it. And there&amp;rsquo;s a good chance that if you didn&amp;rsquo;t have a connection, you would be mildly annoyed. But those connections were not a given in many parts of the world for years after the internet became commonplace in developed countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re going viral</title>
      <link>/2015/07/24/early-computer-virus-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 06:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/07/24/early-computer-virus-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The computer virus has kind of taken on a life of its own in popular culture, often being seen as a device that destroys computers and data, while making itself known in the process. Things have changed since that hallowed era—the malware is still with us, but the way it attacks computers has changed drastically since the &amp;lsquo;80s. Today, we talk about computer viruses as if we&amp;rsquo;re in the midst of an archaeological dig.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The History of Internet Explorer Hatred</title>
      <link>/2015/03/20/the-history-of-internet-explorer-hatred/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/20/the-history-of-internet-explorer-hatred/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Your browser says a lot about you. It highlights your socioeconomic class, your knowledge of computing, your inherent biases, and even the likelihood that you’re a failure at just about everything. For many people, using Internet Explorer was a sign that your relative or co-worker didn’t “get it,” and their resistance to changing browsers was a sign that they never would. Developers, without knowing your name or your circumstances, would curse you under your breath, because your clicking on their website made their job harder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tales Of The Interwebs</title>
      <link>/2015/02/18/early-internet-history-tales/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2015 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/18/early-internet-history-tales/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Last week, one of the men who created the internet as we know it sounded the alarms on its future. Vinton Cerf, a Google executive and one of the architects of ARPANET, noted that decades of files could be lost to history, with no way to access the documents, due to lacking digital preservation efforts. “When you think about the quantity of documentation from our daily lives that is captured in digital form, like our interactions by email, people’s tweets, and all of the world wide web, it’s clear that we stand to lose an awful lot of our history,” he said, according to The Guardian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quitting is OK</title>
      <link>/2015/01/30/andrew-sullivan-quitting-is-ok/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/30/andrew-sullivan-quitting-is-ok/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Everyone is addicted to something. There are certain addictions that we carry around with us that eventually need to be put to bed. Andrew Sullivan, one of the greatest (and most controversial) pundits of the early 21st century, was addicted to blogging. Sully, who&amp;rsquo;s was one of the most popular online writers of his era and the first big-name writer to devote his life to the practice, announced that he was quitting his longtime platform, The Dish, on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LOUD NOISES</title>
      <link>/2015/01/23/loudest-noises-ever-nuclear-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/23/loudest-noises-ever-nuclear-attack/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: This week, the Federal Communications Commission dropped the hammer on cable-TV giants ESPN and Viacom, fining them a combined $1.4 million for running an ad for the movie Olympus Has Fallen. The reason? The ad featured tones from the Emergency Alert System (EAS), and the FCC was not cool with allowing an advertiser to use the tones. They weren&amp;rsquo;t the only ones to face the fine—NBCUniversal got nailed by a $530,000 fine in 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Internet&#39;s First Hater</title>
      <link>/2015/01/07/meet-the-internets-first-hater/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/07/meet-the-internets-first-hater/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Two decades ago this month, a guy named Mirsky changed the internet forever in his own subtle way. His product? A site called Mirsky&amp;rsquo;s Worst of the Web. It was one of the internet&amp;rsquo;s first true phenomena and an icon of Web 1.0 culture. For a couple of years, he could count press mentions from sources as prominent as The Washington Post, People, and The Los Angeles Times.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>