<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Emulation on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/emulation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Emulation on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 07:28:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/emulation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Just Nostalgia</title>
      <link>/2018/04/11/nes-homebrew-scene-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 07:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/11/nes-homebrew-scene-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with another great piece from David Buck, who we last saw talking about Oingo Boingo. Tonight, he’s got something else brewin’.
Today in Tedium: Growing up in the era of the Nintendo Entertainment System, I always wanted to create my own NES game. I scribbled ideas in notebooks, mapped out levels on graph paper and spent countless hours composing my own MIDI-based soundtracks to games that didn’t exist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Extra Serving</title>
      <link>/2017/05/02/nesticle-history-extras-part-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 06:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/02/nesticle-history-extras-part-one/</guid>
      <description>What a day! My article on Vice&amp;rsquo;s Motherboard this week about the history of NESticle—the Nintendo Entertainment System emulator whose early success paved the way for people to play vintage games on their computers whenever they want—took a while to get past the finish line, and came only after I gave the piece a haircut.  To augment the story, I’m gonna spend the next couple of Daily Tedium pieces highlighting things I hoped to get into the original piece but were trimmed out because the piece was getting a bit lengthy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>