<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>History on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/history/</link>
    <description>Recent content in History on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 07:44:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/history/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Pronged</title>
      <link>/2018/10/19/stapler-history-office-supplies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 07:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/19/stapler-history-office-supplies/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: If you’ve been reading my Twitter feed recently, beyond the jokes about old Stephen King aliases and sketchy emails from “Warren Buffett,” you’ll know that I spent a lot of my time recently getting acquainted with a stapler, as part of the now-completed production process with the Tedium zine. (Sorry if you missed it; I might do another zine later on, I’ll keep you posted.) I learned a lot about staples during this process: that you really need a special kind of stapler to do the kind of stapling I was doing real justice, and that Office Depot doesn’t sell that stapler for some reason shakes fist; that staples are brittle and break really easily; and that a guitar pick works in a pinch as a staple-flattener.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stooge Story</title>
      <link>/2018/08/22/three-stooges-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/22/three-stooges-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: A while back, I wrote this piece on the Sound Blaster where I spent a bit of time explaining that internal expansion ports were once very common in PCs. It was the type of thing that, had I written the story even five years earlier, might not even have been necessary. But so many people have grown up without them, on laptops and tablets, that the explainer was actually useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hooked On Velcro</title>
      <link>/2018/06/06/velcro-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 07:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/06/velcro-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Over the weekend, I spent a bit of time cleaning my messenger bag, which had an annoying problem—the pointy half of the Velcro was filthy, covered in ugly pieces of fabric it had picked up through years of heavy regular use. After looking online, I found the great solution to this annoying problem: I took the sharp part of a plastic tape dispenser and rubbed it through the rough part of the material, which, amazingly, did the trick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Blogging Dead?</title>
      <link>/2018/01/02/is-blogging-dead-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 03:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/02/is-blogging-dead-2018/</guid>
      <description>Is a newsletter a blog? And if it is, does that make what I do with Tedium blogging? And if so, is that practice in decline as we enter 2018?  That’s not exactly how I approach this process, certainly, but I think it’s worth discussing at length at the moment, as the culture of blogging evolves away from what it once was. Over at JSTOR’s excellent daily news site, author Farah Mohammed analyzes blogging in the past tense, pondering whether the medium is in broader decline, as big-name bloggers like Nicholas Kristof leave the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doing It For Erma</title>
      <link>/2017/12/19/let-erma-do-it-internet-archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/19/let-erma-do-it-internet-archive/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this year, I got incredibly fascinated by a book. One that had fallen off of store shelves nearly 60 years ago. The problem was, I had no way of getting hold of that book without actually going to the trouble of buying it.  Perhaps that was a little annoying, but David O. Woodbury’s 1956 work Let Erma Do It, which is titled after one of the first automated check-sorting systems ever produced, was a worthy book at the front end of the era of automation that has brought us so many things since.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of Two Samoas</title>
      <link>/2017/10/16/american-samoa-spanish-flu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 19:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/16/american-samoa-spanish-flu/</guid>
      <description>For understandable reasons, Puerto Rico is perhaps the main U.S. territory on the minds of the American public at the moment. The island of 3.5 million has been utterly devastated by Hurricane Maria and it will likely be years before it’s back to a semblance of its normal self—a situation not being helped, to say the least, by the current president.  Tedium, of course, isn’t a news blog, but sometimes it helps to take news and highlight it through the frame of history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Columbus The Enigma</title>
      <link>/2017/10/09/christopher-columbus-appearance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 22:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/09/christopher-columbus-appearance/</guid>
      <description>Editor’s note: Last week, Daily Tedium took a week off, in large part because I felt icky about writing anything related to the news cycle in the wake of the tragic Las Vegas shooting. We’re slowly getting back into things today.
&amp;nbsp;
Christopher Columbus wasn’t first. He misnamed entire swaths of people, entire ethnic groups, in part because he didn’t understand what was in front of him, which understandably didn’t stick well with those people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Nailed It</title>
      <link>/2017/02/08/fingernail-trimming-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/02/08/fingernail-trimming-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Fingernails have a functional purpose—they’re shells for our fingertips—but they sure come with an annoying side effect. That effect? The fact that, every couple of weeks you have to cut them. No matter who you are, you have to go through this process where small pieces of your keratin fly everywhere because you’re shoving them in a nail clipper. By the way, did you know that nail clippers are a fairly new phenomenon, roughly as old as the Swiss Army Knife?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cutting A Rug</title>
      <link>/2017/01/11/carpet-history-evolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/11/carpet-history-evolution/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: I have a song stuck in my head right now. A jingle, really. It’s been stuck in my head for the last 15 years, at least. It’s probably stuck in your head, too—and if you’re near Chicago, it’s been stuck in your head since the days of disco. It’s the work of a man who spent decades trying to sell us carpet. Hardwood flooring too, maybe windows as well, but mostly carpet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Internet&#39;s First Election</title>
      <link>/2016/10/19/1992-election-internet-influence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 07:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/10/19/1992-election-internet-influence/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: For the past 20 years, a familiar trend has exposed itself with the turn of every U.S. presidential election cycle: Each one is ever-slightly more defined (heck, even redefined) by technology, particularly online trends that have come along in the three years prior. In 1996, it was a coming-out party for the web. In 2000, the growth of online news began to have an impact on how we researched candidates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live and Let Dye</title>
      <link>/2015/08/26/food-coloring-dye-safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/26/food-coloring-dye-safety/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Did you hear the news? They&amp;rsquo;re taking the color out of Trix. The General Mills cereal is one of the most recent victims of a move towards more natural food, and in an effort to appease the suddenly health-conscious public, the company will be removing some of the artificial coloring from Trix and all of its other cereals. &amp;ldquo;We wanted to make sure they were still fun vibrant colors that we are providing and the fruity flavor that kids expect,&amp;rdquo; cereal developer Kate Gallager told Good Morning America of the move back in June.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This&#39;ll Blow You Away</title>
      <link>/2015/08/19/hand-dryer-dyson-airblade-xlerator/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 07:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/19/hand-dryer-dyson-airblade-xlerator/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: if you&amp;rsquo;ve been reading us for a while, you might notice a common theme in the pieces we send out to you guys. Often, our strangest issues take things common (but mundane), and discover a secret history hiding under your nose. From belly buttons to bandages to veggie burgers, no subject is too mundane for us. If you use it, there&amp;rsquo;s probably a great story as to how it got there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A phone book for computers</title>
      <link>/2015/08/12/computer-shopper-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 08:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/12/computer-shopper-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The phone book isn&amp;rsquo;t really anyone&amp;rsquo;s idea of an innovative product, but it definitely had its place on the shelf of many a home before the internet took over. In the late throes of the age of the white pages, however, an unusually large magazine stole the hearts of many a techie, and in the process became something of a bible for people looking to replace their 286 with a 486—and maybe buy a laser printer in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Machine That Gives You Stuff</title>
      <link>/2015/06/26/how-vending-machines-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 07:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/26/how-vending-machines-work/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Vending machines are one of the few things keeping us away from the dream of a cashless society. The devices, which offer up an array of items for a little bit of pocket change, are silent but prevalent. They represent some of our most technologically advanced furniture, and they&amp;rsquo;ll probably always be there for us in our time of need. Today&amp;rsquo;s Tedium discusses their history—along with why, for some reason, they make us want to steal stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get off my lawn</title>
      <link>/2015/06/16/lawn-care-history-get-off-my-lawn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 06:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/16/lawn-care-history-get-off-my-lawn/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Rich people care about their grass way more than normal people do. Now, rarely is this an issue, but in recent months, the ongoing California drought has made this mundane issue a political one. This week, the city of Rancho Santa Fe became a target of this culture clash after _The Washington Post_ highlighted the water-rationing requirement it soon faces. Local residents aren&amp;rsquo;t happy. “When we bought, we didn’t plan on getting a place that looks like we’re living in an African savanna,” said conservative radio host and local resident Steve Yuhas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This one&#39;s for the wounded</title>
      <link>/2015/05/20/history-of-bandages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/20/history-of-bandages/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Blood is a terrible thing to waste, and for centuries, the ways to stop blood from leaving the body were inefficient at best and not exactly easy to use. But one day, a guy spotted a problem that his wife was having and came up with one of the most brilliant solutions for solving simple injuries that the world had ever seen. And we’ve only kept innovating from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This land is my land</title>
      <link>/2015/04/24/micronations-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/04/24/micronations-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Starting your own country is not something that&amp;rsquo;s particularly easy to do. For one thing, you have no idea if it&amp;rsquo;s going to work, plus you&amp;rsquo;re stuck having to figure out annoyingly complicated details like currency, how laws will be implemented, and how you&amp;rsquo;re going to defend your borders from jerks you don&amp;rsquo;t want on your land. Czech politician Vít Jedlicka, however, thinks he&amp;rsquo;s up to the task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m older than you&#39;ll ever be</title>
      <link>/2015/04/08/im-older-than-youll-ever-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/04/08/im-older-than-youll-ever-be/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It&amp;rsquo;s the most dangerous title to hold—the title of the world&amp;rsquo;s oldest person. You know that you&amp;rsquo;re not going to survive for long, and while there are occasional exceptions, it&amp;rsquo;s a title that frequently changes hands. Gertrude Weaver barely even had a chance to celebrate her newfound reign as the world&amp;rsquo;s oldest woman—she died a mere five days after the title changed hands, at age 116. (Up next is Michigan woman Jeralean Talley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take me out to the riot</title>
      <link>/2015/04/03/famous-baseball-riots/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/04/03/famous-baseball-riots/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: This weekend marks the opening day of the 2015 season of Major League Baseball—a sport that you find either immensely fascinating or overrated compared to more action-packed sports like football or basketball. Baseball has never completely lost the public&amp;rsquo;s fascination, though it&amp;rsquo;s certainly had some rough periods over the years. And sometimes, the fans can be total jerks. Today&amp;rsquo;s issue of Tedium covers what it&amp;rsquo;s like to be in the midst of a crowd of annoying baseball fans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Can&#39;t Do That On The Internet</title>
      <link>/2015/04/01/you-cant-do-that-on-the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 03:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/04/01/you-cant-do-that-on-the-internet/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Talk about the ultimate after-school job: Back in 1979, an Ottawa television station decided to create a children&amp;rsquo;s television show basically because they were contractually obligated to as part of an agreement with the Canadian government. Their solution to this problem was to create a sketch comedy show, hiring local teenagers, nearly all of whom had no acting experience, to recreate the magic of _Monty Python_ and Saturday Night Live, without a matching budget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s a bright idea</title>
      <link>/2015/03/25/bright-idea-lighting-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/25/bright-idea-lighting-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Not many light bulbs can say that they&amp;rsquo;ve managed to survive two World Wars and then some, but the fire department in Livermore, California has managed to keep a life of its own far beyond many of the firefighters that have stayed on call over the past 114 years. The bulb, which the department calls &amp;ldquo;The Centennial Bulb,&amp;rdquo; has only been shut off a few times in its history, and remains working to this day essentially because they go out of their way to never turn the light bulb off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The History of Internet Explorer Hatred</title>
      <link>/2015/03/20/the-history-of-internet-explorer-hatred/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/20/the-history-of-internet-explorer-hatred/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Your browser says a lot about you. It highlights your socioeconomic class, your knowledge of computing, your inherent biases, and even the likelihood that you’re a failure at just about everything. For many people, using Internet Explorer was a sign that your relative or co-worker didn’t “get it,” and their resistance to changing browsers was a sign that they never would. Developers, without knowing your name or your circumstances, would curse you under your breath, because your clicking on their website made their job harder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re a Winner</title>
      <link>/2015/02/20/awards-shows-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/20/awards-shows-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: A few weeks back, one of our readers, Greg Pace, had an idea for a Tedium issue: One where we highlight the most random and obscure awards we can possibly find. The idea was fascinating enough, but his reasoning for us doing so was what sold us on the idea. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m too lazy to find interesting information about awards, so I thought maybe you would for me,&amp;rdquo; he wrote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hay, Blinken!</title>
      <link>/2015/02/13/hay-blinken-abe-lincoln/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/13/hay-blinken-abe-lincoln/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Apologies to Ronald Reagan, but no president has lent himself to kitsch and over-analysis as much as Abraham Lincoln, perhaps the best 16th president a democratically-elected country could ask for. There has been much written and collected about ol’ Abe, and as someone who has seen Abraham Lincoln: Vampire Hunter in the theater and lived to tell the tale, I’m probably just as qualified as anyone to talk about Lincolniana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evolution, Televised</title>
      <link>/2015/02/11/grown-folks-dancing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/11/grown-folks-dancing/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It may have been the greatest text message my wife had ever sent me. While I was in the middle of a deep sleep, she sent me a message informing me of the existence of a television show that raised the bar for quality late-night television on Saturday evenings. When I woke up and finally saw it, I knew that my life would never be the same, thanks to the fact that I know know that Grown Folks Dancing is a thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of the #SOTU</title>
      <link>/2015/01/21/state-of-the-union-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/21/state-of-the-union-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The State of the Union is generally the biggest speech of most years&amp;mdash;one that has taken a pretty massive role in our society, and is seen as an event that defines the political tone for the entire year. But a few interesting facts about the SOTU: It&amp;rsquo;s not always a speech, and its defining role as a defining political event is actually a relatively recent phenomenon as far as U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Internet&#39;s First Hater</title>
      <link>/2015/01/07/meet-the-internets-first-hater/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/07/meet-the-internets-first-hater/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Two decades ago this month, a guy named Mirsky changed the internet forever in his own subtle way. His product? A site called Mirsky&amp;rsquo;s Worst of the Web. It was one of the internet&amp;rsquo;s first true phenomena and an icon of Web 1.0 culture. For a couple of years, he could count press mentions from sources as prominent as The Washington Post, People, and The Los Angeles Times.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>