<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kodak on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/kodak/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kodak on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/kodak/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kodak Krypto</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/kodak-cryptocurrency-gimmick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/kodak-cryptocurrency-gimmick/</guid>
      <description>[big]Let’s admit that a long time ago, Kodak was a hugely important company. In fact, it was a Hugely Important Company, on a level rivaled in influence by perhaps only Ford and General Electric in the mainstream.[/big]
Everyone takes pictures, and Kodak catered to the masses, iterating repeatedly based on consumer needs.
But, eventually, the company made a bad bet, choosing to protect film at a time when everything was going digital (even though its engineers helped invent some of the basic technology), and that bad bet cost it that lofty position as an important company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Point, Shoot, and Forget</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/disposable-camera-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/disposable-camera-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: It took us about a hundred years to turn film processing (in most cases) from something that took a day or longer into something that was basically instantaneous. The fact is, while photography is a high art for a significant number of people, the masses wanted something simple that minimized the pain of taking photos—because they cared about the pictures more than the camera. They wanted something … well, disposable, that could “disappear” when they were done with it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>