<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amiga on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/amiga/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Amiga on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 22:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/amiga/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Amiga Appreciation</title>
      <link>/2017/01/18/viva-amiga-documentary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/18/viva-amiga-documentary/</guid>
      <description>Love your Amiga: If you’re a longish-time reader of Tedium, you’ll know that we have a lot of appreciation for the Amiga, the Commodore-produced platform, loved by Andy Warhol, that basically set the stage for the visually-graceful computing world we have now.  Which is why the new documentary about the computing platform, Zach Weddington’s Viva Amiga: The Story of a Beautiful Machine is very much on our list of things to watch right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Secret Amiga</title>
      <link>/2016/03/30/cable-prevue-channel-secret-amiga/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 07:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/03/30/cable-prevue-channel-secret-amiga/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In terms of finding out what&amp;rsquo;s on the boob tube at any given time, we&amp;rsquo;ve come a long way from the overly condensed pages of TV Guide. In fact, the magazine was already looking awful obsolete in the 1980s and 1990s, when cable systems around the country began dedicating entire channels to listing TV schedules. Eventually, the approach led to the rise of the set-top box, the power-sucking block that serves as the liaison between you and your cable company.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>