<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Copyright on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/copyright/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Copyright on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/copyright/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bootleg this issue</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/bootleg-this-issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/bootleg-this-issue/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Last month, a director named Joseph Kahn released the _Mighty Morphin Power Rangers_ film that nobody was asking for—but despite that low ceiling, he more than topped it. The 14-minute short film starred people who have actually been cast in real movies and TV shows (James Van Der Beek and Katee Sackhoff), and took the franchise in a dark, gritty new direction that definitely has nothing in common with the Saved By the Bell-in-costume motif that the franchise was known for in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purple Copyright Eater</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/prince-troubled-relationship-with-copyright/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/prince-troubled-relationship-with-copyright/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Today in Tedium: In losing Prince Rogers Nelson, we&amp;rsquo;re losing a lot more than a idiosyncratic pop star who defined an entire New Power Generation. We&amp;rsquo;re losing the last link between our current remix-heavy culture (which, let&amp;rsquo;s face it, this newsletter wouldn&amp;rsquo;t exist without) and an era when ownership of creative work was treated as an end-all-be-all. Here was a guy who started the internet era sporting a name that literally could not be searched, who forced lawsuits over barely-noticeable renditions of his songs in YouTube clips, and who made a lot of creative stuff that nobody will likely ever see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Symbiotic Infringement</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/consumer-john-oliver-copyright-infringement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/consumer-john-oliver-copyright-infringement/</guid>
      <description>[big]On a day when the news is utterly saturated with stories about a famous YouTube user getting blocked from the service, I’d like to spend some time writing about another YouTube user who was blocked from the service today.[/big]
You don’t know him, but you’ve likely seen the videos he uploaded—because news sites linked those videos pretty religiously.
The user, named “consumer,” played a small but important role in the YouTube ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Copyright Goes Copywrong</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/public-domain-film-history-copyright/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/public-domain-film-history-copyright/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: When horror movie icon George A. Romero died earlier this year, it should have started a copyright expiration timeline for his most famous and influential work, the 1968 classic and Halloween icon Night of the Living Dead. But something really scary happened to the film before it became a hit: Due to a last-second title change and a distributor error, the former Night of the Flesh Eaters fell into the public domain upon its release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worst. Birthday. Ever.</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/happy-birthday-copyright-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/happy-birthday-copyright-case/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: 80 years ago, the nature of one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most popular tunes changed forever. It&amp;rsquo;s a song you&amp;rsquo;ve probably sung before, about a bajillion times. &amp;ldquo;Happy birthday to you, happy birthday …&amp;rdquo; you know the rest. In 1935, &amp;ldquo;Happy Birthday&amp;rdquo; was copyrighted, and as a result, it&amp;rsquo;s rare to hear the song performed in any film or concert. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re gonna talk about copyright, traditional songs, and the ways in which people who had no role in creating those songs are making big bucks off of the unwitting public.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>