<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>T Shirts on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/t-shirts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in T Shirts on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 05:15:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/t-shirts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloth, Meet Plastic</title>
      <link>/2017/08/29/3d-printing-t-shirt-designs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 05:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/29/3d-printing-t-shirt-designs/</guid>
      <description>As I learned a few months ago, creating custom T-shirts is a somewhat-complicated, but often quite useful way of promoting a product or raising money for an endeavor. That’s in part because it’s something that can’t effectively be done in the comfort of one’s home.  Screen-printing is a complicated process, embroidery moreso. You generally need specialized equipment, and the result of doing it at home is usually obvious—you can tell when a shirt was the product of an iron-on design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Lives In Fabric</title>
      <link>/2017/05/09/t-shirt-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 05:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/09/t-shirt-history/</guid>
      <description>When Amory Blaine decided to pack a T-shirt before heading to boarding school, he set in place a piece of literary history. Amory, the protagonist of F. Scott Fitzgerald’s This Side of Paradise, was the first literary character to use a T-shirt, ever.  “So early in September Amory, provided with ‘six suits summer underwear, six suits winter underwear, one sweater or T shirt, one jersey, one overcoat, winter, etc.,’ set out for New England, the land of schools,” the passage states.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>