<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Webtv on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/webtv/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Webtv on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 04:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/webtv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WebTV’s Greatest Celebrity User</title>
      <link>/2018/05/16/r-stevie-moore-webtv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/16/r-stevie-moore-webtv/</guid>
      <description>R. Stevie Moore is an extraordinary archivist of his own material. Recently, the online short film series Great Big Story released a superb mini documentary about Stevie and on April 6, 2018, R. Stevie Moore was featured on the front page of Wikipedia.  The page asked “Did you know R. Stevie Moore pioneered modern indie rock, earning him the sobriquet ‘the godfather of home recording?’”
Yes, Wikipedia. I believe we already knew that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Internet Will Be Televised</title>
      <link>/2016/09/14/webtv-history-20th-anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 07:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/09/14/webtv-history-20th-anniversary/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Terrible product ideas are a dime a dozen, but what about ideas that are fascinating, and perhaps executionally sound, but conceptually flawed? How often do they come about? And how often is it that they stick around the market for 17 years, despite fairly limited public interest? Such is the case of WebTV, the set-top device that allowed you to surf a television-optimized version of the web. On September 18, 1996—20 years ago this week—a startup firm released a device that meant to bring the internet to the living room.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>