<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Computer History on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/computer-history/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Computer History on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 07:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/computer-history/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Double Trouble</title>
      <link>/2018/09/05/disk-compression-stacker-doublespace-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 07:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/09/05/disk-compression-stacker-doublespace-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: As anyone who has ever owned a smartphone with the minimum amount of flash storage knows, space runs out fast, and once you realize you need more than you’ve allocated yourself, it’s way too late. In computing, this is a story that goes back decades, to a time when giant platters walked (OK, rolled) the Earth. But while running out of storage space on a 16-gig iPhone is annoying, it’s at least reasonable; you can put stuff on the cloud, and if the space drives you nuts, you can always upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Click, Clack</title>
      <link>/2018/07/20/cherry-mx-keyboard-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 07:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/20/cherry-mx-keyboard-history/</guid>
      <description>Editor’s Note: Tonight’s Tedium is a piece of mine that recently ran in Motherboard_, a site that recently ran a cool piece on a counterfeit iPhone X. Enjoy!_
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: Sometimes, cornering the market on a relatively niche idea is all a company needs to seal its fate as an enterprise that’s destined to stick around for the long haul. And you don’t get more relatively niche than the keyboard switch, as far as gadgets go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Command Line</title>
      <link>/2018/07/18/dos-nostalgia-squirrel-monkey-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/18/dos-nostalgia-squirrel-monkey-interview/</guid>
      <description>Hey all, Ernie here with a fresh piece from David Buck, who has moved away from his NES for a while to tell you all about how awesome DOS is as a creative medium. Yeah, DOS.
Today in Tedium: From the early 90s, up until 2005 or so, I did much of my computer gaming on an American Megatrends IBM PC, running MS-DOS and Windows 3.11. I even got online once using Netscape Communicator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Toy That Talked Back</title>
      <link>/2018/06/20/speak-and-spell-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/20/speak-and-spell-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Four decades ago this month, a company that helped set the stage for the modern computing era got into the toy market thanks to an announcement at the 1978 Summer Consumer Electronics Show. While it wasn’t the first time that kids got their hands on something truly electronic, its influence ran deep, even as its technology was fairly primitive. With its robotic voice and limited memory, the Speak &amp;amp; Spell somehow mixed the seemingly incompatible worlds of education and entertainment in an impressive way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Some Noise</title>
      <link>/2018/05/11/sound-blaster-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/11/sound-blaster-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey all, Ernie here with a classic (though lightly updated) Tedium piece about one of the defining pieces of ’90s computer technology: The Sound Blaster. Crank it up!
Today in Tedium: Before we embraced MP3s as the official noise of the internet (taking the place of screechy modems), it took a while before the synthesized notes of our musical past could be modulated through the inner-workings of a computer. Some of our earliest computers, for example, could only make very basic bleeps and bloops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Oracle That Spoke Too Soon</title>
      <link>/2018/04/13/larry-ellison-network-computer-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 07:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/13/larry-ellison-network-computer-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Oracle has a few reasons to hate Google. The search company built a significant chunk of its empire, the Android operating system, based on Java, a programming language created by one of Oracle’s largest acquisitions, Sun Microsystems. As a result, the two companies have been going at it in court for years now. Google won a few rounds, but Oracle, more importantly, won the latest, likely ensuring a Supreme Court showdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camper Van Mainframe</title>
      <link>/2018/03/16/early-portable-computer-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 07:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/16/early-portable-computer-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Portability is relative. When former Texas Instruments employees Rod Canion, Jim Harris and Bill Murto created a portable version of the IBM PC in 1982, it was a hulking device that weight 28 pounds and was roughly the size of a sewing machine. If you sold a desktop computer that weighed 28 pounds in 2018, you’d be laughed off the block. But the device, called the Compaq Portable, was revolutionary for its time and thrust the company that made it into the mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall Of Voodoo</title>
      <link>/2018/02/14/3dfx-history-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 16:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/14/3dfx-history-failure/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Today’s startup companies seem to have a certain arc to them—they get some seed funding, they launch, they draw some interest for their good idea, they keep growing, and maybe they become a part of the fabric of our lives … or a part of the fabric of a significantly larger company. Strangely, 3Dfx didn’t so much draw interest as blow the lid off of a trend that redefined how we think of video games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How&#39;s Your Soldering Technique?</title>
      <link>/2018/01/26/soldering-technology-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 09:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/26/soldering-technology-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: A lot of people use electronics with little to no idea of what actually happens inside of the little box they have on their desk or in their pockets. Sure, we might talk about the chips inside of that machine, or the processing power, but rarely do we think about the connective tissue holding many of the circuits onto the silicon. That tissue is solder, the meltable filler metal that has existed in one form or another for more than 4,000 years—long before electronics even existed as a modern context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Worst Part Of Waking Up</title>
      <link>/2018/01/24/digital-alarm-clock-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/24/digital-alarm-clock-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Here’s a strange question for you Tedium readers out there. Can you become nostalgic for abrasive noises? Particularly those noises that are specifically designed to force you out of bed into the arms of morning glory? I ask this because I was posed a question on this topic recently by a pal of mine, Sarah Davis, a.k.a. Laughterkey, one of the best Tumblr users of all time. She was watching a cooking video recently when she heard an alarm that took her way back to her childhood—a staccato four-beep sound which you can find isolated here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dots Vs. Pixels</title>
      <link>/2018/01/19/dots-per-inch-pixels-per-inch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 09:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/19/dots-per-inch-pixels-per-inch/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: If you stare into the heart of your smartphone for a while, you may start to make out the pixels. If your smartphone is really old, like the original iPhone or a cheap Android phone, that might not take a while, because the pixel resolution is quite low. But if you have an iPhone X, with its 458ppi (pixels per inch) OLED screen, perhaps it might not be so easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doing It For Erma</title>
      <link>/2017/12/19/let-erma-do-it-internet-archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/19/let-erma-do-it-internet-archive/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this year, I got incredibly fascinated by a book. One that had fallen off of store shelves nearly 60 years ago. The problem was, I had no way of getting hold of that book without actually going to the trouble of buying it.  Perhaps that was a little annoying, but David O. Woodbury’s 1956 work Let Erma Do It, which is titled after one of the first automated check-sorting systems ever produced, was a worthy book at the front end of the era of automation that has brought us so many things since.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flash Forward</title>
      <link>/2017/11/24/flash-memory-compactflash-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 09:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/24/flash-memory-compactflash-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Thanksgiving, of course, was a day full of memories. You, of course, need a place to store all those memories—and for a long time, preferably in a way that makes them easy to access for many years to come. It would also help if that method was easy to carry, easy to store, and, well, was standardized. For years, when it came to pictures, that format was, of course, film.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Scrolling Orb</title>
      <link>/2017/10/13/trackball-input-device-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/13/trackball-input-device-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Ever find yourself in a bar with a single arcade machine, and the machine is inevitably not targeting gamers? Like, rather than, say, a fighting game or something iconic like NBA Jam or even Donkey Kong, it’s either a variation of Big Buck Hunter, a bowling game like Silver Strike Bowling, or a golf game like Golden Tee. These games, of course, aim for a wide audience, quite literally in the case of Big Buck Hunter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Eulogy for Eudora</title>
      <link>/2017/09/29/eudora-email-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 07:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/29/eudora-email-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Email is such a pain in the butt. (Hopefully not this specific email.) We’ve been doing everything in our power to fight the influence it has on our lives, to minimize the spam, the marketing, the burden. That burden leads lots of folks to fruitlessly hunt for the perfect email client like I hunt for the perfect word processor. Others have followed the path of least resistance: Either Gmail or Outlook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Early Touchpoint</title>
      <link>/2017/09/22/wacom-tablet-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 07:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/22/wacom-tablet-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: There was once a time when I worked in graphic design—mostly in newspapers—and as a result of that, I owned a tablet. For drawing, of course. It didn’t have a screen. I wasn’t a great artist by any means, but that little Wacom device was a nice functionality add when I was tweaking cutouts and hopping into Photoshop or Illustrator. (I’m pretty good at cutouts if I do say so myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life In Four Colors</title>
      <link>/2017/06/16/igm-pc-cga-graphics-cards-legacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 07:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/16/igm-pc-cga-graphics-cards-legacy/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In our 4K-televised world, in which things (usually) look good at 120 frames per second, it’s strange to think back to points in our history where the graphics weren’t nearly that good—where the visuals took something of a backseat to the graphics getting pumped out. But it wasn’t all that long ago when our graphics were crude, blocky, and very limited in resolution. And part of the reason for this can be pointed at IBM, which prioritized text over imagery on its early PCs, all in an effort to win over business users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Spin Me Right Round, Baby</title>
      <link>/2017/05/31/early-hard-drive-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 07:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/31/early-hard-drive-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Hard drives may be the most fundamental building block of the computer revolution. Hitting the perfect balance between size and cost, it was a defining piece of computer history, one that made our machines more permanent and helped us rethink the way we store information. With a hard drive, we were eventually able to move away from the idea of thinking of our documents in terms of a linear order and a physical space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>86’ed</title>
      <link>/2017/05/19/intel-386-486-trademark-battles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/19/intel-386-486-trademark-battles/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Why did Intel move away from naming its widely used microprocessors after numbers—you know, like the 286 and the 386? They were perfectly succinct, along with easy to remember—what’s not to like? As it turns out, Intel was very much into the idea of using these numbers, and really wanted to stick with it. But legal and trademark-related problems got in the way. The same spirit of reverse-engineering innovation that gave Intel its longtime advantage in the world of desktop computers ultimately cost it the right to hold onto its numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clone Wars</title>
      <link>/2017/05/05/apple-ii-clones-franklin-vtech/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 07:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/05/apple-ii-clones-franklin-vtech/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Often, retrospectives on computer history focus pretty intently on the IBM PC era and how that system’s many clones helped to democratize computing by centering most computing-industry efforts on a single platform—a major breakthrough at the time. But other platforms attracted clones as well—including the Apple II, though the computing giant’s protectionist habits kicked in quickly. And oddly enough, it may have the best thing for everyone involved—including consumers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operating In Obscurity</title>
      <link>/2017/04/21/obscure-operating-systems-os2-qnx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 07:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/04/21/obscure-operating-systems-os2-qnx/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Operating systems are the cockroaches of the digital revolution. They’re everywhere, hiding in low-level crevices, and most of the time, you don’t really notice when they’re there—except, of course, when they draw attention to themselves. (Cough, cough Windows 8 cough.) But most of those operating systems fade from view—except when they don’t. Case in point: The company Arca Noae claims it’s about to launch a brand-new version of IBM’s coulda-been ‘90s contender, OS/2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COBOLed Together</title>
      <link>/2017/04/11/cobol-programmers-cobol-cowboys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 06:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/04/11/cobol-programmers-cobol-cowboys/</guid>
      <description>If you’re a regular reader of Y Combinator’s excellent mini-Reddit aggregator Hacker News (as I am), you start to see some trends arise. Programming languages and frameworks become incredibly popular (Ruby on Rails! Django! Node! Go!), but then start to lose their luster over time as programmers inevitably move onto the next coding innovation.  But the thing is, programming frameworks didn’t used to be this trendy, and some of the really old ones are becoming highly-sought-after in certain sectors because they’re becoming very uncommon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Data</title>
      <link>/2017/03/30/ibm-port-a-punch-card-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 07:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/30/ibm-port-a-punch-card-device/</guid>
      <description>These days, we have a whole lot of options for portably collecting information that needs to be put in a computer. But in 1960, that wasn’t always easy.  Usually, this meant paper—but considering they barely even had working OCR at the time, it also meant a lot of manual entry after the fact.
Fortunately, IBM had a solution to this problem: A portable device called the Port-A-Punch, which allowed workers in the field to create their own punch cards by hand to use for later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seek And Spell</title>
      <link>/2017/03/23/ocr-typography-optical-character-recognition-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 07:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/23/ocr-typography-optical-character-recognition-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: We live in a world where facial recognition has become so sophisticated that we’re being forced to ask very serious ethical questions about it. (In the U.S., the depth of the FBI’s facial-recognition capabilities are raising some serious questions from Congress. In China, it’s being used to detect toilet paper theft. To each country their own.) But I want to take a step back from the big hairy ethical questions and consider how we started on this road—with typography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Soft</title>
      <link>/2017/03/21/dial-up-soft-modem-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 07:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/21/dial-up-soft-modem-history/</guid>
      <description>Dial-up modems were underpowered enough back in the days of AOL, but at the height of their popularity, manufacturers figured out a way to make them even worse.  During the late ‘90s, a spate of companies, including big name modem manufacturers like U.S. Robotics, Motorola, and PCtel, had the idea to replace hardware-based modems, which generally required a separate digital signal processor to manage the dial-up connection, with software-based equivalents, which took this task and put it on top of the CPU already being used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re Gunning For IBM</title>
      <link>/2017/02/15/wang-computers-history-demise/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/02/15/wang-computers-history-demise/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The history of computing is full of stories that follow a specific arc, or a slight variation on it. Here’s the gist: A company has massive success, dominating an entire era of computing. They, understandably, get big in their britches, and fail to consider that their technology may not always be the greatest thing since sliced bread. First, they go into slow decline, then leadership problems pile up and the slow decline happens fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s All In The Cards</title>
      <link>/2017/01/27/pcmcia-pc-card-laptop-expansion-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/27/pcmcia-pc-card-laptop-expansion-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The problem with laptops has, at least in recent years, been one of expandability. Once you buy a machine, you’re generally stuck with it, unless you’re willing to take it apart with repairs that have more in common with surgery than mechanics. Part of this has to do with the complexity of our modern machines, but a bigger part is the fact that, simply, upgradability has become less of a concern for manufacturers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amiga Appreciation</title>
      <link>/2017/01/18/viva-amiga-documentary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/18/viva-amiga-documentary/</guid>
      <description>Love your Amiga: If you’re a longish-time reader of Tedium, you’ll know that we have a lot of appreciation for the Amiga, the Commodore-produced platform, loved by Andy Warhol, that basically set the stage for the visually-graceful computing world we have now.  Which is why the new documentary about the computing platform, Zach Weddington’s Viva Amiga: The Story of a Beautiful Machine is very much on our list of things to watch right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weirdest Ransom Note Ever</title>
      <link>/2017/01/11/joseph-l-popp-aids-ransomware/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/11/joseph-l-popp-aids-ransomware/</guid>
      <description>Back in the ’80s, it was a big deal when a frustrated satellite dish operator overrode the HBO feed for a few minutes on a Saturday night. But late last year, a saga involving a programmer whose family member’s TV set had fallen victim to ransomware shows we haven’t even scratched the surface of TV hacking.  https://twitter.com/darrencauthon/status/813096722989809665
Ransomware has a long and sordid history, though it’s relatively new to television.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Many Lives of Packard Bell</title>
      <link>/2016/12/28/packard-bell-multiple-brand-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/12/28/packard-bell-multiple-brand-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Let’s go back in time about 20 years, to two days after Christmas, 1996. On this day, as I was becoming accustomed to Bush’s second album, millions of families around the United States were unpacking and setting up their first home computers. For those who skipped the Commodore and Apple II eras, who didn’t have a Videotex installed in their televisions, and had no idea who Commander Keen even was, this was the moment in time when they joined the internet revolution, brandishing their their AOL or Hotmail addresses for all the world to see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Annoying Clicking Sound</title>
      <link>/2016/12/07/iomega-zip-disk-click-of-death-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/12/07/iomega-zip-disk-click-of-death-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: As proprietary, non-standardized formats go, Iomega’s Zip drive got a heck of a lot further than most of its competitors. It managed to improve on a format people were used to (the old floppy) just enough that it ensured it’d gain popularity. It fit niches for people who had to share a lot of data. And it even had a sizable base of home users—which was impressive for its time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons From The Video Professor</title>
      <link>/2016/11/16/video-professor-infomercial-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 08:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/11/16/video-professor-infomercial-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Home computers and infomercials were always meant to go together. Here were these devices, arguably the most complex products ever to enter homes in Middle America, and they needed a lot of explaining at first. (Not complicated explanations, mind you. Simple ones.) Enter Video Professor. For two decades, John Scherer made millions by selling educational products to the public, mostly through late-night infomercials and on home-shopping networks like QVC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Original In-App Purchase</title>
      <link>/2016/10/28/shareware-history-legacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 07:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/10/28/shareware-history-legacy/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Before software, purchases generally worked like this: You walked into a store, you bought a physical object, and that object was yours until it became damaged or outdated, and you threw it out. But software, being much smaller in physical space than any commercial object that came before it, wasn&amp;rsquo;t limited by these rules. Data came in bits and bytes, and could be dripped out or distributed in any number of ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Secret Amiga</title>
      <link>/2016/03/30/cable-prevue-channel-secret-amiga/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 07:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/03/30/cable-prevue-channel-secret-amiga/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In terms of finding out what&amp;rsquo;s on the boob tube at any given time, we&amp;rsquo;ve come a long way from the overly condensed pages of TV Guide. In fact, the magazine was already looking awful obsolete in the 1980s and 1990s, when cable systems around the country began dedicating entire channels to listing TV schedules. Eventually, the approach led to the rise of the set-top box, the power-sucking block that serves as the liaison between you and your cable company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Some Noise</title>
      <link>/2016/02/10/creative-sound-blaster-sound-card-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 05:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/02/10/creative-sound-blaster-sound-card-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Before we embraced MP3s as the official noise of the internet (taking the place of screechy modems), it took a while before the synthesized notes of our musical past could be modulated through the inner-workings of a computer. Some of our earliest computers, for example, could only make very basic bleeps and bloops. But in 1989, everything changed when a Singaporean company called Creative Technology hit upon the perfect approach for synthesizing sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A phone book for computers</title>
      <link>/2015/08/12/computer-shopper-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 08:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/12/computer-shopper-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The phone book isn&amp;rsquo;t really anyone&amp;rsquo;s idea of an innovative product, but it definitely had its place on the shelf of many a home before the internet took over. In the late throes of the age of the white pages, however, an unusually large magazine stole the hearts of many a techie, and in the process became something of a bible for people looking to replace their 286 with a 486—and maybe buy a laser printer in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>