<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Word Processors on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/word-processors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Word Processors on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 20:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/word-processors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Love Letter to Gingko</title>
      <link>/2017/06/19/gingko-experimental-word-processor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/19/gingko-experimental-word-processor/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to writing, I think that the biggest problem for a lot of people is properly organizing their ideas. There&amp;rsquo;s just so much to put into a document, and without well-considered organization, it can get a little long, jumbled, and overly ranty. (Overly ranty is bad.)  But that doesn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily mean that there isn&amp;rsquo;t room to rethink the approach. Perhaps you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be writing in a totally linear format—perhaps you need to think in terms of a flow chart, one that is flexible to the whims of your prose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting The Next Word In</title>
      <link>/2016/10/05/word-processors-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 07:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/10/05/word-processors-future/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Word processors are generally kind of boring—they do their job, and that&amp;rsquo;s about it. Most people don&amp;rsquo;t put a ton of second thought into their word processors. As you might have noticed from my rant from a couple of months ago, I&amp;rsquo;m not that kind of person. That rant drew up a lot of conversation, most of it good and interesting. (It did have its critics, but even their comments were interesting!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bare-Metal Writing</title>
      <link>/2016/08/19/bare-metal-writing-word-processor-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 07:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/08/19/bare-metal-writing-word-processor-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: I&amp;rsquo;m writing these opening lines in Markdown, using a Mac app called Focused, one of many attempts to rethink the word processor as a minimalist exercise. Every one of my articles starts out in this app (or at least in John Gruber&amp;rsquo;s neglected gift to the world), and yet, I always find myself looking for another option, periodically launching into a Google deep dive that rarely leads to a better solution.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>