<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publishing on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/publishing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publishing on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 09:15:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/publishing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Straight Flush</title>
      <link>/2018/03/07/uncle-johns-bathroom-reader-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/07/uncle-johns-bathroom-reader-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie from Tedium here with a fresh piece from Andrew Egan, who wants to tell you all about a series of books that come in handy during a certain time of the day … uh, I’ll let him explain it. Thanks Andrew!
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: Book publishing is no stranger to specialty products. From leather-bound editions of classic literature, to coffee table books, publishers will provide anything to take advantage of people’s need to look smart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who’s Who? Who Cares</title>
      <link>/2017/07/19/whos-who-vanity-publishing-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 07:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/19/whos-who-vanity-publishing-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: On an average day floating through the press release service PR Newswire, it’s inevitable that you run into a list of people who are designated as new members of the “Who’s Who” list. The list always varies but the intent is always the same: To give a person notice for their life and career. The problem with these lists is that, in an era where everyone is seemingly notable for something, they seem to amount to a hill of beans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Internet On Dead Trees</title>
      <link>/2017/06/30/90s-internet-books-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 07:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/30/90s-internet-books-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Here&amp;rsquo;s the thing about the internet that is striking from the position of a crate-digger: The crate never ends. It always keeps growing just a little bigger every single second. But that crate has a hole at the bottom. Stuff is falling out just as quickly, and pieces of history that would stick around in meatspace disappear in an instant online. So as a result, there aren&amp;rsquo;t a lot of websites from 1995 that made it through to the present day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Magazine You Can&#39;t Bend</title>
      <link>/2016/02/24/cd-rom-magazines-launch-blender/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 09:11:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/02/24/cd-rom-magazines-launch-blender/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The promise of multimedia technology led creators of all stripes to do particularly crazy things in an effort to seem hip and with the times. The CD-ROM, much like the sound card, was seen as the lynchpin for much of this innovation—as it could hold a large amount of data, making room for audio, video, and interactive features that no piece of paper, glossy or otherwise, could pull off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A phone book for computers</title>
      <link>/2015/08/12/computer-shopper-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 08:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/12/computer-shopper-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The phone book isn&amp;rsquo;t really anyone&amp;rsquo;s idea of an innovative product, but it definitely had its place on the shelf of many a home before the internet took over. In the late throes of the age of the white pages, however, an unusually large magazine stole the hearts of many a techie, and in the process became something of a bible for people looking to replace their 286 with a 486—and maybe buy a laser printer in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.) Learn About Lists 2.) See Item 1</title>
      <link>/2015/05/06/learn-about-lists/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 05:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/06/learn-about-lists/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: David Letterman is retiring soon, and while he didn&amp;rsquo;t invent the list, he probably did more to ensure its pop-culture legacy than anything _BuzzFeed_ could ever hope. Author and Death and Taxes editor-in-chief Brian Abrams, who wrote a book about Letterman&amp;rsquo;s NBC career last year, noted that the idea for Letterman&amp;rsquo;s Top Ten list came as a satire of the then-current obsession with lists in the mass media.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>