<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Super Nes on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/super-nes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Super Nes on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 09:43:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/super-nes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharper Pixels</title>
      <link>/2017/12/01/analogue-super-nt-premium-retro-gaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/01/analogue-super-nt-premium-retro-gaming/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Recently, I had a big problem really put a damper on my retro-gaming experience. After modding my Super NES Classic, I proceeded to play one of my all-time favorite games, The Legend of the Mystical Ninja. I got all the way up to level 5, but when I ran into that level’s boss, something strange happened: The entire system crashed, hard. What happened? Well, the Super NES Classic’s emulator couldn’t handle what was on the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super FX Turbo Mode</title>
      <link>/2017/08/22/star-fox-super-fx-overclocking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 06:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/22/star-fox-super-fx-overclocking/</guid>
      <description>I’m going to come right out and say it: I want a Super NES Classic. I wanted an NES Classic, but that sold out too quickly and the variations on the market cost way too much money, so I have my finger on the trigger for potential pre-orders of the new device, expected to hit this week. I, like most of my other fellow retro geeks, can at least embrace the fact that we still have as much of a shot at getting these mini-consoles right now as we did Pearl Jam tickets circa 1994.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is My Top Secret Room</title>
      <link>/2017/03/14/zelda-chris-houlihan-secret-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 06:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/14/zelda-chris-houlihan-secret-room/</guid>
      <description>These days, The Legend of Zelda is getting a whole lot of well-deserved extra attention as a franchise, thanks to Breath of the Wild being one of the Nintendo Switch’s launch titles.  (Side note: We totally covered Bitrex months before Nintendo started covering its Switch cartridges with it. Yes, we’re ahead of the curve.)
But as interesting as Breath of the Wild is, I wanted to spend a minute talking about one of the weirdest things ever to appear on a Nintendo cartridge, ever, let alone a Legend of Zelda game.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>