<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sonic the Hedgehog on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/sonic-the-hedgehog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sonic the Hedgehog on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/sonic-the-hedgehog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lost (And Found) Levels</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/hidden-content-video-games-cutting-room-floor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/hidden-content-video-games-cutting-room-floor/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: It took a while for us to culturally admit it, but video games are a form of art on the level of many films—and that means that game developers are very much auteurs in the way that film directors are. (Or, depending on the game, schlockmeisters.) But as anyone who has ever used a Game Genie could tell you, there are things that developers don&amp;rsquo;t want you to see, at a basic level far removed from a mere easter egg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trapper Keeper Contraband</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/trapper-keeper-contraband-decline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/trapper-keeper-contraband-decline/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Editor’s note: With the idea of treating my work as something of a living document, I sometimes update old Tedium issues in an effort to keep them up to date. When I was updating this one, though, I noticed something weird, and as a result, I wrote a much bigger update than usual. Read on, pals.
[big]Today in Tedium: Schools are weird. They get super-political about the strangest things, because kids tend to get hung up about stupid things and those stupid things tend to affect what happens in the classroom.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>