<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Novelties on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/novelties/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Novelties on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 09:45:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/novelties/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh? Haven’t You Heard?</title>
      <link>/2018/02/02/surfin-bird-song-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/02/surfin-bird-song-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with another piece from David Buck, who knows the truth about the Surfin’ Bird. Previously, he was talkin’ Y2K.
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: In a recent Tedium piece, Ernie posed the question: “Can one become nostalgic for abrasive noises?” He was referring to alarm clocks, but that got me thinking about songs others may find annoying or abrasive like “It’s Halloween” by the Shaggs, just about anything by the Legendary Stardust Cowboy, and an old surf song that seems to keep popping up in my life—“Surfin’ Bird.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terrible Digital Trinkets</title>
      <link>/2017/01/13/terrible-novelty-usb-drives/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/13/terrible-novelty-usb-drives/</guid>
      <description>Not too long ago, I acquired a pretty useful USB drive that is a combination of large and small. It’s large because it has 128 gigabytes of storage, which comes in handy for my experiences testing Chromium OS and Ubuntu on my MacBook Pro. It’s small because it’s designed to recede in my laptop. It’s about the size of the tip of my finger. It’s, of course, incredibly easy to lose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Taboola of the 1930s</title>
      <link>/2016/06/22/johnson-smith-company-taboola-outbrain-advertising/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/06/22/johnson-smith-company-taboola-outbrain-advertising/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: When I see people complaining about the images and links shared through the &amp;ldquo;content discovery&amp;rdquo; platform Taboola and its cousin Outbrain—something I admittedly have been known to do—I inevitably find myself drawn to the &amp;ldquo;taboo&amp;rdquo; part of the Israeli company&amp;rsquo;s name. Because, if you think about it, it&amp;rsquo;s a really good descriptor of the images you see adding noise to nearly every large site on the internet. They show ways of life and images you wish didn&amp;rsquo;t exist—images of stuff that shouldn&amp;rsquo;t exist, if there was a God.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>