<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scams on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/scams/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scams on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 07:18:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/scams/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chinese Robocall Blues</title>
      <link>/2018/05/16/spam-robocalls-history-comparison/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 07:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/16/spam-robocalls-history-comparison/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Recently, I got a phone call from a number I’d never seen before. In other words, an average day. But this call was weird, largely because it was decidedly not for me. It sounded like Chinese, which was confirmed when I had the bright idea of holding my phone against my laptop’s microphone so Google Translate could make it out. Suddenly, it became slightly more clear: The message was a robocall—a strange one at that, one that suggested some sort of immigration trouble for the caller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unsettled</title>
      <link>/2018/05/01/ticketmaster-live-nation-free-ticket-settlement-boycott/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 19:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/01/ticketmaster-live-nation-free-ticket-settlement-boycott/</guid>
      <description>Nearly a quarter-century ago, Pearl Jam—which had become the biggest band in the world around this time effectively by ignoring the music industry orthodoxy of the time—decided to take on live music’s biggest middleman.  It probably hurt their career to take aim at Ticketmaster, which had become known for charging expensive service fees on every ticket it sold. But the politically minded band did, going so far as to file a complaint with the Justice Department and speak in front of Congress about the problem, something rock bands don’t usually do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Weaponized Slogan</title>
      <link>/2017/02/02/weird-scam-calls-verizon-slogan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 05:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/02/02/weird-scam-calls-verizon-slogan/</guid>
      <description>A not-so-innocent question: For years, Verizon sold millions of people on the promise of solid cellular phone signals with a simple question. “Can you hear me now?” asked Paul Marcarelli, the living pitchman who spent years in anonymity because of his ties to the brand. (He’s much happier with Sprint.)  But that question, so innocent-seeming, has become weaponized in the hands of a bunch of scamming robocallers. The Better Business Bureau reported this week that scammers were calling unsuspecting people, asking people on the other end of the line if they can hear them, then hanging up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Pyramids Collapse</title>
      <link>/2015/06/19/anatomy-scams-when-pyramids-collapse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 07:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/19/anatomy-scams-when-pyramids-collapse/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It&amp;rsquo;s the oldest scam in the book, and people fall for it all the freaking time. Pyramid schemes of all shapes and sizes have been bilking people out of their hard-earned money for generations, and you&amp;rsquo;re probably gonna get screwed out of your hard-earned money before you even realize it. Today&amp;rsquo;s Tedium is all about scams that leave scars way deeper than all the money stolen. — Ernie @ Tedium</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>