<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>World War Ii on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/world-war-ii/</link>
    <description>Recent content in World War Ii on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/world-war-ii/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Tourism</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/dark-tourism-dresden-slaughterhouse-five/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/dark-tourism-dresden-slaughterhouse-five/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Editor’s note: After doing such a great job with his last piece, I brought back Andrew Egan for another post. Check it out.
[big]Today in Tedium: Governments, or more specifically, their tourism boards are usually enthusiastic to promote any noteworthy site or event possible. This has lead to more than a few missteps, of course. Like the recent &amp;ldquo;Syria: Always Beautiful&amp;rdquo; campaign touting the country’s beaches. Come for the Mediterranean scenery, please ignore the raging civil war.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Copy?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/walkie-talkie-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/walkie-talkie-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: It seems so quaint now, but there was a time when the walkie-talkie was the coolest possible toy you could own (barring, perhaps, Power Wheels). But the invention of the walkie-talkie, which is often used by consumers as either a fun tool or a simple communications device, is a great reminder that this technology used to be so much more fundamental for both businesses and the military.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drip And Drive</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/blood-donation-bloodmobile-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/blood-donation-bloodmobile-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Today in Tedium: Recently, my wife has really gotten into putting on blood drives, in no small part because of their ability to save lives—by making the iron-laden resources already running through our veins and arteries available to people who need them just a little bit more. These blood drives, quite often, happen in public places. You don’t have to go to the Red Cross; the Red Cross will come to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math &#43; The Mechanics</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/curta-calculator-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/curta-calculator-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: We think of computers as being purely digital objects—computational beasts that work with abstracted collections of 1s and 0s. As complexity increased, so did the tactics to making the computing devices smaller, to the point where we can shove one in our skin as if that’s something we wanna do. Of course, computers are reliant on power these days, but there was a time when computers didn’t need things like batteries, because they weren’t electronic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>