<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pop Stars on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/pop-stars/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pop Stars on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 07:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/pop-stars/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Members Only</title>
      <link>/2018/06/29/non-performing-band-members-coldplay-grateful-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/29/non-performing-band-members-coldplay-grateful-dead/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: “Look at the stars, look how they shine for you, and all the things that you do, non-performing band member …” I personally gained a major distaste for Coldplay sometime in the early naughts, when I failed to understand the appeal of “Clocks,” despite having enjoyed Parachutes. Perhaps it’s for that reason I never realized that Coldplay has five members, that I assumed they were a quartet. Certainly there are four members on stage actually playing the songs, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purple Copyright Eater</title>
      <link>/2016/04/22/prince-troubled-relationship-with-copyright/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 04:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/04/22/prince-troubled-relationship-with-copyright/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In losing Prince Rogers Nelson, we&amp;rsquo;re losing a lot more than a idiosyncratic pop star who defined an entire New Power Generation. We&amp;rsquo;re losing the last link between our current remix-heavy culture (which, let&amp;rsquo;s face it, this newsletter wouldn&amp;rsquo;t exist without) and an era when ownership of creative work was treated as an end-all-be-all. Here was a guy who started the internet era sporting a name that literally could not be searched, who forced lawsuits over barely-noticeable renditions of his songs in YouTube clips, and who made a lot of creative stuff that nobody will likely ever see.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>