<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Diaspora on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/diaspora/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Diaspora on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 07:48:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/diaspora/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hot Pocket Diaspora</title>
      <link>/2016/05/27/hot-pocket-history-iran-jewish-diaspora/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 07:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/05/27/hot-pocket-history-iran-jewish-diaspora/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Laugh all you want, but Hot Pockets are the ultimate modern food. Incredibly easy to eat and simple to cook, they cleverly were designed to be easy to microwave and completely, utterly portable. Less known about the Hot Pocket, however, is its origins, which are the product of a duo of Iranian-born Jewish immigrants who arguably popularized the concept of microwavable frozen meals. Jim Gaffigan hates these things, but we admit something of a respect for them as a bottom-up success story (that just happens to be incredibly unhealthy).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diaspora: Not just a forgotten social network</title>
      <link>/2015/05/15/how-a-diaspora-forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/15/how-a-diaspora-forms/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: North America is a melting pot of the highest order, and it&amp;rsquo;s something that&amp;rsquo;s best exemplified by our junk food—a stew made of Taco Bell, ranch dressing, Sriracha, ramen noodles, and a whole lot of ground beef. But despite our disparate histories and tastes, we all made it here—some assimilating more than others. In today&amp;rsquo;s issue of Tedium, we consider some of the more unusual cultural pockets that have put a stake into the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>