<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Compact Discs on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/compact-discs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Compact Discs on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 09:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/compact-discs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ban The Box</title>
      <link>/2018/02/07/compact-disc-longbox-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/07/compact-disc-longbox-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Thirty years ago, the record industry decided it didn’t want to be the record industry anymore. It wanted to be the CD industry, with maybe some cassettes on the side. It was getting rid of all that vinyl! This situation, oddly enough, may just repeat in 2018—except, this time, not by choice. Best Buy is about to throw out its record racks entirely; Target is making the idea of selling physical CDs less financially advantageous for record labels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hide And Seek</title>
      <link>/2017/11/10/hidden-tracks-album-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 09:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/10/hidden-tracks-album-history/</guid>
      <description>Editor’s note: Tonight’s issue is a slightly expanded rerun of a classic issue of Tedium with some additional info added in spots where it makes sense. Enjoy!
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: We gained a lot when albums went fully digital, but we also lost a bunch of stuff along the way. Among the things we lost: Record sleeves, media towers, and Tower Records. We have digital equivalents of all these things, so it&amp;rsquo;s not like we necessarily miss them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Discs Die</title>
      <link>/2017/02/03/disc-rot-phenomenon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/02/03/disc-rot-phenomenon/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Often, it looks like a coffee stain—a noticeable discoloration that for whatever reason you can’t get rid of. Sometimes, it looks like tiny pin pricks on the surface. And there are other times when the whole thing changes color. In any case, when you run into what’s known as “disc rot,” you’re out a great album or an interesting movie. It’s a serious situation, whether you’re a digital archivist or simply someone who wants to watch a movie on a weird format like a Laserdisc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Magazine You Can&#39;t Bend</title>
      <link>/2016/02/24/cd-rom-magazines-launch-blender/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 09:11:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/02/24/cd-rom-magazines-launch-blender/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The promise of multimedia technology led creators of all stripes to do particularly crazy things in an effort to seem hip and with the times. The CD-ROM, much like the sound card, was seen as the lynchpin for much of this innovation—as it could hold a large amount of data, making room for audio, video, and interactive features that no piece of paper, glossy or otherwise, could pull off.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>