<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nintendo on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/nintendo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nintendo on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 07:13:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/nintendo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ballad of Yo! Noid</title>
      <link>/2018/08/17/video-games-advertising-mascots-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 07:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/17/video-games-advertising-mascots-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with a piece from the Tedium archives about Madison Avenue’s infiltration of classic video games, which is legitimately a thing that happened.
Today in Tedium: Here&amp;rsquo;s a challenge for you: Take your favorite video game of the &amp;lsquo;90s and don&amp;rsquo;t think about it in terms of the quality of the game, its graphical quality, or its replayability—especially if it&amp;rsquo;s a game based on an existing license. Instead, think of that game in terms of it merely being a vessel to market another product: say, a movie like Terminator 2, a toy like a Barbie doll, or a musical act like Aerosmith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Absolutely Brilliant!</title>
      <link>/2018/06/15/codemasters-history-nes-nintendo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/15/codemasters-history-nes-nintendo/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie from Tedium here with another piece from David Buck, who’s become something of a megafan of a video game company that wasn’t afraid to break the rules.
Today in Tedium: Throughout the years of the original Nintendo Entertainment System’s life, several companies produced games for the system. The licensed games—titles sporting the official Nintendo seal of quality—came from companies like Konami and Capcom, complete with Nintendo approved hardware, marketing and support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What if Tedium … Had Lyrics?</title>
      <link>/2018/06/14/brentalfloss-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 06:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/14/brentalfloss-interview/</guid>
      <description>As our readers are now undoubtedly aware, there are two things I’m incredibly interested in—unique types of music and the history/technical aspects/playing the games of the original Nintendo Entertainment System (I’m also really into miniatures, FWIW). Knowing this, it was only a matter of time before I discovered someone who combined these two interests into one. Unlike U2, circa 1987, I found what I was looking for almost a decade ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Still Rocks</title>
      <link>/2018/05/18/nintendo-nes-chiptune-music-scene/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/18/nintendo-nes-chiptune-music-scene/</guid>
      <description>Hey all, Ernie here with another piece from David Buck, who&amp;rsquo;s currently in the midst of following his Nintendo muse. Feel free to follow along with him!
Today in Tedium: Gamers of a certain age may remember the opening notes of Super Mario Bros as well—or perhaps better than—any other song from their childhoods. As the pack-in title for the original Nintendo Entertainment System, the game was likely the first exposure to video games many of us had outside of arcades and Atari.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Just Nostalgia</title>
      <link>/2018/04/11/nes-homebrew-scene-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 07:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/11/nes-homebrew-scene-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with another great piece from David Buck, who we last saw talking about Oingo Boingo. Tonight, he’s got something else brewin’.
Today in Tedium: Growing up in the era of the Nintendo Entertainment System, I always wanted to create my own NES game. I scribbled ideas in notebooks, mapped out levels on graph paper and spent countless hours composing my own MIDI-based soundtracks to games that didn’t exist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australian Rules Nintendo</title>
      <link>/2017/12/28/nintendo-beam-software-australia-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 09:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/28/nintendo-beam-software-australia-history/</guid>
      <description>Recently I found myself hanging out in a retro video game store, looking at the cheapo bin at the various titles for the NES and other systems. If you’ve done something similar in the recent past, you’ll know that the cheapo bin will inevitably be filled with lots of sports games. It doesn’t matter if the sports games are well-regarded or even iconic—for whatever reason gamers just don’t want to buy them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modem Madness</title>
      <link>/2017/09/19/video-game-modem-experiments/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 07:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/19/video-game-modem-experiments/</guid>
      <description>A couple of months ago, I gave a little notice to Sega’s early attempt to tie cable connections with video games, the Sega Channel. Certainly, it was the most interesting communications-related experiment that Sega had formulated that year. But as it turns out, it was probably not Sega’s most interesting experiment involving communications. Far from it.  Now, to start off, Sega is famously a company that, during the Genesis/Mega Drive era at least, was not opposed to add-ons for this device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“It&#39;s Weird That it Didn&#39;t Seem Weirder”</title>
      <link>/2017/05/04/nesticle-history-extras-part-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 07:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/04/nesticle-history-extras-part-two/</guid>
      <description>“A Bloodlust game was clearly a Bloodlust game,” Bloodlust visual artist Ethan Petty told me. “Some people loved it. Some people thought it was visual torture. I was with the second group, but hey—we had to keep creating. It was what we loved.”  Of the many fascinating things about Bloodlust Software and its emulators—NESticle in particular, but also Genecyst and Callus—was that there was a distinctive visual style that went along with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Extra Serving</title>
      <link>/2017/05/02/nesticle-history-extras-part-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 06:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/02/nesticle-history-extras-part-one/</guid>
      <description>What a day! My article on Vice&amp;rsquo;s Motherboard this week about the history of NESticle—the Nintendo Entertainment System emulator whose early success paved the way for people to play vintage games on their computers whenever they want—took a while to get past the finish line, and came only after I gave the piece a haircut.  To augment the story, I’m gonna spend the next couple of Daily Tedium pieces highlighting things I hoped to get into the original piece but were trimmed out because the piece was getting a bit lengthy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Warped Mindset</title>
      <link>/2017/04/19/nintendo-times-warp-zone-nes-coverage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 20:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/04/19/nintendo-times-warp-zone-nes-coverage/</guid>
      <description>What if we reported on the past like it was happening in the present day—not reflecting on it nostalgically like I do at Tedium, but literally trying to cover the past as if you had no knowledge of the future?  It sounds like an odd thought exercise, but in reality, it’s a whole lot of fun, based on the website Nintendo Times. Since 2015, the writer and blogger Craig Majaski, who cut his teeth at the long-running gaming site Gaming Age, has been editing and putting together a site in which 30-year-old discussions and interviews about the early days of the Nintendo Entertainment System are published as if they’re happening in real time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is My Top Secret Room</title>
      <link>/2017/03/14/zelda-chris-houlihan-secret-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 06:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/14/zelda-chris-houlihan-secret-room/</guid>
      <description>These days, The Legend of Zelda is getting a whole lot of well-deserved extra attention as a franchise, thanks to Breath of the Wild being one of the Nintendo Switch’s launch titles.  (Side note: We totally covered Bitrex months before Nintendo started covering its Switch cartridges with it. Yes, we’re ahead of the curve.)
But as interesting as Breath of the Wild is, I wanted to spend a minute talking about one of the weirdest things ever to appear on a Nintendo cartridge, ever, let alone a Legend of Zelda game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reverse-Engineering The Industry</title>
      <link>/2017/03/10/video-games-reverse-engineering-tengen-accolade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/10/video-games-reverse-engineering-tengen-accolade/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: When it comes to video game consoles, the manufacturers don’t like it when you bend the rules. But it happens anyway. Technically inclined individuals inevitably want to bend the platforms to their will, despite platform owners that want to protect their massive investments, and aren’t afraid to resort to lawsuits to get their way. There are plenty of cases like this, most infamously the case of the Game Genie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You Not Entertained?</title>
      <link>/2017/02/24/in-flight-entertainment-system-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/02/24/in-flight-entertainment-system-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: There was a time when in-flight entertainment was better than anything you could actually bring onto a plane. That time has long passed, and some airlines are looking to get rid of seat-back screens, in favor of letting you use whatever screen you have with you—while making the WiFi better so you’d actually want to do that. Odds are that not many people are going to miss those screens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a Wonderful World</title>
      <link>/2016/09/09/worlds-of-wonder-teddy-ruxpin-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/09/09/worlds-of-wonder-teddy-ruxpin-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: If you grew up in the &amp;lsquo;80s, you already you probably know this, but that decade&amp;rsquo;s toy industry was a fascinating place. At this juncture, parents were already used to having to get batteries for their kids&amp;rsquo; toys, and at the same time, primitive computing technology was just getting cheap enough that it could be integrated into those toys. Some companies, like Tiger Electronics, doubled down on the cheap silicon and thrived.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lost (And Found) Levels</title>
      <link>/2016/06/17/hidden-content-video-games-cutting-room-floor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 07:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/06/17/hidden-content-video-games-cutting-room-floor/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It took a while for us to culturally admit it, but video games are a form of art on the level of many films—and that means that game developers are very much auteurs in the way that film directors are. (Or, depending on the game, schlockmeisters.) But as anyone who has ever used a Game Genie could tell you, there are things that developers don&amp;rsquo;t want you to see, at a basic level far removed from a mere easter egg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ballad of Yo! Noid</title>
      <link>/2016/05/25/video-games-advertising-mascots/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2016 05:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/05/25/video-games-advertising-mascots/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Here&amp;rsquo;s a challenge for you: Take your favorite video game of the &amp;lsquo;90s and don&amp;rsquo;t think about it in terms of the quality of the game, its graphical quality, or its replayability—especially if it&amp;rsquo;s a game based on an existing license. Instead, think of that game in terms of it merely being a vessel to market another product: say, a movie like Terminator 2, a toy like a Barbie doll, or a musical act like Aerosmith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Game Genie Generation</title>
      <link>/2015/07/01/the-game-genie-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/07/01/the-game-genie-generation/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: For kids of a certain age, the Game Genie was a life-changer. Literally. It could change the number of lives you had in whatever cartridge you put it on, as well as do a bunch of other crazy things to the game you were playing. It provided a thrill that we&amp;rsquo;ve kinda gotten away from as video games have grown more complex, but the device leaves behind a rich legacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8-Bit Archaeology</title>
      <link>/2015/02/04/8-bit-archaeology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/04/8-bit-archaeology/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Here&amp;rsquo;s something you probably don&amp;rsquo;t know about me. For a couple years in the late-&amp;lsquo;90s and early 2000s, I got my sea legs in writing from a little site called Zophar&amp;rsquo;s Domain, a console emulation enthusiast site. At the time, ZD held a kind of legendary status among retro gamers, and though it&amp;rsquo;s aged some, it&amp;rsquo;s still around. (Here&amp;rsquo;s what it looked like when I was there.) I&amp;rsquo;m not really much of a gamer anymore, but this stuff still holds a place in my heart.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>