<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vintage Technology on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/vintage-technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vintage Technology on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/vintage-technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Back To The Shack</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/radio-shack-bankruptcy-auction-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/radio-shack-bankruptcy-auction-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: For many reasons, largely related to a shifting business model incompatible with modern tech needs, a whole generation of people saw RadioShack as less a store for tinkerers and more a place to buy commodity tech products. It was a business model that fell out of sync with the enthusiast community that once championed its products, and the twice-bankrupt RadioShack has been paying the price for that pivot ever since.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall Of Voodoo</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/3dfx-history-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/3dfx-history-failure/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Today’s startup companies seem to have a certain arc to them—they get some seed funding, they launch, they draw some interest for their good idea, they keep growing, and maybe they become a part of the fabric of our lives … or a part of the fabric of a significantly larger company. Strangely, 3Dfx didn’t so much draw interest as blow the lid off of a trend that redefined how we think of video games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Right Track, Wrong Station</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/kartrak-railroad-barcode-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/kartrak-railroad-barcode-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox] [big]Today in Tedium: Trying to codify and organize things is really hard. Case in point: When Amazon tried to launch a cashier-free grocery store concept late last year, the company saw a lot of problems crop up when too many customers used the store at the same time. On a macro level, the railroad industry once faced similar problems with automatically tracking things—a problem they started working on 60 years ago, without the benefits of modern innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Persistence</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/sgi-collector-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/sgi-collector-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey all, Ernie here with a recent piece of mine that also showed up in Motherboard. In case you haven&amp;rsquo;t read it yet, it&amp;rsquo;s a good one and highlights both SGI and the the excellent community IRIX.cc. Read on, and hope you dig!
[big]Today in Tedium: Recently, I was faced with an unusual question about a piece of hardware that very few people have ever used. The question: What makes a giant workstation, one that once cost as much as a house when it was first produced in the early ‘90s and makes as much noise as a vacuum, so appealing to a 16-year-old?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>