<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Medicine on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/medicine/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Medicine on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 07:40:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/medicine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Drip And Drive</title>
      <link>/2018/03/21/blood-donation-bloodmobile-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/21/blood-donation-bloodmobile-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Recently, my wife has really gotten into putting on blood drives, in no small part because of their ability to save lives—by making the iron-laden resources already running through our veins and arteries available to people who need them just a little bit more. These blood drives, quite often, happen in public places. You don’t have to go to the Red Cross; the Red Cross will come to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Not Trust</title>
      <link>/2017/12/05/do-not-resuscitate-tattoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/05/do-not-resuscitate-tattoo/</guid>
      <description>A tattoo probably isn’t a binding legal document, but it certainly seems like a convincing argument. Clearly you must believe what you tattoo on yourself if you’re willing to go to that level of permanence, right?  But a recent saga involving a patient at a Miami hospital proved that question is a little more fraught than it seems. Doctors at Jackson Memorial Hospital, located at the University of Miami, were presented with a unconscious 70-year-old man who had a “Do Not Resuscitate” tattoo, along with his apparent signature, emblazoned on his chest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Case Of Emergency</title>
      <link>/2017/06/21/911-emergency-system-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 07:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/21/911-emergency-system-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Of all the things William Shatner has done in his career—captain of the starship USS Enterprise, veteran police officer, totally-game muse for Ben Folds, fairly good tweeter for being 86 years old—the one thing that&amp;rsquo;s stuck with me the most is his years on Rescue 911, the early reality show that was America&amp;rsquo;s Most Wanted (mostly) without the crime and Unsolved Mysteries with the solutions laid out clear as day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brand Indigestion</title>
      <link>/2016/02/12/xifaxan-pharmaceutical-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 09:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/02/12/xifaxan-pharmaceutical-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Mascots can be great ways to promote a product, but sometimes they&amp;rsquo;re full of crap. The Xifaxan intestine, which I&amp;rsquo;ve been going on about for months now, fits into the latter category. Xifaxan, if you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar, is a medication for irritable bowel syndrome. Some marketing company somewhere got paid millions of dollars to create an animated character that runs around ready to lose its … y&amp;rsquo;know, every time it turns a corner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Drugs Don&#39;t Work</title>
      <link>/2016/01/27/alternative-medicine-interest/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2016 04:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/01/27/alternative-medicine-interest/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Does meditation make for a good replacement to, y&amp;rsquo;know, going to a doctor? That doctor may tell you that skipping the normal treatment isn&amp;rsquo;t a good idea, but those without health insurance have increasingly embraced alternative medicine as a replacement for the more expensive stuff. A new Centers for Disease Control and Prevention study found that people without insurance between 2002 and 2012 were more likely to give alternative medicine offerings a spin, while those with insurance were just as indifferent to alternative medicine as always.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This&#39;ll Blow You Away</title>
      <link>/2015/08/19/hand-dryer-dyson-airblade-xlerator/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 07:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/19/hand-dryer-dyson-airblade-xlerator/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: if you&amp;rsquo;ve been reading us for a while, you might notice a common theme in the pieces we send out to you guys. Often, our strangest issues take things common (but mundane), and discover a secret history hiding under your nose. From belly buttons to bandages to veggie burgers, no subject is too mundane for us. If you use it, there&amp;rsquo;s probably a great story as to how it got there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This one&#39;s for the wounded</title>
      <link>/2015/05/20/history-of-bandages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/20/history-of-bandages/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Blood is a terrible thing to waste, and for centuries, the ways to stop blood from leaving the body were inefficient at best and not exactly easy to use. But one day, a guy spotted a problem that his wife was having and came up with one of the most brilliant solutions for solving simple injuries that the world had ever seen. And we’ve only kept innovating from there.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>