<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wikipedia on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/wikipedia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wikipedia on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 07:04:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/wikipedia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>By Our Powers Combined …</title>
      <link>/2018/06/01/webring-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 07:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/01/webring-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: These days, social media tends to take a specific form—basically, you share content on a platform owned by someone else, who profits off your data and attention span. (No, this is not a piece about GDPR. I. Promise.) The idea of a truly federated social network that brings together individuals but is unburdened by the big guy, is still relatively uncommon. (I’m on Mastodon, though. Are you?) Recently, one social network that did a good job of promoting the little guy, StumbleUpon, announced it was shutting down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burrowing A Gopher Hole</title>
      <link>/2017/06/23/modern-day-gopher-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 07:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/23/modern-day-gopher-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Every time I use pieces of the early internet, I get this warm feeling in my chest. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to describe, but I imagine it&amp;rsquo;s a feeling not unlike the feeling that went through the crowd during the Sex Pistols concert at Manchester&amp;rsquo;s Lesser Free Trade Hall on June 4, 1976. There&amp;rsquo;s a sense of purity and simplicity there that is hard to recapture through other means—the sense that I&amp;rsquo;m witnessing something culturally important that, in its own way, could change the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Big Data Jukebox</title>
      <link>/2016/09/21/allmusic-database-historic-importance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/09/21/allmusic-database-historic-importance/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Discovering new kinds of music is easier than ever, something we can credit Napster for—along with its later legal followers, particularly Spotify, Pandora, and Apple Music. (Oh, and eMusic. That site was great back in the day.) But having all this music at our fingertips was only part of the equation—we needed to be armed with information. I think I realized that point during the early 2000s, when I found myself in the music section of a Barnes &amp;amp; Noble store.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>