<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Science on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Science on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 07:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuck On You</title>
      <link>/2017/03/22/suction-cups-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/22/suction-cups-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It was the cup that comical YouTube unboxing videos were made for. Last year, the Mighty Mug, a drink receptacle that’s designed to not fall down under normal circumstances, gained a lot of attention from video makers the world over because of its one weird trick. Unboxer extraordinaire Lamarr Wilson, for example, was so freaked out by this cup that he took a baseball bat to it. (That did the trick, by the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live and Let Dye</title>
      <link>/2015/08/26/food-coloring-dye-safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/26/food-coloring-dye-safety/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Did you hear the news? They&amp;rsquo;re taking the color out of Trix. The General Mills cereal is one of the most recent victims of a move towards more natural food, and in an effort to appease the suddenly health-conscious public, the company will be removing some of the artificial coloring from Trix and all of its other cereals. &amp;ldquo;We wanted to make sure they were still fun vibrant colors that we are providing and the fruity flavor that kids expect,&amp;rdquo; cereal developer Kate Gallager told Good Morning America of the move back in June.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Literally Navel-Gazing</title>
      <link>/2015/05/13/were-literally-navel-gazing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/13/were-literally-navel-gazing/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It&amp;rsquo;s the one thing that separates humans from androids. Like the appendix, it&amp;rsquo;s functionally useless—minus the period before you&amp;rsquo;re actually born, when it&amp;rsquo;s pretty much the most important part of your body. Unlike the appendix, it&amp;rsquo;s visible and easy to spot. It, of course, is the belly button—one of the most-common but least-discussed parts of the human body. (Well, unless you&amp;rsquo;re Taylor Swift.) Innie or outie? The answer to that question could very well define your life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>