<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Toilet on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/toilet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Toilet on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/toilet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Internet&#39;s Final Frontier</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/smart-bathroom-technology-toilets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/smart-bathroom-technology-toilets/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Thanks to the ever-shrinking nature of our electronics, the internet can go literally anywhere. I mean anywhere. It fits in your bag, appears on your television set, shows up on your desk, it makes a great window into your fridge, and even appears in your pocket. And since it fits in your pocket, that means you can take it inside the bathroom, making it a worthy replacement for a certain series of books we covered earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toilet Duck Dynasty</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/toilet-duck-design-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/toilet-duck-design-history/</guid>
      <description>[big]It’s not easy to come up with a product that’s built around a completely, utterly unique design. Especially involving a topic as unflattering as cleaning a toilet.[/big]
But in the early 1980s, a man named Walter Düring had such a moment. The Swiss man’s company, Düring AG, had made a name for itself with the concept of decalcification, based on a formula his mother, Maria, came up with. But it was in the early 1980s that the firm had come up with something truly successful on a mainstream stage: A uniquely shaped nozzle that could spray decalcifiers into obscure crevices.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>