<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music History on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/music-history/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music History on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 07:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/music-history/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Maybe You’ve Been Brainwashed Too</title>
      <link>/2018/10/10/new-radicals-gregg-alexander-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/10/new-radicals-gregg-alexander-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Two decades ago this month, a couple of things happened in the world of music that forever shaped the way I thought about it. One, the Barenaked Ladies scored a number-one hit on the Billboard Hot 100 with “One Week,” and a band called The New Radicals released their first and only album, *Maybe You’ve Been Brainwashed Too*—whose lead single, “You Get What You Give,” would turn the band into the perfect one-hit wonder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unsettled</title>
      <link>/2018/05/01/ticketmaster-live-nation-free-ticket-settlement-boycott/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 19:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/01/ticketmaster-live-nation-free-ticket-settlement-boycott/</guid>
      <description>Nearly a quarter-century ago, Pearl Jam—which had become the biggest band in the world around this time effectively by ignoring the music industry orthodoxy of the time—decided to take on live music’s biggest middleman.  It probably hurt their career to take aim at Ticketmaster, which had become known for charging expensive service fees on every ticket it sold. But the politically minded band did, going so far as to file a complaint with the Justice Department and speak in front of Congress about the problem, something rock bands don’t usually do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mystic Knights of the Movie Soundtrack</title>
      <link>/2018/03/15/oingo-boingo-pop-culture-appearances/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 07:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/15/oingo-boingo-pop-culture-appearances/</guid>
      <description>Before Danny Elfman became the go-to guy for scoring great films, his band Oingo Boingo was a mid-&amp;lsquo;80s go-to for soundtrack contributions. This ensured that, even as Elfman moved away from the band, Oingo Boingo would carry a massive pop-culture footprint.  &amp;ldquo;I think Oingo&amp;rsquo;s music is good for the audience for those films; the people will relate to it,&amp;rdquo; Elfman said of the phenomenon, according to the Encyclopedia of Pop, Rock &amp;amp; Soul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Wave Titans</title>
      <link>/2018/03/14/oingo-boingo-danny-elfman-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 07:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/14/oingo-boingo-danny-elfman-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with another piece from David Buck. Last we saw of him, he was talking to Tom Bodett. Tonight, he’s obsessing over an iconic West Coast band. Read on; it&amp;rsquo;s worth it.
Today in Tedium: If you’re a fan of director Tim Burton, you may recognize the name Danny Elfman. If you’re a Nightmare before Christmas fan, you may even recognize his voice. But, did you know he started his music career with a band called The Mystic Knights of the Oingo Boingo (later just Oingo Boingo)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Beautiful Neighborhood</title>
      <link>/2018/02/14/ernest-hood-neighborhoods/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 06:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/14/ernest-hood-neighborhoods/</guid>
      <description>Back in 2004, the Arcade Fire released one of the greatest musical documents of our still-young 21st century, an album titled Funeral that was built around a series of four songs, each titled “Neighborhood.” Those songs, with their high tension and genuine pain, evoked something both local and emotional. They became huge. They moved far beyond neighborhoods, into the stratosphere.  Nearly three decades earlier, Portland, Oregon jazz musician Ernest Hood wasn’t aiming for the same kind of emotions with his album Neighborhoods, but he did hit on something very local and emotional in his own right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ban The Box</title>
      <link>/2018/02/07/compact-disc-longbox-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/07/compact-disc-longbox-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Thirty years ago, the record industry decided it didn’t want to be the record industry anymore. It wanted to be the CD industry, with maybe some cassettes on the side. It was getting rid of all that vinyl! This situation, oddly enough, may just repeat in 2018—except, this time, not by choice. Best Buy is about to throw out its record racks entirely; Target is making the idea of selling physical CDs less financially advantageous for record labels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh? Haven’t You Heard?</title>
      <link>/2018/02/02/surfin-bird-song-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/02/surfin-bird-song-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with another piece from David Buck, who knows the truth about the Surfin’ Bird. Previously, he was talkin’ Y2K.
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: In a recent Tedium piece, Ernie posed the question: “Can one become nostalgic for abrasive noises?” He was referring to alarm clocks, but that got me thinking about songs others may find annoying or abrasive like “It’s Halloween” by the Shaggs, just about anything by the Legendary Stardust Cowboy, and an old surf song that seems to keep popping up in my life—“Surfin’ Bird.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primitive Streaming Gods</title>
      <link>/2018/01/31/legal-music-streaming-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/31/legal-music-streaming-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: This week, the music industry had a pretty good reason to cheer, and not just because of the Grammys. They won big in Washington, after the the United States Copyright Royalty Board ruled in favor of songwriters that felt like they had gotten the short end of the stick from Spotify, Apple Music, and the like. Over the next five years, the guy who wrote “All Star” and the dude who wrote “Fish Heads” will see their royalties go up by nearly 45 percent—a sign that, given time, the system works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wesley Willis WinAmp Connection</title>
      <link>/2017/11/21/wesley-willis-winamp-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/21/wesley-willis-winamp-history/</guid>
      <description>Wesley Willis was a prolific musician and wonderful artist. Beloved by most folks he ran across, it’s no surprise his legacy would live on in an unlikely place—your computer.  Some may recognize Mike the llama as the mascot of legendary music software WinAmp. But did you know, there is a somewhat tenuous, but quite obvious connection to Wesley built into the software?
Windows users in the mid-to-late 90s are probably used WinAmp or know of it in some capacity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moore R. Stevie Moore</title>
      <link>/2017/08/31/r-stevie-moore-starting-points/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 05:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/31/r-stevie-moore-starting-points/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: This is a companion piece to yesterday&amp;rsquo;s newsletter issue on R. Stevie Moore, by David Buck. Read that first, then come back here.
&amp;nbsp;
R. Stevie Moore&amp;rsquo;s vast body of work may intimidate some and may delight others. I&amp;rsquo;ve taken the liberty of curating a list of my top R. Stevie Moore songs that will entertain, amuse and otherwise. They also serve as a great introduction to the man and his work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Man With 400 Albums</title>
      <link>/2017/08/30/r-stevie-moore-outsider-music-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 06:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/30/r-stevie-moore-outsider-music-history/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Hey all, Ernie from Tedium here! So I&amp;rsquo;m happy to introduce David Buck, a first-time writer for the newsletter who&amp;rsquo;s a massive fan of a guy you&amp;rsquo;re probably not even aware of. He makes me excited about the guy, to be honest. Read on—tonight&amp;rsquo;s piece is a total treat. And be sure to check out his list for newbies!
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: Many great artists exist outside the mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sing Your Heart Out</title>
      <link>/2017/08/11/karaoke-technology-evolution-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/11/karaoke-technology-evolution-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Apologies to Chris Carrabba and his decades-old heartbreak, but my favorite karaoke song is totally at the Dashboard Confessional singer’s expense. During the height of the emo era, I was shocked that the heart-bleeding-on-floor anthem “Screaming Infidelities” was commonly featured in the books at karaoke bars, because it seemed like the opposite of a good karaoke song. So, knowing it was available, I decided to make it my signature song.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stammer Of Success</title>
      <link>/2017/01/25/scatman-john-stuttering-success-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 05:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/25/scatman-john-stuttering-success-story/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Hey guys, Ernie here. Our good pal Andrew Egan is back with an awesome tale about a guy who kicked adversity&amp;rsquo;s ass. Enjoy.
Today in Tedium: On the 14th floor of a midtown Manhattan office building, an organization works diligently to help raise awareness of stuttering. The National Stuttering Association was founded in 1977 to teach the general public about one of America’s more common speech impediments. The association holds an annual conference (taking place in Dallas this year) and sponsors various outreach programs for those dealing with a stutter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Be Frank</title>
      <link>/2017/01/02/frank-sidebottom-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 21:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/02/frank-sidebottom-story/</guid>
      <description>Behind the Mask: It takes a certain kind of human being to create a persona for yourself, and—by all accounts—Chris Sievey was very much that person.  The British musician made his name in the ‘80s with an oddball comic persona named Frank Sidebottom, who was noted for both the giant mask he wore and his ability to rewrite classic pop songs into comic odes about Frank’s hometown, the Manchester suburb of Timperley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Big Idea, Synthesized</title>
      <link>/2016/11/18/casio-keyboards-casiotone-cultural-impact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/11/18/casio-keyboards-casiotone-cultural-impact/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In the late 1970s, a man who had changed the business world by turning massive calculators into handheld devices decided that he wanted to scratch another itch. And with that itch scratched, he introduced a world of creativity to bedroom warriors around the country—a set of training wheels to the musically inclined. The devices he created proudly ignored their weaknesses and succeeded despite themselves. And they even inspired pop culture in ways big and small.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>