<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music Industry on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/music-industry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music Industry on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/music-industry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of Creative Destruction</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/a-tale-of-creative-destruction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/a-tale-of-creative-destruction/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: The early Counting Crows hit &amp;ldquo;Mr. Jones&amp;rdquo; was a lie. Take that back—the incident was real, and Adam Duritz did hang out with a guy with the last name Jones, but the song&amp;rsquo;s whole plotline about how they were gonna be happier when they were famous didn&amp;rsquo;t come to pass. If you go to a Counting Crows show these days, in fact, the lyric is now &amp;ldquo;we all wanna be big, big stars, yeah, but then we get second thoughts about that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art, Commerce, and Zamfir</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/heartland-music-direct-tv-music-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/heartland-music-direct-tv-music-marketing/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: When I grew up, I listened to a lot of John Denver. Well, not really full songs, so much as the 10-second snippets of tunes that played during his commercials on late-night cable TV. “You fill up my senses like a night in the forest,” Denver sang to the masses, even though he was really only singing to Annie, his first wife. But those choruses and hooks had a way of bleeding together into one super-song.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ban The Box</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/compact-disc-longbox-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/compact-disc-longbox-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Thirty years ago, the record industry decided it didn’t want to be the record industry anymore. It wanted to be the CD industry, with maybe some cassettes on the side. It was getting rid of all that vinyl! This situation, oddly enough, may just repeat in 2018—except, this time, not by choice. Best Buy is about to throw out its record racks entirely; Target is making the idea of selling physical CDs less financially advantageous for record labels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Behind By A Century</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/the-tragically-hip-appreciation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/the-tragically-hip-appreciation/</guid>
      <description>[big]My wife, for years, has had this tendency of deciding to watch some shows, usually dramas, only after their run has completed, which I’m sure that TV studios friggin’ love. Sometimes, though, there’s so much out there that it’s just functionally easier to tackle a body of work like Weeds in full, over the span of a week, rather than as a number of disparate, easily-forgotten pieces.[/big]
Music, which has always been more of my forte, often doesn’t have this problem—a song is usually self-contained in a theme, and an album usually stands on its own as a complete thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre String Theories</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/prepared-guitar-bizarre-string-theories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/prepared-guitar-bizarre-string-theories/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Of the many fascinating experiments on the internet these days involving red hot nickel balls, my personal favorite is this one, involving two guitars. This clip, apparently inspired by nickel-ball innovator Matthew Neuland&amp;rsquo;s uncle, at first attempted to show whether a fiery nickel ball would put the guitar out of tune. Then Neuland used the nickel ball to destroy the strings. It&amp;rsquo;s far from the first example of someone messing with guitar strings just to see what might happen—in fact, there&amp;rsquo;s something of a whole subgenre of guitar playing based on the concept of modifying or breaking guitars in unusual ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bootleg this issue</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/bootleg-this-issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/bootleg-this-issue/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Last month, a director named Joseph Kahn released the _Mighty Morphin Power Rangers_ film that nobody was asking for—but despite that low ceiling, he more than topped it. The 14-minute short film starred people who have actually been cast in real movies and TV shows (James Van Der Beek and Katee Sackhoff), and took the franchise in a dark, gritty new direction that definitely has nothing in common with the Saved By the Bell-in-costume motif that the franchise was known for in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chartered Waters</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/billboard-pop-charts-alternative-charts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/billboard-pop-charts-alternative-charts/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: As a fan of the underdog, I love reading the bottom half of music charts. Forget Billboard&amp;rsquo;s Hot 100; I wanna see what&amp;rsquo;s happening on the Bubbling Under Hot 100 chart, if that indie band I&amp;rsquo;m digging actually has a chance of breaking into the top half. (Oh, who am I kidding? I spent the last week listening to Hüsker Dü and American Music Club. My taste is off the grid these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Format War Footnotes</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/format-wars-laserdisc-hitclips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/format-wars-laserdisc-hitclips/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: They say that history is written by the people who win—a standard that translates to wars and land grabs of all types. But it also translates pretty effectively to format wars. Generally, when we reminisce about old-school formats, we tend to focus on vinyl records, tape decks, and floppy disks, but those only really scratch the surface of the kind of bizarre formats out there to grab content from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hide And Seek</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/hidden-tracks-album-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/hidden-tracks-album-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Editor’s note: Tonight’s issue is a slightly expanded rerun of a classic issue of Tedium with some additional info added in spots where it makes sense. Enjoy!
&amp;nbsp;
[big]Today in Tedium: We gained a lot when albums went fully digital, but we also lost a bunch of stuff along the way. Among the things we lost: Record sleeves, media towers, and Tower Records. We have digital equivalents of all these things, so it&amp;rsquo;s not like we necessarily miss them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Want to Live Like Common People</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/common-people-rich-to-poor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/common-people-rich-to-poor/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: The greatest six minutes that the British band Pulp ever put to wax pulled off a lot of small victories as it leaped into a larger one. &amp;ldquo;Common People&amp;rdquo; highlighted the lingering definitions of class that the U.K. still hasn&amp;rsquo;t managed to shake; it drew a vibrant character sketch that few songwriters can put together in a single album, let alone a pop song; and it broke through to the mainstream at a time when most British music buyers were focused mostly on Blur and Oasis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In front of the music</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/worst-album-covers-analyzed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/worst-album-covers-analyzed/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Nearly as long as there has been the internet, there have been lists of terrible album covers—many of which predate the internet and are looked at using modern standards for humor and kitsch. But the problem with these images is that there&amp;rsquo;s often no story behind them, because they&amp;rsquo;re often not shared with any information to speak of. They&amp;rsquo;re historic memes, but they never seem to have any attached history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Lock Information Down</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/drm-history-intertrust-contentguard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/drm-history-intertrust-contentguard/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Digital rights management seemingly came out of nowhere to define our relationship with technology in the modern day. Popularly, it seemed like its birth had come as a direct response to the growth of piracy in the film and music industries, but what’s interesting—and perhaps not properly contextualized—is that it existed for years prior to Napster, and had a technical component before the Digital Millennium Copyright Act gave it a legal component.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Like A Rock</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/bob-seger-digital-holdout/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/bob-seger-digital-holdout/</guid>
      <description>[big]Music executive Tim Quirk is best known for his band Too Much Joy, but his big problem these days is that there’s not enough joy—at least when it comes to the music of Bob Seger.[/big]
Last week, Quirk made a lengthy case in an NPR article as to why Seger, who is barely represented on any digital music platforms at all, should make his back catalog available on services like iTunes and Spotify.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Literal Dad Rock</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/adrian-belew-oh-daddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/adrian-belew-oh-daddy/</guid>
      <description>[big]It doesn’t get nearly as much attention as, say, 1992, but 1989 may have been the most interesting year for modern rock.[/big]
The reason for this was that the creation of Billboard’s Modern Rock Tracks chart the year prior created a context for people in the music industry who never would have had a chance at having a mainstream hit otherwise. And MTV, with its 120 Minutes franchise going strong, was ready to push the songs, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Livin&#39; on the Edge</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/art-decency-shocking-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/art-decency-shocking-content/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: That sound you hear is Tipper Gore&amp;rsquo;s eyes bulging out. On June 1, a new video game called Hatred aims for the absolute edge of decency and taste, with a plot line that essentially involves killing innocent people en masse for no good reason other than to push forth the destruction of society. &amp;ldquo;We say ‘yes, it is a game about killing people’ and the only reason of the antagonist doing that sick stuff is his deep-rooted hatred,&amp;ldquo; its makers state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maybe You’ve Been Brainwashed Too</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/new-radicals-gregg-alexander-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/new-radicals-gregg-alexander-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Two decades ago this month, a couple of things happened in the world of music that forever shaped the way I thought about it. One, the Barenaked Ladies scored a number-one hit on the Billboard Hot 100 with “One Week,” and a band called The New Radicals released their first and only album, *Maybe You’ve Been Brainwashed Too*—whose lead single, “You Get What You Give,” would turn the band into the perfect one-hit wonder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Members Only</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/non-performing-band-members-coldplay-grateful-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/non-performing-band-members-coldplay-grateful-dead/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: “Look at the stars, look how they shine for you, and all the things that you do, non-performing band member …” I personally gained a major distaste for Coldplay sometime in the early naughts, when I failed to understand the appeal of “Clocks,” despite having enjoyed Parachutes. Perhaps it’s for that reason I never realized that Coldplay has five members, that I assumed they were a quartet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mystic Knights of the Movie Soundtrack</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/oingo-boingo-pop-culture-appearances/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/oingo-boingo-pop-culture-appearances/</guid>
      <description>[big]Before Danny Elfman became the go-to guy for scoring great films, his band Oingo Boingo was a mid-&amp;lsquo;80s go-to for soundtrack contributions. This ensured that, even as Elfman moved away from the band, Oingo Boingo would carry a massive pop-culture footprint.[/big]
&amp;ldquo;I think Oingo&amp;rsquo;s music is good for the audience for those films; the people will relate to it,&amp;rdquo; Elfman said of the phenomenon, according to the Encyclopedia of Pop, Rock &amp;amp; Soul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primitive Streaming Gods</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/legal-music-streaming-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/legal-music-streaming-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: This week, the music industry had a pretty good reason to cheer, and not just because of the Grammys. They won big in Washington, after the the United States Copyright Royalty Board ruled in favor of songwriters that felt like they had gotten the short end of the stick from Spotify, Apple Music, and the like. Over the next five years, the guy who wrote “All Star” and the dude who wrote “Fish Heads” will see their royalties go up by nearly 45 percent—a sign that, given time, the system works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purple Copyright Eater</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/prince-troubled-relationship-with-copyright/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/prince-troubled-relationship-with-copyright/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Today in Tedium: In losing Prince Rogers Nelson, we&amp;rsquo;re losing a lot more than a idiosyncratic pop star who defined an entire New Power Generation. We&amp;rsquo;re losing the last link between our current remix-heavy culture (which, let&amp;rsquo;s face it, this newsletter wouldn&amp;rsquo;t exist without) and an era when ownership of creative work was treated as an end-all-be-all. Here was a guy who started the internet era sporting a name that literally could not be searched, who forced lawsuits over barely-noticeable renditions of his songs in YouTube clips, and who made a lot of creative stuff that nobody will likely ever see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searching for the perfect tones</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/unusual-musical-instruments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/unusual-musical-instruments/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: If you&amp;rsquo;ve never seen a 12-foot-tall upright piano, you&amp;rsquo;re in for a treat. The neo-classical German musician Nils Frahm recorded his latest album, Solo, on such a device, the Klavins Model 370. Frahm told Pitchfork that the experience was so inspiring that he wanted to launch a crowdfunding effort to help the piano&amp;rsquo;s creator, David Klavins, build an even taller instrument. (Read about that here.) Today, inspired by Frahm&amp;rsquo;s excitement, we want to talk about some incredibly bizarre instruments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sing Your Heart Out</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/karaoke-technology-evolution-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/karaoke-technology-evolution-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Apologies to Chris Carrabba and his decades-old heartbreak, but my favorite karaoke song is totally at the Dashboard Confessional singer’s expense. During the height of the emo era, I was shocked that the heart-bleeding-on-floor anthem “Screaming Infidelities” was commonly featured in the books at karaoke bars, because it seemed like the opposite of a good karaoke song. So, knowing it was available, I decided to make it my signature song.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take me out to the riot</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/famous-baseball-riots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/famous-baseball-riots/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: This weekend marks the opening day of the 2015 season of Major League Baseball—a sport that you find either immensely fascinating or overrated compared to more action-packed sports like football or basketball. Baseball has never completely lost the public&amp;rsquo;s fascination, though it&amp;rsquo;s certainly had some rough periods over the years. And sometimes, the fans can be total jerks. Today&amp;rsquo;s issue of Tedium covers what it&amp;rsquo;s like to be in the midst of a crowd of annoying baseball fans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tape Deck Heart</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/magnetic-tape-revival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/magnetic-tape-revival/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: When&amp;rsquo;s the big comeback for magnetic tapes coming around, anyway? These days, vinyl is making a serious comeback with the public. Even Taylor Swift is selling a ton of vinyl records these days. But in a world where streaming and optical discs are more common than ever, the magnetic tape—which arguably has as much nostalgic hipster cachet as the vinyl record, and across a variety of formats at that—hasn&amp;rsquo;t seen nearly as much love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Big Data Jukebox</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/allmusic-database-historic-importance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/allmusic-database-historic-importance/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Discovering new kinds of music is easier than ever, something we can credit Napster for—along with its later legal followers, particularly Spotify, Pandora, and Apple Music. (Oh, and eMusic. That site was great back in the day.) But having all this music at our fingertips was only part of the equation—we needed to be armed with information. I think I realized that point during the early 2000s, when I found myself in the music section of a Barnes &amp;amp; Noble store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stammer Of Success</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/scatman-john-stuttering-success-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/scatman-john-stuttering-success-story/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Hey guys, Ernie here. Our good pal Andrew Egan is back with an awesome tale about a guy who kicked adversity&amp;rsquo;s ass. Enjoy.
[big]Today in Tedium: On the 14th floor of a midtown Manhattan office building, an organization works diligently to help raise awareness of stuttering. The National Stuttering Association was founded in 1977 to teach the general public about one of America’s more common speech impediments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The first 12 cost a penny, but …</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/columbia-house-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/columbia-house-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Yesterday, a coworker and good friend of mine revealed to me a fact that made me feel very old. We were talking about Spotify—and his desire not to pay $10 per month for the service—and I referenced Columbia House. He did not know what I was talking about. I was taken aback by this news—I thought everyone knew what Columbia House was! The mail-order CD service (along with its competitor BMG) had a bright moment in the early &amp;lsquo;90s, only to see its business model fall apart thanks to iTunes, and later, Spotify.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trippin&#39; On A Hole In A Paper Heart</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/scott-weiland-stone-temple-pilots-what-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/scott-weiland-stone-temple-pilots-what-next/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: As we were putting the finishing touches on last Thursday&amp;rsquo;s Tedium, a terrible bit of news hit the internet—the death of Scott Weiland, one of the most influential rock vocalists of the last quarter-century. Weiland&amp;rsquo;s death, for many, was not a surprise, and that fact was touched upon by his former band, Stone Temple Pilots. In 2013, Weiland was kicked out of the band he helped make famous, leading to a lengthy legal battle between the two sides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unsettled</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/ticketmaster-live-nation-free-ticket-settlement-boycott/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/ticketmaster-live-nation-free-ticket-settlement-boycott/</guid>
      <description>[big]Nearly a quarter-century ago, Pearl Jam—which had become the biggest band in the world around this time effectively by ignoring the music industry orthodoxy of the time—decided to take on live music’s biggest middleman.[/big]
It probably hurt their career to take aim at Ticketmaster, which had become known for charging expensive service fees on every ticket it sold. But the politically minded band did, going so far as to file a complaint with the Justice Department and speak in front of Congress about the problem, something rock bands don’t usually do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vulcan creativity</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/leonard-nimoy-vulcan-creativity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/leonard-nimoy-vulcan-creativity/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox] [big]Today in Tedium: William Shatner got all the weirdo pop attention back in the 1960s, but his _Star Trek_ co-star deserved just as much of it—if not more. The just-departed Leonard Nimoy (God rest his half-Vulcan soul) recorded a number of pop albums in the 1960s, including his own renditions of &amp;ldquo;I Walk the Line&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Proud Mary.&amp;rdquo; But the career highlight to top them all was a bizarro pop tune about a fantasy character who sported ears nearly as pointy as Spock&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walk on the Vinyl Side</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/soundalike-records-walk-on-the-vinyl-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/soundalike-records-walk-on-the-vinyl-side/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Late rock legend Lou Reed has been in the news lately for a somewhat odd reason. On Monday, Reed&amp;rsquo;s sister wrote about her brother&amp;rsquo;s medical situation during his teenage years—when, the rumor goes, his parents had him undergo electroshock therapy to fend off homosexual urges. (Lou did undergo the controversial therapy treatment, but his sister denies that latent homosexuality was the cause. Speaking of their parents, she explains: &amp;ldquo;They were caught in a bewildering web of guilt, fear, and poor psychiatric care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worst. Birthday. Ever.</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/happy-birthday-copyright-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/happy-birthday-copyright-case/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: 80 years ago, the nature of one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most popular tunes changed forever. It&amp;rsquo;s a song you&amp;rsquo;ve probably sung before, about a bajillion times. &amp;ldquo;Happy birthday to you, happy birthday …&amp;rdquo; you know the rest. In 1935, &amp;ldquo;Happy Birthday&amp;rdquo; was copyrighted, and as a result, it&amp;rsquo;s rare to hear the song performed in any film or concert. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re gonna talk about copyright, traditional songs, and the ways in which people who had no role in creating those songs are making big bucks off of the unwitting public.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>