<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Money on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/money/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Money on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 05:20:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/money/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Running Out of Widgets</title>
      <link>/2017/09/13/barnes-noble-third-place-widgets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 05:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/13/barnes-noble-third-place-widgets/</guid>
      <description>Editor’s note: Apple’s revelation on Tuesday that it was rethinking its approach to stores into something akin to a “town square” got me thinking about an old piece I wrote a while back—one that I, ironically, was just interviewed about for Ozy. In lieu of a fresh one, here’s a lightly refreshed 2015 piece that still feels pretty relevant.
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: When physical objects can be turned into a series of bits and bytes and streamed over the airwaves, the result is that stores start running out of things to sell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Little off the Top</title>
      <link>/2016/02/17/barber-shop-credit-card-transactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 03:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/02/17/barber-shop-credit-card-transactions/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: If you find yourself in a mom-and-pop barber shop or hair salon of any kind, you might find this common (but annoying) state of affairs in play: Despite the fact that basically every other store on the block accepts credit cards, the barber shop is the lone holdout on that front, forcing consumers who may have otherwise stopped paying cash for most things long ago to hit up the ATM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Shell Game</title>
      <link>/2015/12/18/shell-companies-easy-to-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/18/shell-companies-easy-to-launch/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Last week, the journalists at the Las Vegas Review-Journal had a problem: Their newspaper had a new owner, but they couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out who the hell it was. After roughly a week of reporting, they finally figured out exactly who spent $140 million on the paper—one Sheldon Adelson, the casino owner and major Republican donor—but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t easy to get quite that far. Thanks to the law, there was nothing requiring the owner to come forward and reveal themselves to the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Want to Live Like Common People</title>
      <link>/2015/07/29/common-people-rich-to-poor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2015 05:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/07/29/common-people-rich-to-poor/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The greatest six minutes that the British band Pulp ever put to wax pulled off a lot of small victories as it leaped into a larger one. &amp;ldquo;Common People&amp;rdquo; highlighted the lingering definitions of class that the U.K. still hasn&amp;rsquo;t managed to shake; it drew a vibrant character sketch that few songwriters can put together in a single album, let alone a pop song; and it broke through to the mainstream at a time when most British music buyers were focused mostly on Blur and Oasis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your money is worthless here</title>
      <link>/2015/06/24/your-money-is-worthless-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 07:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/24/your-money-is-worthless-here/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: If you&amp;rsquo;re watching the right digital substation, the message is hard to ignore. Ron Paul says we&amp;rsquo;re facing a catastrophic financial crisis that could leave you screwed. That&amp;rsquo;s a weird message to hear from any former politician, even one with the libertarian bonafides of Ron Paul. (His son Rand must be psyched that this is how he&amp;rsquo;s spending his retirement.) But the paid ads, which are designed to get you to buy some financial services you don&amp;rsquo;t need, nonetheless offer a funhouse mirror from which to consider the market forces that cause currency to lose its value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Pyramids Collapse</title>
      <link>/2015/06/19/anatomy-scams-when-pyramids-collapse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 07:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/19/anatomy-scams-when-pyramids-collapse/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It&amp;rsquo;s the oldest scam in the book, and people fall for it all the freaking time. Pyramid schemes of all shapes and sizes have been bilking people out of their hard-earned money for generations, and you&amp;rsquo;re probably gonna get screwed out of your hard-earned money before you even realize it. Today&amp;rsquo;s Tedium is all about scams that leave scars way deeper than all the money stolen. — Ernie @ Tedium</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give us some credit</title>
      <link>/2015/06/10/credit-card-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/10/credit-card-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The payment card as we know it is both more popular than ever and, well, dying. According to a 2013 Federal Reserve study, the number of credit card payments in the United States passed the number of check-based payments for the first time, and debit cards passed that mark way back in 2004. But the magnetic swipe isn&amp;rsquo;t long for this world—the industry is switching to a chip-based system this year, and mobile payments threaten to put cards out to pasture soon after that.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>