<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Obscure Music on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/obscure-music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Obscure Music on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 09:32:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/obscure-music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hide And Seek</title>
      <link>/2017/11/10/hidden-tracks-album-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 09:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/10/hidden-tracks-album-history/</guid>
      <description>Editor’s note: Tonight’s issue is a slightly expanded rerun of a classic issue of Tedium with some additional info added in spots where it makes sense. Enjoy!
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: We gained a lot when albums went fully digital, but we also lost a bunch of stuff along the way. Among the things we lost: Record sleeves, media towers, and Tower Records. We have digital equivalents of all these things, so it&amp;rsquo;s not like we necessarily miss them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>His Name Was Larry</title>
      <link>/2017/10/06/larry-wild-man-fischer-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 07:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/06/larry-wild-man-fischer-story/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Hey all, Ernie here with another piece from David Buck, who wrote his first Tedium piece on outsider icon R. Stevie Moore. Turns out his knowledge of outsider artists goes deep—as you&amp;rsquo;ll see with today&amp;rsquo;s piece.
Today in Tedium: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve got a camera, loaded with film,&amp;rdquo; he sang, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m gonna take a picture of you.&amp;rdquo; I became particularly fascinated with the unique vocal stylings of Larry “Wild Man” Fischer after hearing his song &amp;ldquo;I Got a Camera&amp;rdquo; on a warm summer day, just before my freshman year of high school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moore R. Stevie Moore</title>
      <link>/2017/08/31/r-stevie-moore-starting-points/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 05:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/31/r-stevie-moore-starting-points/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: This is a companion piece to yesterday&amp;rsquo;s newsletter issue on R. Stevie Moore, by David Buck. Read that first, then come back here.
&amp;nbsp;
R. Stevie Moore&amp;rsquo;s vast body of work may intimidate some and may delight others. I&amp;rsquo;ve taken the liberty of curating a list of my top R. Stevie Moore songs that will entertain, amuse and otherwise. They also serve as a great introduction to the man and his work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Man With 400 Albums</title>
      <link>/2017/08/30/r-stevie-moore-outsider-music-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 06:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/30/r-stevie-moore-outsider-music-history/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Hey all, Ernie from Tedium here! So I&amp;rsquo;m happy to introduce David Buck, a first-time writer for the newsletter who&amp;rsquo;s a massive fan of a guy you&amp;rsquo;re probably not even aware of. He makes me excited about the guy, to be honest. Read on—tonight&amp;rsquo;s piece is a total treat. And be sure to check out his list for newbies!
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: Many great artists exist outside the mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Be Frank</title>
      <link>/2017/01/02/frank-sidebottom-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 21:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/02/frank-sidebottom-story/</guid>
      <description>Behind the Mask: It takes a certain kind of human being to create a persona for yourself, and—by all accounts—Chris Sievey was very much that person.  The British musician made his name in the ‘80s with an oddball comic persona named Frank Sidebottom, who was noted for both the giant mask he wore and his ability to rewrite classic pop songs into comic odes about Frank’s hometown, the Manchester suburb of Timperley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre String Theories</title>
      <link>/2016/05/20/prepared-guitar-bizarre-string-theories/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/05/20/prepared-guitar-bizarre-string-theories/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Of the many fascinating experiments on the internet these days involving red hot nickel balls, my personal favorite is this one, involving two guitars. This clip, apparently inspired by nickel-ball innovator Matthew Neuland&amp;rsquo;s uncle, at first attempted to show whether a fiery nickel ball would put the guitar out of tune. Then Neuland used the nickel ball to destroy the strings. It&amp;rsquo;s far from the first example of someone messing with guitar strings just to see what might happen—in fact, there&amp;rsquo;s something of a whole subgenre of guitar playing based on the concept of modifying or breaking guitars in unusual ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trippin&#39; On A Hole In A Paper Heart</title>
      <link>/2015/12/09/scott-weiland-stone-temple-pilots-what-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2015 07:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/09/scott-weiland-stone-temple-pilots-what-next/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: As we were putting the finishing touches on last Thursday&amp;rsquo;s Tedium, a terrible bit of news hit the internet—the death of Scott Weiland, one of the most influential rock vocalists of the last quarter-century. Weiland&amp;rsquo;s death, for many, was not a surprise, and that fact was touched upon by his former band, Stone Temple Pilots. In 2013, Weiland was kicked out of the band he helped make famous, leading to a lengthy legal battle between the two sides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tape Deck Heart</title>
      <link>/2015/08/21/magnetic-tape-revival/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2015 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/21/magnetic-tape-revival/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: When&amp;rsquo;s the big comeback for magnetic tapes coming around, anyway? These days, vinyl is making a serious comeback with the public. Even Taylor Swift is selling a ton of vinyl records these days. But in a world where streaming and optical discs are more common than ever, the magnetic tape—which arguably has as much nostalgic hipster cachet as the vinyl record, and across a variety of formats at that—hasn&amp;rsquo;t seen nearly as much love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of Creative Destruction</title>
      <link>/2015/08/07/a-tale-of-creative-destruction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/07/a-tale-of-creative-destruction/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The early Counting Crows hit &amp;ldquo;Mr. Jones&amp;rdquo; was a lie. Take that back—the incident was real, and Adam Duritz did hang out with a guy with the last name Jones, but the song&amp;rsquo;s whole plotline about how they were gonna be happier when they were famous didn&amp;rsquo;t come to pass. If you go to a Counting Crows show these days, in fact, the lyric is now &amp;ldquo;we all wanna be big, big stars, yeah, but then we get second thoughts about that.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>