<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amtrak on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/amtrak/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Amtrak on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 07:02:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/amtrak/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Special Delivery</title>
      <link>/2017/05/16/unique-pizza-delivery-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 07:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/16/unique-pizza-delivery-methods/</guid>
      <description>As I highlighted recently, Amtrak trains are rife with delays—which can be blamed on a combination of failing infrastructure and a lack of track ownership.  We can’t solve the problem of Amtrak very easily, but pizza is a pretty nice salve.
On Sunday, a mechanical failure knocked out a train on the way to Washington from New York City, eventually leading passengers to have to switch trains. While they were stuck waiting in the Wilmington, Delaware, area, someone stuck on the underfunded transit medium got the idea to call a local pizza place for nourishment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Are Trains Always Late?</title>
      <link>/2017/04/26/amtrak-train-delay-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/04/26/amtrak-train-delay-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Recently, airlines have gotten all the chatter about how terrible they are, and I was in that category, too … on Twitter. Tedium is a different beast, and it requires me to not jump on every big news story, as much as I’d like to. It took every ounce of restraint in my body to not email the “United Breaks Guitars” guy and ask him what he’s been doing lately.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>