<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hospitality Industry on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/hospitality-industry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hospitality Industry on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 09:17:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/hospitality-industry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Leavin’ The Light On</title>
      <link>/2018/02/21/tom-bodett-motel-6-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 09:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/21/tom-bodett-motel-6-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey all, Ernie here with another slice of life from my pal David Buck. This time, he gives us the story of the Great American Motel Chain, and the man whose voice defines that story.
Today in Tedium: You may recognize the voice of Tom Bodett as the whimsical narrator of those hilarious Motel 6 radio spots that have been floating around the airwaves for the past thirty years. Today’s Tedium seeks to explore the career of the man behind the voice and how he helped take what was essentially a discount motel chain and helped change its image through what AdAge magazine calls “the greatest ads of all time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Vacancy</title>
      <link>/2016/03/25/hotel-psychology-amenities-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2016 07:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/03/25/hotel-psychology-amenities-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: When we go to a hotel, especially a nice one where we&amp;rsquo;re dropping a couple hundred bucks for a single night&amp;rsquo;s stay, we expect a lot out of the experience—something nicer than our schlubby apartment, preferably with an exotic or urban locale easily in sight. But when we open the door, no matter how ugly the motel we end up staying in turns out to be, there are always a handful of things that are always consistent—the TV and remote, the well-made bed, the cheap artwork on the walls.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>