<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manufacturing on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/manufacturing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Manufacturing on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/manufacturing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>An Escalating Danger</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/escalators-are-dangerous/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/escalators-are-dangerous/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Mitch Hedberg was a funny guy, and the main reason he was funny was because his one-liners were so on-point. Perhaps his best-known one involved the escalator. &amp;ldquo;An escalator can never break, it can only become stairs,&amp;rdquo; he famously joked. &amp;ldquo;You would never see an &amp;lsquo;Escalator Temporarily Out Of Order&amp;rsquo; sign, just &amp;lsquo;Escalator Temporarily Stairs. Sorry for the convenience. We apologize for the fact that you can still get up there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ban The Box</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/compact-disc-longbox-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/compact-disc-longbox-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Thirty years ago, the record industry decided it didn’t want to be the record industry anymore. It wanted to be the CD industry, with maybe some cassettes on the side. It was getting rid of all that vinyl! This situation, oddly enough, may just repeat in 2018—except, this time, not by choice. Best Buy is about to throw out its record racks entirely; Target is making the idea of selling physical CDs less financially advantageous for record labels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Click, Clack</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/cherry-mx-keyboard-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/cherry-mx-keyboard-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Editor’s Note: Tonight’s Tedium is a piece of mine that recently ran in Motherboard_, a site that recently ran a cool piece on a counterfeit iPhone X. Enjoy!_
&amp;nbsp;
[big]Today in Tedium: Sometimes, cornering the market on a relatively niche idea is all a company needs to seal its fate as an enterprise that’s destined to stick around for the long haul. And you don’t get more relatively niche than the keyboard switch, as far as gadgets go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genuine Imitation Leather</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/genuine-imitation-leather/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/genuine-imitation-leather/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: As any cursory watch of an episode of Happy Days will tell you, we&amp;rsquo;re obsessed with the look of leather—but perhaps not fans of the way leather is produced. Much like a meal at McDonald&amp;rsquo;s or a fur coat, we&amp;rsquo;re more impressed with the final result without any worries about where it came from—because thinking about where it came from potentially raises some heavy ethical questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junk Food’s Happiest Accident</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/cheese-curls-creation-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/cheese-curls-creation-story/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: They change the color of our skin. They get stuck in our teeth. But for some reason, we can’t stop eating cheese curls, the puffiest snack food ever created. But these corn-and-powder snacks didn’t just fall like manna from the sky into our bowls, always there for us ahead of our Bojack Horseman marathon. The story of the cheese curl is one of the more unusual creation stories in snack-food history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let &#39;Er Rip</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/clothing-tags-why-they-exist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/clothing-tags-why-they-exist/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Last week, there was a tag on an item on my clothing that was so uncomfortable that there was nothing I wanted to do more than pull it off—to send that miserable tag to a recycling bin where it would never again see the light of day. But that annoying tag got me to thinking: Where did clothing tags come from, and who decided that an annoying tag was an important thing to have on a piece of clothing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math &#43; The Mechanics</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/curta-calculator-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/curta-calculator-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: We think of computers as being purely digital objects—computational beasts that work with abstracted collections of 1s and 0s. As complexity increased, so did the tactics to making the computing devices smaller, to the point where we can shove one in our skin as if that’s something we wanna do. Of course, computers are reliant on power these days, but there was a time when computers didn’t need things like batteries, because they weren’t electronic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rough Edges</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/ceramic-coffee-cups-rough-spots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/ceramic-coffee-cups-rough-spots/</guid>
      <description>[big]This sounds strange to think about, but when it comes down to it, there’s often a reason for everything, even if you’ve never even pondered it before.[/big]
Case in point: Have you ever wondered why traditional ceramic coffee cups, which are smooth around the edges, have that rough circular spot on the bottom? That was not a happy accident—it was a design choice.
See, that squat ceramic coffee cup, the one you’ve seen millions of times, in diners and living rooms, sometimes with brass-knuckle designs, came from somewhere—specifically Victor, New York, a town that initially made its name building porcelain insulators in the late 19th century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sauce-Packet Squeeze</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/condiment-sauce-packet-squeeze/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/condiment-sauce-packet-squeeze/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Alright, I&amp;rsquo;d like to do a quick survey. (This is optional, but it would be nice if you humored me.) OK, here goes: Step away from your computer for ten to fifteen seconds and look in your fridge, particularly the door area of the fridge. (Waits …) Do you have any sauce packets just sitting around? If so, how many, and where did they come from?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total Eclipse Of The Counterfeit</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/amazon-counterfeit-solar-eclipse-glasses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/amazon-counterfeit-solar-eclipse-glasses/</guid>
      <description>[big]If you bought a pair of eclipse glasses from Amazon recently, you probably received a shock when the company informed you that it was selling solar eclipse glasses that weren’t certified to be used to watch the forthcoming eclipse—and that you would be getting a refund.[/big]
See, here’s what happened: A lot of major science and optical associations have been working with NASA on a campaign to ensure that people are buying glasses verified to be used during the solar eclipse happening in North America over the next few days.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>