<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food Industry on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/food-industry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food Industry on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 22:42:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/food-industry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Cream Fakery</title>
      <link>/2017/01/16/breyers-frozen-dairy-dessert-not-ice-cream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 22:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/16/breyers-frozen-dairy-dessert-not-ice-cream/</guid>
      <description>A couple of months ago, I was scooping myself a bowl of ice cream, when I discovered something interesting and a little disturbing: Nowhere on the label did the ice cream describe itself as “ice cream.”  The label was for Breyers, a brand that has a long, lengthy history in the ice cream manufacturing game and a pledge to use “high quality ingredients.” But this pledge had been put into doubt by the fact that Breyers couldn’t describe what it was selling as ice cream, but rather “frozen dairy dessert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Doesn’t Love Pickles?</title>
      <link>/2017/01/04/interesting-facts-about-pickles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/04/interesting-facts-about-pickles/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Of the many things that we lost in 2016, one of the saddest losses might have been a purely cultural one. At the end of 2016, the Carnegie Deli, an iconic slice of New York City, served its last overstuffed, overpriced pastrami sandwich. (That’s despite an on-the-table, quickly rebuffed offer from a New York restaurateur to buy out the owners for $10 million.) The Jewish deli will survive—Katz’s is still with us, for one thing—but it’s still a bummer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Acquiring This Taste</title>
      <link>/2016/10/07/bitrex-terrible-flavors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 07:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/10/07/bitrex-terrible-flavors/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: We love things that taste good. We hate things that taste bad. Perhaps it&amp;rsquo;s for that reason we don&amp;rsquo;t spend a lot of time talking about terrible-tasting things. But there&amp;rsquo;s plenty of reason that we should. The biggest is this: Sometimes, hiding in that terrible taste might be something so important that it can change the world in a noticeable way. Today&amp;rsquo;s Tedium is about a really terrible flavor that&amp;rsquo;s hiding all over your home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Every Piece Count</title>
      <link>/2016/09/30/meat-science-flat-iron-steak-innovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/09/30/meat-science-flat-iron-steak-innovation/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: You may not like meat, but even if you do, you may not think of it in terms of innovation. It sounds like a concept incompatible with the idea of meat—we do so many things with cows, chicken, fish, and pigs that it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to consider these animals in terms of reinvention. We&amp;rsquo;ve already mashed these four types of animals into combinations more creative than Legos, taken their parts and turned them into products that don&amp;rsquo;t even fit into the same genre as dinner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seedy Politics</title>
      <link>/2016/04/06/seed-industry-bureaucracy-politics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 05:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/04/06/seed-industry-bureaucracy-politics/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: This time of the year is perfect for planting a garden, so it&amp;rsquo;s natural to hit your local store and buy a bunch of tomato seeds, perhaps some carrot seeds, and maybe you&amp;rsquo;re in the mood for some spice, so you add a couple of habanero seeds to the cart. Soon, you might plant these seeds in the ground, without even giving a second thought to the fact that you showed your support to the commercial seed industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sauce-Packet Squeeze</title>
      <link>/2016/01/08/condiment-sauce-packet-squeeze/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2016 07:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/01/08/condiment-sauce-packet-squeeze/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Alright, I&amp;rsquo;d like to do a quick survey. (This is optional, but it would be nice if you humored me.) OK, here goes: Step away from your computer for ten to fifteen seconds and look in your fridge, particularly the door area of the fridge. (Waits …) Do you have any sauce packets just sitting around? If so, how many, and where did they come from? And why did you keep them?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frozen Karma&#39;s Gonna Get You</title>
      <link>/2015/12/30/klondike-bar-trademark-lawsuit-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 01:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/30/klondike-bar-trademark-lawsuit-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: What would you do for a Klondike bar? Most people would probably go to the nearest store, buy a package of chocolate-covered ice cream novelties, and make sure that the package eventually finds an icebox—well, as long as they don&amp;rsquo;t finish said novelties first. (That said, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m ashamed of what I did for a Klondike bar&amp;rdquo; makes for a pretty good T-shirt slogan.) The food conglomerate Kraft was willing to do more than most for a Klondike bar: They saw an opportunity to usurp a rising regional dairy treat with their own version, blatantly ripping it off, causing a listeria outbreak, and finding themselves mired in legal battles, all within the span of a few years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live and Let Dye</title>
      <link>/2015/08/26/food-coloring-dye-safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/26/food-coloring-dye-safety/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Did you hear the news? They&amp;rsquo;re taking the color out of Trix. The General Mills cereal is one of the most recent victims of a move towards more natural food, and in an effort to appease the suddenly health-conscious public, the company will be removing some of the artificial coloring from Trix and all of its other cereals. &amp;ldquo;We wanted to make sure they were still fun vibrant colors that we are providing and the fruity flavor that kids expect,&amp;rdquo; cereal developer Kate Gallager told Good Morning America of the move back in June.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>