<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trademark on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/trademark/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trademark on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/trademark/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Frozen Karma&#39;s Gonna Get You</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/klondike-bar-trademark-lawsuit-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/klondike-bar-trademark-lawsuit-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: What would you do for a Klondike bar? Most people would probably go to the nearest store, buy a package of chocolate-covered ice cream novelties, and make sure that the package eventually finds an icebox—well, as long as they don&amp;rsquo;t finish said novelties first. (That said, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m ashamed of what I did for a Klondike bar&amp;rdquo; makes for a pretty good T-shirt slogan.) The food conglomerate Kraft was willing to do more than most for a Klondike bar: They saw an opportunity to usurp a rising regional dairy treat with their own version, blatantly ripping it off, causing a listeria outbreak, and finding themselves mired in legal battles, all within the span of a few years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hooked On Velcro</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/velcro-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/velcro-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Over the weekend, I spent a bit of time cleaning my messenger bag, which had an annoying problem—the pointy half of the Velcro was filthy, covered in ugly pieces of fabric it had picked up through years of heavy regular use. After looking online, I found the great solution to this annoying problem: I took the sharp part of a plastic tape dispenser and rubbed it through the rough part of the material, which, amazingly, did the trick.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>