<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chicago on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/chicago/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chicago on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 08:45:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/chicago/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock and Roll Remodel</title>
      <link>/2017/12/21/rock-and-roll-mcdonalds-remodel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 08:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/21/rock-and-roll-mcdonalds-remodel/</guid>
      <description>In the early 1990s, Chicago icon and outsider musician Wesley Willis wrote a tribute to one of his favorite dining establishments—McDonald&amp;rsquo;s. Dubbed &amp;ldquo;Rock and Roll McDonald&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; and set to a fun, keyboard-driven melody, the song extolls the virtues of the fast food haven. Willis once spent time both in and out of the McDonald&amp;rsquo;s and surrounding area, making and selling his beautiful drawings most days.  (via the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s Yelp page)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock On Chicago</title>
      <link>/2017/11/17/wesley-willis-remembrance-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 09:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/17/wesley-willis-remembrance-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with a fresh Tedium piece comes from outsider artist aficionado and newsletter contributor David J. Buck, who hit us up last time with a piece on Wild Man Fischer. By popular demand, here’s a piece on Wesley Willis!
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: People loved Wesley Willis. Despite a rough upbringing, struggles with mental illness, extreme poverty and an abusive family, he was friendly and lovable. Wesley became a Chicago icon, building a network of friends, fans, and followers along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waaaaay Left of the Dial</title>
      <link>/2016/07/01/frankenfm-radio-fcc-analog-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/07/01/frankenfm-radio-fcc-analog-tv/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: TV on the Radio isn&amp;rsquo;t just the name of a really freaking good band. Instead, it&amp;rsquo;s a quirk of the design of analog television. But a funny thing happened on the way to obscurity: As analog TV gave way to digital, a handful of risk-taking broadcasters, sensing an opportunity, have started to run those analog TV stations as FM radio stations—big FCC plans be damned. The shift is surprisingly contentious in the world of broadcast.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>