<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Telecom on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/telecom/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Telecom on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/telecom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Dish</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/early-satellite-dish-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/early-satellite-dish-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: As a whole, the most interesting time for television was the late 1970s and early 1980s. It was an era when most networks were still willing to experiment and the technology wasn’t so locked down that an enthusiast couldn’t get around it. Comcast existed back then, but it wasn’t the juggernaut it is now; DirecTV and Dish Network hadn’t yet taken their current forms. The result was that satellite dishes—which were really freaking massive back then—were only starting to take off, and there was nothing really stopping people willing to buy a dish from investing once and getting all their shows for free after that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything You Want</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/vertical-horizon-verizon-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/vertical-horizon-verizon-theory/</guid>
      <description>[big]On April 3, 2000, one of the most prominent companies of the 21st century was born. That day, the name and logo for Verizon became known to the masses. The company, for better or worse, became a defining middleman, fundamental to the way we use our phones and access our internet.[/big]
The next day, a popular rock band released a physical single for what would become their biggest hit. “Everything You Want,” a song from Vertical Horizon&amp;rsquo;s first major label record, had already been on the radio for a few months by this point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fake Metal Trees</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/cell-towers-nimby-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/cell-towers-nimby-trees/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Here&amp;rsquo;s a tough problem. People love their cell phones, but the they hate the towers necessary to make those phones function. In fact, they really piss many people off, leading to situations where unnecessary fear-mongering wins the day, or leading people to worry that the towers will become eyesores that destroy their property values—or worse. So how do we get around the issue of these useful-but-ugly devices, anyway?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Before Netflix</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/first-streaming-service-itv-hong-kong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/first-streaming-service-itv-hong-kong/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Earlier this week, I got a little grumpy over at Product Hunt, due to an undercurrent of snark around the fact that Netflix still has a DVD service. The reason for this was that too many people were skeptical about whether such a service was still necessary. It absolutely, totally is, and I’ll give you one reason why: Netflix’s DVD service has roughly 93,000 options, while its streaming service (between shows and movies) has fewer than 8,000 options—ensuring that DVDs will have a reason to exist for quite a while.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>