<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hipster Mattress on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/hipster-mattress/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hipster Mattress on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 06:27:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/hipster-mattress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Purple Unicorn</title>
      <link>/2017/11/07/purple-com-domain-sold/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 06:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/07/purple-com-domain-sold/</guid>
      <description>For more than 23 years, the Purple.com domain reflected one guy’s simple, colorful vision. But last week, the man who owned what was secretly becoming the internet’s most valuable domain finally sold it. To … wait for it … a mattress company.  Per Domain Investing, Purple Innovations LLC, the company that owns the hipster mattress giant worth an estimated $1.1 billion, purchased the domain from Jeff Abrahamson, who spent more than two decades pledging that he would never sell the domain—instead suggesting he’d rather hold onto the URL and license it out to an interested party for a six-digit sum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lurking In Your Bed</title>
      <link>/2017/10/19/hipster-mattress-online-sales-practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 05:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/19/hipster-mattress-online-sales-practices/</guid>
      <description>As you guys may or may not know, my first really big piece on Tedium was a takedown of sorts on hipster mattresses. It pondered the idea of how the companies came to prominence, as well as what it would take to start up a company just like this. It was absurd, but it was fun to write. It’s currently the top-ranking item on Google for the term “hipster mattress.”  Since then, I’ve gotten, somewhat like clockwork, repeated emails asking if I might add links to my website to promote either other mattress companies, or websites that review mattresses.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>