<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vinyl Records on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/vinyl-records/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vinyl Records on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 07:39:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/vinyl-records/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Flexible Noise</title>
      <link>/2018/06/13/flexi-disc-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 07:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/13/flexi-disc-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In many ways, writing a Tedium piece is like an ongoing search for a “white whale” (or a Baby Beluga, if you will)—a hunt to find a great story and give it some cultural context before it’s lost to history. One such story I’ve always looked longingly at was the tale of the million-dollar McDonald’s record, a record that, quite literally, was one in 80 million (meaning that 79.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hide And Seek</title>
      <link>/2017/11/10/hidden-tracks-album-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 09:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/10/hidden-tracks-album-history/</guid>
      <description>Editor’s note: Tonight’s issue is a slightly expanded rerun of a classic issue of Tedium with some additional info added in spots where it makes sense. Enjoy!
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: We gained a lot when albums went fully digital, but we also lost a bunch of stuff along the way. Among the things we lost: Record sleeves, media towers, and Tower Records. We have digital equivalents of all these things, so it&amp;rsquo;s not like we necessarily miss them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books on Vinyl</title>
      <link>/2016/02/19/audiobooks-blind-vinyl-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 09:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/02/19/audiobooks-blind-vinyl-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It&amp;rsquo;s the great challenge of a newsletter editor when they hear this phrase—&amp;rdquo;hey, this newsletter would be really good as a podcast!&amp;rdquo; I understand the demand for things like this, because people love sounds running into their ears when they&amp;rsquo;re on the go, and you have to physically press your fingers down on your phone to read Tedium. But I&amp;rsquo;m way more clever and way less likely to say &amp;ldquo;like&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;y&amp;rsquo;know&amp;rdquo; when I write things down, so that&amp;rsquo;s why this comes in a text format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In front of the music</title>
      <link>/2015/06/03/worst-album-covers-analyzed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/03/worst-album-covers-analyzed/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Nearly as long as there has been the internet, there have been lists of terrible album covers—many of which predate the internet and are looked at using modern standards for humor and kitsch. But the problem with these images is that there&amp;rsquo;s often no story behind them, because they&amp;rsquo;re often not shared with any information to speak of. They&amp;rsquo;re historic memes, but they never seem to have any attached history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walk on the Vinyl Side</title>
      <link>/2015/04/17/soundalike-records-walk-on-the-vinyl-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 07:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/04/17/soundalike-records-walk-on-the-vinyl-side/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Late rock legend Lou Reed has been in the news lately for a somewhat odd reason. On Monday, Reed&amp;rsquo;s sister wrote about her brother&amp;rsquo;s medical situation during his teenage years—when, the rumor goes, his parents had him undergo electroshock therapy to fend off homosexual urges. (Lou did undergo the controversial therapy treatment, but his sister denies that latent homosexuality was the cause. Speaking of their parents, she explains: &amp;ldquo;They were caught in a bewildering web of guilt, fear, and poor psychiatric care.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>