<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Holidays on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/holidays/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Holidays on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 07:53:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/holidays/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Halloween-Industrial Complex</title>
      <link>/2018/10/17/halloween-stores-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 07:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/17/halloween-stores-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey all, with the just-announced bankruptcy of Sears (which I have a timely piece about) and the liquidation of Toys ‘R’ Us this year, now felt like a good time to relive one of my favorite Tedium pieces, the story of the pop-up Halloween store, complete with refreshed data and the whole bit.
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: When a retail chain or store inevitably shuts down, it leaves an open sore in the real estate sector—with no more Blockbuster nights to be had nor any fresh tenants to be found (Perhaps mattress stores?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fourth Of Why</title>
      <link>/2018/07/04/independence-day-why-july-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 07:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/04/independence-day-why-july-4/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with another piece from Andrew Egan that ponders the details of American independence. Why do we celebrate it exactly this way? I’ll let him take it away.
Today in Tedium: America is still a fairly young country, but old enough to have traditions we don’t question. The World Series, hot dogs, and brutal, drawn out political campaigns are great examples. But as Americans fire up their barbecues and toss some beer into the cooler, it’s worth taking a closer look at one of America’s greatest traditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gifts For Total Strangers</title>
      <link>/2017/12/20/tedium-2017-gift-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 09:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/20/tedium-2017-gift-guide/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: We’re nearing the part of the holiday shopping season when it’s do or die time. If you didn’t do something already, you’re likely scrambling to figure out a Plan B, or maybe even a Plan Q. The gift, no matter the quality, needs to show up by, like, Friday to count as a decent gift for Christmas. Maybe you can swing Saturday—if UPS is willing to swing it for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gifts For People You Don’t Like</title>
      <link>/2016/12/21/tedium-gift-guide-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/12/21/tedium-gift-guide-2016/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: You’ve already checked off the people you know and love. Maybe even the people you know and tolerate. But what about gifts for folks you have a distaste for? That’s where our end-of-season gift guide comes into play. It’s full of obscure stuff and absolute dreck that you may or may not care for. But it’s perfect for breaking off weak friendships, telling a long-lost relative that they probably shouldn’t have returned, or for lowering someone’s overall standard for living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Drop the Ball Again</title>
      <link>/2016/01/01/tedium-trends-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 04:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/01/01/tedium-trends-2016/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Here it is, mofos—issue 100 of Tedium, the Dull Side of the Internet. A year–and 99 issues—ago, we launched this thing by looking ahead at the year 2015. Now 2015 is over, and we need new things to hope and dream for. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about the inane things that will come to define the 2016 calendar year. Despite the focus on the inane, we promise that there will be no mentions of a man whose name rhymes with Monald Mump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas on Repeat</title>
      <link>/2015/12/23/christmas-nostalgia-psychology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 20:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/23/christmas-nostalgia-psychology/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: This is a special Wednesday morning issue, in an effort to get ahead of your holiday travel. We&amp;rsquo;ll be back to our normal Tuesday/Thursday schedule next week.
Today in Tedium: Every year, I have a tradition that I&amp;rsquo;ve followed pretty religiously for more than a decade. Whether in its original form or in its Mystery Science Theater 3000 send-up, I&amp;rsquo;ll watch the junk-culture film Santa Claus Conquers the Martians, despite knowing that the movie is perhaps one of the worst of all time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stocking Stinkers: A Tedium Gift Guide</title>
      <link>/2015/12/21/stocking-stinkers-tedium-gift-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/21/stocking-stinkers-tedium-gift-guide/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Tedium is publishing on an different schedule this week—Monday and Wednesday mornings rather than Tuesday and Thursday evenings—so as to get in your inbox before the holiday rush of out-of-office replies and connecting flights.
Today in Tedium: If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this and still in need of gift ideas for your loved ones, it&amp;rsquo;s already too late. (Did you know that Christmas is on Friday?!) You will find nothing good in your inbox or elsewhere that will save you at this point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time To Drop The Ball.</title>
      <link>/2015/01/01/tedium-time-to-drop-the-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/01/tedium-time-to-drop-the-ball/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Tedium. Here&amp;rsquo;s the first issue of the twice-weekly newsletter that&amp;rsquo;s bound to become the only email you read—just in time for New Year&amp;rsquo;s Day. And in honor of everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite hangover catalyst, we&amp;rsquo;re gonna tell you some crazy crap about the first holiday of the year, as well as the holiday that bookends it. May your internet be functional as you scroll through this message on your electronic reading device of choice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>