<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cell Phones on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/cell-phones/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cell Phones on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/cell-phones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Weaponized Slogan</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/weird-scam-calls-verizon-slogan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/weird-scam-calls-verizon-slogan/</guid>
      <description>[big]A not-so-innocent question: For years, Verizon sold millions of people on the promise of solid cellular phone signals with a simple question. “Can you hear me now?” asked Paul Marcarelli, the living pitchman who spent years in anonymity because of his ties to the brand. (He’s much happier with Sprint.)[/big]
But that question, so innocent-seeming, has become weaponized in the hands of a bunch of scamming robocallers. The Better Business Bureau reported this week that scammers were calling unsuspecting people, asking people on the other end of the line if they can hear them, then hanging up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Copy?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/walkie-talkie-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/walkie-talkie-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: It seems so quaint now, but there was a time when the walkie-talkie was the coolest possible toy you could own (barring, perhaps, Power Wheels). But the invention of the walkie-talkie, which is often used by consumers as either a fun tool or a simple communications device, is a great reminder that this technology used to be so much more fundamental for both businesses and the military.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fake Metal Trees</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/cell-towers-nimby-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/cell-towers-nimby-trees/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Here&amp;rsquo;s a tough problem. People love their cell phones, but the they hate the towers necessary to make those phones function. In fact, they really piss many people off, leading to situations where unnecessary fear-mongering wins the day, or leading people to worry that the towers will become eyesores that destroy their property values—or worse. So how do we get around the issue of these useful-but-ugly devices, anyway?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Dial Up the Weirdness</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/weird-telephone-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/weird-telephone-numbers/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: NYNEX hasn&amp;rsquo;t been a going concern since Smash Mouth was first telling us to walk on the sun. (You might know it under its current post-merger name, Verizon.) But that didn&amp;rsquo;t stop me last night from dialing up a message on my Google Hangouts window with an automated request from a NYNEX operator that I deposit five cents or my phone call will be terminated. (Couldn&amp;rsquo;t do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search By Text</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/google-sms-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/google-sms-history/</guid>
      <description>[big]Back in college, some friends and I found ourselves dealing with a pre-mobile Internet problem. After engaging in activity that is now legal for recreational use in four states, we desperately needed to order pizza. No one knew the number for Domino’s or any other place from memory. And we weren’t immediately near a computer with internet access. Through the disappointment and haze, my friend suddenly remembered, &amp;ldquo;Hey, we can text Google!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Polyphonic Screed</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/cell-phone-ringtone-history-evolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/cell-phone-ringtone-history-evolution/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: For nearly a century, the ring that we associated with a telephone sounded like a variation on this noise. It was simple, consistent. It was boring. And we eventually improved on it, especially in the digital age. When our phones shrank to pocket dimensions and their innards integrated into tiny circuits, it allowed us to redefine exactly a ringtone could be. But that created another problem entirely—the default noise.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>