<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Theft on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/theft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Theft on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 09:14:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/theft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching Labels</title>
      <link>/2017/11/14/retail-theft-ticket-switching/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/14/retail-theft-ticket-switching/</guid>
      <description>Recently I had two pretty good six-packs of beer for $3.99 each. I had scored a deal because I wasn’t picky—the beers were rebranded by a grocery store to celebrate a special event that happened months prior, but the tell was on the cap—these beers, despite the labels, had been brewed by a well-known local craft brewer, and were the same beers that were in the “beer cave” for seven dollars more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security In Stereo</title>
      <link>/2016/11/30/car-stereo-security-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/11/30/car-stereo-security-lessons/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Car stereos play an important role in making traveling in vehicles bearable. They give radio a reason for continued existence. They help to downplay the dull noises of wheels hitting asphalt, to blunt out engine trouble when it arises. But for decades, car stereos have had a problematic feature: They often were the most obvious thing that could be stolen out of a vehicle. Thieves could break a window, pull out the stereo with some basic tools, and sell the device on the black market for a pretty penny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bootleg this issue</title>
      <link>/2015/03/11/bootleg-this-issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/11/bootleg-this-issue/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Last month, a director named Joseph Kahn released the _Mighty Morphin Power Rangers_ film that nobody was asking for—but despite that low ceiling, he more than topped it. The 14-minute short film starred people who have actually been cast in real movies and TV shows (James Van Der Beek and Katee Sackhoff), and took the franchise in a dark, gritty new direction that definitely has nothing in common with the Saved By the Bell-in-costume motif that the franchise was known for in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>