<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Language on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/language/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Language on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/language/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A cromulent exercise</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/a-cromulent-exercise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/a-cromulent-exercise/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox] [big]Today in Tedium: Language is constantly expanding in numerous ways—and in tends to make us uncomfortable to see a new bastardization of the language, even a good one. A recent study noted that the evolution of language has lots in common with the shifts in DNA throughout history, though with one major difference: As a society becomes more insular, the genetic makeup becomes more same-y, but the language becomes more interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Suburban Dictionary</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/sniglet-history-rich-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/sniglet-history-rich-hall/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey guys, Ernie here with an item from a brand new writer for the newsletter, Karen Corday. Today, she has a whole lot to tell you about sniglets. What’s a sniglet? Read on to find out.
&amp;nbsp;
[big]Today in Tedium: Comedian Rich Hall introduced sniglets—“any word that doesn’t appear in the dictionary but should”—in 1982 on the HBO comedy news show Not Necessarily the News. Several books followed, three of which were New York Times best-sellers, along with a daily comic panel and assorted sniglets merchandise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They Should Stop</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/singular-they-grammar-copy-editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/singular-they-grammar-copy-editing/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Of all the turf wars that have complicated the landscape of grammar over the past few hundred years, the most complicated and frustrating may be that of the singular &amp;ldquo;they.&amp;rdquo; It may be the most controversial word use in the English language—because it highlights a hole in the language where a better-fitting word should go. It creates a conflict between writers and editors who want things to follow the natural symmetry of Latin, and people who find they the only logical option for referring to a single person without a gender attached.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>