<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Economy on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/economy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Economy on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/economy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Charmeleon Chaos Theory</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/pokemon-go-spontaneity-charmeleon-chaos-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/pokemon-go-spontaneity-charmeleon-chaos-theory/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: There&amp;rsquo;s something wild about watching people play this game that everyone won&amp;rsquo;t shut up about. And I think it has a lot to do with how it shifts social order in an unexpected way. Here&amp;rsquo;s why: If you see a group of people standing in an otherwise empty park, all from different walks of life, brought together by this game, it looks spontaneous from a distance—totally unplanned, as if they all stumbled there independently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Want to Live Like Common People</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/common-people-rich-to-poor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/common-people-rich-to-poor/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: The greatest six minutes that the British band Pulp ever put to wax pulled off a lot of small victories as it leaped into a larger one. &amp;ldquo;Common People&amp;rdquo; highlighted the lingering definitions of class that the U.K. still hasn&amp;rsquo;t managed to shake; it drew a vibrant character sketch that few songwriters can put together in a single album, let alone a pop song; and it broke through to the mainstream at a time when most British music buyers were focused mostly on Blur and Oasis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Teach Textbooks A Lesson</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/college-textbooks-high-prices-theories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/college-textbooks-high-prices-theories/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: When I recently wrote about airport stores, one of the most interesting (albeit minor) facets of the piece was the fact that airport travelers are generally considered a captive audience, making it easy for shops to jack up prices. But they&amp;rsquo;re far from the only industry sector that knows a thing or two about captive audiences. Just ask textbook publishers; they&amp;rsquo;re experts at this sort of thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trimmed For Space</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/newspaper-newsprint-cuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/newspaper-newsprint-cuts/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
_Editor’s note: Tonight’s Tedium is an updated rerun of a classic issue about the stuff that newspapers get rid of when trying to slim down. Unspoken in this article: Usually, the final step of this process is people. And with the recent sagas of L.A. Weekly and (on the digital side of things) DNAinfo, now felt like a good time to revisit. (If you&amp;rsquo;ve read before, keep reading; there&amp;rsquo;s a new section on newsprint.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>