<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Clothes on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/clothes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Clothes on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 09:24:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/clothes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweating the Ugly Truth</title>
      <link>/2017/12/13/ugly-christmas-sweater-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 09:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/13/ugly-christmas-sweater-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey all, Ernie here with another issue of Tedium by Andrew Egan. Last time he showed up on Tedium, he broke down NYC&amp;rsquo;s now-repealed dancing ban, and before that, he told us about professional cornhole. Now, he&amp;rsquo;s talking sweaters.
Today in Tedium: Some simple inventions took a surprising amount of time to create. Case in point: The can opener was invented 45 years after the can. Reasons for these delays tended to result from technological gaps rather than a lack of Ingenuity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Aren&#39;t You Wearing Corduroy?</title>
      <link>/2017/09/08/corduroy-trend-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/08/corduroy-trend-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: This newsletter/information feed is many things, but it’s not a fashion blog. We’re anything but fashionable. But we do have a tendency to follow trends to at least understand them, so when I saw on Refinery 29 today that “The Corduroy Comeback is in Full Swing,” I knew what was about to happen next in my life. I had to do a deep dive to understand this trend and understand why corduroy, of all fabrics, was important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloth, Meet Plastic</title>
      <link>/2017/08/29/3d-printing-t-shirt-designs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 05:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/29/3d-printing-t-shirt-designs/</guid>
      <description>As I learned a few months ago, creating custom T-shirts is a somewhat-complicated, but often quite useful way of promoting a product or raising money for an endeavor. That’s in part because it’s something that can’t effectively be done in the comfort of one’s home.  Screen-printing is a complicated process, embroidery moreso. You generally need specialized equipment, and the result of doing it at home is usually obvious—you can tell when a shirt was the product of an iron-on design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lint, Filtered</title>
      <link>/2017/07/12/lint-roller-history-dryer-lint/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 07:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/12/lint-roller-history-dryer-lint/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Of the many appliances in our home that create byproducts, is there a more interesting byproduct than dryer lint? I don&amp;rsquo;t ask this to be facetious, nor to overplay its value, but to point out that there&amp;rsquo;s something inherently interesting about lint. It looks fluffy. It feels weird in your hands. And while it&amp;rsquo;s somewhat annoying to get rid of (and yes, you should get rid of it), it nonetheless is a novel object, one that&amp;rsquo;s more interesting and less disgusting than navel lint could ever claim to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Lives In Fabric</title>
      <link>/2017/05/09/t-shirt-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 05:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/09/t-shirt-history/</guid>
      <description>When Amory Blaine decided to pack a T-shirt before heading to boarding school, he set in place a piece of literary history. Amory, the protagonist of F. Scott Fitzgerald’s This Side of Paradise, was the first literary character to use a T-shirt, ever.  “So early in September Amory, provided with ‘six suits summer underwear, six suits winter underwear, one sweater or T shirt, one jersey, one overcoat, winter, etc.,’ set out for New England, the land of schools,” the passage states.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>