<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rock Music on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/rock-music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rock Music on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 04:20:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/rock-music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Trademark Things All Night</title>
      <link>/2017/06/15/gene-simmons-trademark-devil-horns/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 04:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/15/gene-simmons-trademark-devil-horns/</guid>
      <description>Gene Simmons, love him or hate him, has a history of trademarking very common things.  As any fan of the Scottish power-pop group Teenage Fanclub knows, the band’s label, Geffen, had to send a check to Simmons because the cover of the alternative rock band’s Bandwagonesque (which is a stellar album) featured a sack of money with a dollar sign on it—an image that Gene Simmons has long owned the trademark for, as it was the logo of his label, Simmons Records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock &amp; Retro</title>
      <link>/2016/01/29/retro-video-games-featuring-rock-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/01/29/retro-video-games-featuring-rock-stars/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: After Lemmy Kilmister of Motörhead died last month, tributes to the rocker were pretty easy to find—what couldn&amp;rsquo;t you say about this guy, who clearly played a massive role in the history of heavy metal? Perhaps the most curious and interesting tribute came from the world of retro gaming, where fans of Lemmy (a noted gamer) worked diligently to make an Amiga game based on Motörhead available to modern users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take a look at me. Now.</title>
      <link>/2015/11/11/phil-collins-awesome-drummer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2015 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/11/11/phil-collins-awesome-drummer/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Today’s issue is dedicated to a troll named Brian Pee, who posted a mean petition on Change.org to discourage Phil Collins from his upcoming comeback attempt, only to end it when it started getting attention from the media. By the time he did, it had 4,352 signatures—and Pee was trying to laugh it off as a “silly joke” that had gotten out of hand. But before this guy fades into the ethers of dumb meme history, I have to interject here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>