<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Year End on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/year-end/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Year End on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/year-end/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Finish Line In Sight</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/tedium-trends-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/tedium-trends-2017/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Can you believe we’ve been publishing this newsletter for two full years now? (Our anniversary hits on New Year’s Day, just like with my last project, ShortFormBlog.) There’s a good chance that most of you might not be aware of this fact. See, it was only back in January of 2016 that we topped a thousand subscribers, a fact that we revealed in an issue about dollar stores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gifts For Total Strangers</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/tedium-2017-gift-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/tedium-2017-gift-guide/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: We’re nearing the part of the holiday shopping season when it’s do or die time. If you didn’t do something already, you’re likely scrambling to figure out a Plan B, or maybe even a Plan Q. The gift, no matter the quality, needs to show up by, like, Friday to count as a decent gift for Christmas. Maybe you can swing Saturday—if UPS is willing to swing it for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There’s Always Next Year</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/tedium-trends-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/tedium-trends-2018/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: We’re near the start of the new year, and, as a result, I’m closing in on the third anniversary of launching this crazy newsletter. New Year’s Day is kind of an important day for me personally, as it’s the day that I’ve launched two of my projects, including this one. So I’d like to spend this time reflecting back a little bit … and looking forward.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>