<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Commerce on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/commerce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Commerce on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Little off the Top</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/barber-shop-credit-card-transactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/barber-shop-credit-card-transactions/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: If you find yourself in a mom-and-pop barber shop or hair salon of any kind, you might find this common (but annoying) state of affairs in play: Despite the fact that basically every other store on the block accepts credit cards, the barber shop is the lone holdout on that front, forcing consumers who may have otherwise stopped paying cash for most things long ago to hit up the ATM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Machine That Gives You Stuff</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/how-vending-machines-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/how-vending-machines-work/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Vending machines are one of the few things keeping us away from the dream of a cashless society. The devices, which offer up an array of items for a little bit of pocket change, are silent but prevalent. They represent some of our most technologically advanced furniture, and they&amp;rsquo;ll probably always be there for us in our time of need. Today&amp;rsquo;s Tedium discusses their history—along with why, for some reason, they make us want to steal stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big in Brazil</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/sega-master-system-brazil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/sega-master-system-brazil/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Here’s a true fact that will blow your mind—the game-maker Sega started out as an American company, not as a Japanese one. Sure, much of its success came about after it moved to Japan, but it was not by any means a company that necessarily needed Japan, like notable competitors Nintendo, Sony, and NEC did. While the company had one solid era of major success in the American market—where the Sega Genesis went toe-to-toe with the Super NES and became one of the most popular systems of the ‘90s—it was Brazil where Sega really came into its own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delivered To Your Door</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/monthly-subscription-box-delivery-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/monthly-subscription-box-delivery-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Don’t let the talk of content on the cloud fool you. It’s easier than ever to get physical stuff mailed to your duplex nearly every single day of the year. (OK, maybe it’s not Jetsons-easy yet. We’ll get there.) In recent years, that’s led to the rise of subscription box services like Birchbox, BlueApron, and Loot Crate. (Personally, I’m obsessed with Blue Bottle’s biweekly coffee bean delivery service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t mess with the Michelin Man</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/michelin-guide-unusual-side-businesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/michelin-guide-unusual-side-businesses/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: The problem with giving anyone on the street the right to review a restaurant is that he or she can easily be influenced by the wider political or social climate in setting their review score. When it comes to Yelp, the way the wind blows has a ton of influence on the final rating, something Indiana&amp;rsquo;s Memories Pizza learned the hard way when they took a stance in favor of the state&amp;rsquo;s controversial religious freedom law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get off my lawn</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/lawn-care-history-get-off-my-lawn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/lawn-care-history-get-off-my-lawn/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Rich people care about their grass way more than normal people do. Now, rarely is this an issue, but in recent months, the ongoing California drought has made this mundane issue a political one. This week, the city of Rancho Santa Fe became a target of this culture clash after _The Washington Post_ highlighted the water-rationing requirement it soon faces. Local residents aren&amp;rsquo;t happy. “When we bought, we didn’t plan on getting a place that looks like we’re living in an African savanna,” said conservative radio host and local resident Steve Yuhas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gifts For People You Don’t Like</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/tedium-gift-guide-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/tedium-gift-guide-2016/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: You’ve already checked off the people you know and love. Maybe even the people you know and tolerate. But what about gifts for folks you have a distaste for? That’s where our end-of-season gift guide comes into play. It’s full of obscure stuff and absolute dreck that you may or may not care for. But it’s perfect for breaking off weak friendships, telling a long-lost relative that they probably shouldn’t have returned, or for lowering someone’s overall standard for living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give us some credit</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/credit-card-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/credit-card-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: The payment card as we know it is both more popular than ever and, well, dying. According to a 2013 Federal Reserve study, the number of credit card payments in the United States passed the number of check-based payments for the first time, and debit cards passed that mark way back in 2004. But the magnetic swipe isn&amp;rsquo;t long for this world—the industry is switching to a chip-based system this year, and mobile payments threaten to put cards out to pasture soon after that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s a bright idea</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/bright-idea-lighting-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/bright-idea-lighting-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Not many light bulbs can say that they&amp;rsquo;ve managed to survive two World Wars and then some, but the fire department in Livermore, California has managed to keep a life of its own far beyond many of the firefighters that have stayed on call over the past 114 years. The bulb, which the department calls &amp;ldquo;The Centennial Bulb,&amp;rdquo; has only been shut off a few times in its history, and remains working to this day essentially because they go out of their way to never turn the light bulb off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>House of product cards</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/house-of-product-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/house-of-product-cards/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Last weekend, you may have been like me and binged on House of Cards. Along the way, you may have spotted a few direct references to big-name brands … many of which may have paid for the chance to be on screen with Frank Underwood and SPOILER ALERT. But the nature of products on screen and elsewhere have become so prevalent that they just bleed into the action after a while—subliminally influencing us along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Get Sauced</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/ranch-dressing-lets-get-sauced/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/ranch-dressing-lets-get-sauced/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big] Today in Tedium: It was a business model that was destined to happen at some point. With overpriced lunches at fast-casual restaurants and unfortunate late-night fourthmeals at GrubHub alike sporting a certain buttermilk something-or-other at all times, someone was bound to build an entire restaurant concept around it—lest Sriracha get all the attention. And happen it did: Last week, word of a restaurant that includes ranch dressing in every single menu item (besides, we&amp;rsquo;re assuming, the drinks—ranch milkshakes, everyone!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outside-the-Bottle Thinking</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/bottle-design-outside-the-bottle-thinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/bottle-design-outside-the-bottle-thinking/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: It may be the most famous hard-to-read bottle in history. For generations, Dr. Bronner&amp;rsquo;s 18-in-1 Pure Castile Soap has become an essential tool for many looking to stay clean without the extra chemicals they throw into more main-line soaps. But all the benefits that come with the soap (it&amp;rsquo;s highly concentrated, it&amp;rsquo;s effective at getting you clean) are joined by Emanuel Bronner&amp;rsquo;s unusual opinions about just about everything—particularly his unique take on religion called the &amp;ldquo;Moral ABC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PC LOAD LETTER</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/office-supply-stores-seventh-circle-of-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/office-supply-stores-seventh-circle-of-hell/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox] [big]Today in Tedium: It was one of about a million things hidden in the so-called Cromnibus bill that passed late last year. But it&amp;rsquo;s something that reflects a big change in the nature of how offices everywhere get stuff done. Last year, the Government Printing Office got rid of a name that dated back to the Civil War—and became the Government Publishing Office. When the federal government is downplaying its usage of paper and trying to push stuff on the cloud, you know office supply stores are in trouble—and that they are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scanning And Sorting</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/check-processing-history-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/check-processing-history-automation/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: The physical check, for most general purposes, is a sheer relic—basically used mostly for specific big-ticket purchases like rent, it certainly doesn’t have the sex appeal of, say, blockchain-based currencies like Ethereum and Litecoin. But it’s worth keeping in mind that check scanning, sorting, and distribution played an important early role in electronic commerce. Before we got niceties like ACH and magnetic strips, it set the wheels in motion for our highly automated commerce-based world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sodium chloride? So crazy.</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/sodium-chloride-so-crazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/sodium-chloride-so-crazy/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Late last month, 11 cars were damaged—and three crushed—by a giant avalanche of salt that spilled out of a Morton&amp;rsquo;s holding facility in Chicago onto the vehicles sitting at a nearby Acura dealership. The building, which has the company&amp;rsquo;s fairly ironic slogan &amp;ldquo;When it rains it pours&amp;rdquo; emblazoned on it, suffered severe structural damage, and the mess it left behind took more than a week to clean up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stocking Stinkers: A Tedium Gift Guide</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/stocking-stinkers-tedium-gift-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/stocking-stinkers-tedium-gift-guide/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Tedium is publishing on an different schedule this week—Monday and Wednesday mornings rather than Tuesday and Thursday evenings—so as to get in your inbox before the holiday rush of out-of-office replies and connecting flights.
[big]Today in Tedium: If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this and still in need of gift ideas for your loved ones, it&amp;rsquo;s already too late. (Did you know that Christmas is on Friday?!) You will find nothing good in your inbox or elsewhere that will save you at this point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ted Turner&#39;s Satellite Of Love</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/ted-turner-tbs-superstation-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/ted-turner-tbs-superstation-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: For a brief moment in time, independent local television stations held an impressive level of power over the country as a whole. They could share regional messages with national audiences, advertise to millions more people than they ever could on their crusty UHF signals, and punch far above their potential. The era of the superstation is past, but it undeniably had a massive effect on cable television.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The first 12 cost a penny, but …</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/columbia-house-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/columbia-house-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Yesterday, a coworker and good friend of mine revealed to me a fact that made me feel very old. We were talking about Spotify—and his desire not to pay $10 per month for the service—and I referenced Columbia House. He did not know what I was talking about. I was taken aback by this news—I thought everyone knew what Columbia House was! The mail-order CD service (along with its competitor BMG) had a bright moment in the early &amp;lsquo;90s, only to see its business model fall apart thanks to iTunes, and later, Spotify.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This one&#39;s for the wounded</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/history-of-bandages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/history-of-bandages/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Blood is a terrible thing to waste, and for centuries, the ways to stop blood from leaving the body were inefficient at best and not exactly easy to use. But one day, a guy spotted a problem that his wife was having and came up with one of the most brilliant solutions for solving simple injuries that the world had ever seen. And we’ve only kept innovating from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Pyramids Collapse</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/anatomy-scams-when-pyramids-collapse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/anatomy-scams-when-pyramids-collapse/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: It&amp;rsquo;s the oldest scam in the book, and people fall for it all the freaking time. Pyramid schemes of all shapes and sizes have been bilking people out of their hard-earned money for generations, and you&amp;rsquo;re probably gonna get screwed out of your hard-earned money before you even realize it. Today&amp;rsquo;s Tedium is all about scams that leave scars way deeper than all the money stolen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You probably don&#39;t understand watches</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/apple-watch-haters-you-probably-dont-understand-watches/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/apple-watch-haters-you-probably-dont-understand-watches/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: If someone shows you a $10,000 watch, do you understand its inherent value, or do you roll your eyes? Do you think it looks ugly? Do you think that watches that cost a quarter of the average American&amp;rsquo;s salary make any sense whatsoever? Do you see them as an opportunity to play up the class wars a little more? Or are you a techie thinking about watches in terms of that awesome laptop with the USB-C port?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>