<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cable on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/cable/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cable on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 06:44:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/cable/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>That &#39;70s Interactive TV</title>
      <link>/2018/06/27/qube-cable-television-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 06:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/27/qube-cable-television-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with a new writer for Tedium, a guy named Chris Tonn who wanted to talk about an awesome piece of television history that happened in his hometown of Columbus, Ohio. Perhaps it didn’t come to your neck of the woods, but you certainly benefited from it. I’ll let him explain. Thanks all!
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: When Facebook’s Mark Zuckerberg testified about the platform’s privacy concerns in April, one would be forgiven for thinking that this was the first serious lapse in maintaining user data in history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Secret Amiga</title>
      <link>/2016/03/30/cable-prevue-channel-secret-amiga/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 07:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/03/30/cable-prevue-channel-secret-amiga/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In terms of finding out what&amp;rsquo;s on the boob tube at any given time, we&amp;rsquo;ve come a long way from the overly condensed pages of TV Guide. In fact, the magazine was already looking awful obsolete in the 1980s and 1990s, when cable systems around the country began dedicating entire channels to listing TV schedules. Eventually, the approach led to the rise of the set-top box, the power-sucking block that serves as the liaison between you and your cable company.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>