<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Metal on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/metal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Metal on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 09:56:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/metal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How&#39;s Your Soldering Technique?</title>
      <link>/2018/01/26/soldering-technology-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 09:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/26/soldering-technology-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: A lot of people use electronics with little to no idea of what actually happens inside of the little box they have on their desk or in their pockets. Sure, we might talk about the chips inside of that machine, or the processing power, but rarely do we think about the connective tissue holding many of the circuits onto the silicon. That tissue is solder, the meltable filler metal that has existed in one form or another for more than 4,000 years—long before electronics even existed as a modern context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Ned</title>
      <link>/2017/04/18/okilly-dokilly-ned-flanders-metal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 07:20:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/04/18/okilly-dokilly-ned-flanders-metal/</guid>
      <description>If you haven’t been following the modern metal scene, you’ve apparently been missing out on a lot of bands pigging out on pop-culture references in the best way possible.  Last month, a trio of bands went on tour that make Tenacious D look like they’re not high-concept enough. The two co-headliners of the 2017 Mockstrosity Tour were weird enough: Metalachi, a mariachi-themed metal band, shared the stage with Mac Sabbath, a McDonald’s-themed Black Sabbath cover band.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>