<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hot Peppers on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/hot-peppers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hot Peppers on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 23:17:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/hot-peppers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Live Forever</title>
      <link>/2017/01/20/worlds-hottest-peppers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 23:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/20/worlds-hottest-peppers/</guid>
      <description>Eating hot peppers is apparently a great way to avoid having a stroke or heart attack, according to a recent study from the University of Vermont’s Larner College of Medicine. The study found that people who ate hot peppers tended to live longer despite the fact that they had other bad habits, such as smoking.  To be fair, it’s not entirely clear where the direct tie is between the peppers and the longevity (the researchers speculate that capsaicin helps prevent obesity), but going by the crazy logic of studies like this, it only makes sense that we take a logical leap of our own: If you eat increasingly hotter peppers, you should theoretically be able to live forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Hands Are Burning</title>
      <link>/2015/07/31/my-hands-are-burning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/07/31/my-hands-are-burning/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Last night, I learned a difficult fact the hard way—always wear gloves when handling the innards of hot peppers. In my efforts to create homemade jalapeño poppers, I covered my hands in oil to avoid getting stung, only to find that my strategy did not go far enough in preventing the capsaicin from scorching my poor fingers. After considering my options, I decided I would turn this experience into the hottest Tedium issue ever.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>