<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Color on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/color/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Color on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/color/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CMYK All The Way</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/color-printing-lithography-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/color-printing-lithography-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: In the 1990s, after much delay, the newspaper industry’s largest and most prominent newspapers finally started printing most of their pages in color on a regular basis. It was a much delayed phenomenon, driven less by a lack of technology and more by a mixture of cost and tradition. In 1993, The New York Times printed its first page in color, far later than most of the rest of the newspaper industry, and the only other big holdouts at that point were The Wall Street Journal and The Washington Post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live and Let Dye</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/food-coloring-dye-safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/food-coloring-dye-safety/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: Did you hear the news? They&amp;rsquo;re taking the color out of Trix. The General Mills cereal is one of the most recent victims of a move towards more natural food, and in an effort to appease the suddenly health-conscious public, the company will be removing some of the artificial coloring from Trix and all of its other cereals. &amp;ldquo;We wanted to make sure they were still fun vibrant colors that we are providing and the fruity flavor that kids expect,&amp;rdquo; cereal developer Kate Gallager told Good Morning America of the move back in June.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>