<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Comic Books on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/comic-books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Comic Books on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 03:21:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/comic-books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Funny Page</title>
      <link>/2018/02/20/newspaper-funny-pages-rethink-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 03:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/20/newspaper-funny-pages-rethink-2018/</guid>
      <description>At the beginning of 2018, we’re on the cusp of something that might arguably be one of the biggest changes to newspapers in generations: Comic strips, one of the newspaper’s great standbys, are starting to “age out.”  This took quite a long time, but two major things have happened in recent weeks that suggest a major sea change is on the way: the January death of Mort Walker, who was responsible for creating Beetle Bailey and co-creating Hi and Lois, and the decision by cartoonist Guy Gilchrist (who has plenty of years in front of him) to stop doing Nancy, whose final edition published on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Coat of Paint</title>
      <link>/2017/03/02/anthony-dortch-artist-stroke-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 08:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/02/anthony-dortch-artist-stroke-recovery/</guid>
      <description>Last year, Anthony Dortch suffered a major personal setback—surviving a stroke at a young age.  This health struggle threatened to stop Dortch, a Washington, D.C.-based artist, from following his muse, a muse that he’s followed for years with a long-term creative project that’s taken on many layers. Quite literally, in fact.
See, Dortch’s art literally involves painting people to and making them, effectively, into comic book characters—each in different colors to represent different walks of life, with elements of his storytelling highlighting issues of race, gender and sexuality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Taboola of the 1930s</title>
      <link>/2016/06/22/johnson-smith-company-taboola-outbrain-advertising/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/06/22/johnson-smith-company-taboola-outbrain-advertising/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: When I see people complaining about the images and links shared through the &amp;ldquo;content discovery&amp;rdquo; platform Taboola and its cousin Outbrain—something I admittedly have been known to do—I inevitably find myself drawn to the &amp;ldquo;taboo&amp;rdquo; part of the Israeli company&amp;rsquo;s name. Because, if you think about it, it&amp;rsquo;s a really good descriptor of the images you see adding noise to nearly every large site on the internet. They show ways of life and images you wish didn&amp;rsquo;t exist—images of stuff that shouldn&amp;rsquo;t exist, if there was a God.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>