<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Archival on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/archival/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Archival on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 09:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/archival/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pretty Darn Fascinating</title>
      <link>/2018/02/28/pdf-file-format-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/28/pdf-file-format-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Every once of our file formats has a story. The GIF, for example, came to being thanks to a need to serve up images on pokey Compuserve connections with limited RAM. The MP3, meanwhile, was built around the contours of Suzanne Vega’s unaccompanied voice on “Tom’s Diner.” And the ZIP file came to life in a brutal legal battle that was egged on by the whims of BBS users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down With Snippet View</title>
      <link>/2017/06/27/google-books-snippet-view-archival/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 03:29:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/27/google-books-snippet-view-archival/</guid>
      <description>You may or may not have noticed this, but Tedium relies pretty heavily on archival content to exist. This newsletter and publication is not just about offering up weird facts: It&amp;rsquo;s often about introducing facts that have otherwise been forgotten about by the public at large.  Sometimes, this takes me in some interesting directions. An example I regularly cite is my piece on lemon juice squeeze bottles. It was the rare piece I had the chance to mostly write ahead of time, and while there were some incredibly useful starting points on the issue from the Beach Packaging Design, I find it important that, even if an existing resource like this offers a starting point, I spend time doing some digging of my own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey, I Shrunk The Page</title>
      <link>/2016/06/15/microfiche-microfilm-libraries-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/06/15/microfiche-microfilm-libraries-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Do me a favor while you read these opening lines. Pick up your phone, and open up your photos app. Scroll through the many pictures of you, your dumb friends, and your crazy family. Pick a photo—it can be any photo, really, and blow it up so it fills the whole screen. Still with me? Good. Now, tell me, how would you recreate this experience using physical devices alone—where you flipped through thousands of tiny images and blew up a really big one to a size where you can actually read it without (and here&amp;rsquo;s the key part) destroying the original?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>