<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Clothing Tags on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/clothing-tags/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Clothing Tags on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 05:00:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/clothing-tags/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Lives In Fabric</title>
      <link>/2017/05/09/t-shirt-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 05:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/09/t-shirt-history/</guid>
      <description>When Amory Blaine decided to pack a T-shirt before heading to boarding school, he set in place a piece of literary history. Amory, the protagonist of F. Scott Fitzgerald’s This Side of Paradise, was the first literary character to use a T-shirt, ever.  “So early in September Amory, provided with ‘six suits summer underwear, six suits winter underwear, one sweater or T shirt, one jersey, one overcoat, winter, etc.,’ set out for New England, the land of schools,” the passage states.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let &#39;Er Rip</title>
      <link>/2016/06/01/clothing-tags-why-they-exist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 07:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/06/01/clothing-tags-why-they-exist/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Last week, there was a tag on an item on my clothing that was so uncomfortable that there was nothing I wanted to do more than pull it off—to send that miserable tag to a recycling bin where it would never again see the light of day. But that annoying tag got me to thinking: Where did clothing tags come from, and who decided that an annoying tag was an important thing to have on a piece of clothing?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>