<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gimmicks on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/gimmicks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gimmicks on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 09:43:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/gimmicks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kodak Krypto</title>
      <link>/2018/01/11/kodak-cryptocurrency-gimmick/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/11/kodak-cryptocurrency-gimmick/</guid>
      <description>Let’s admit that a long time ago, Kodak was a hugely important company. In fact, it was a Hugely Important Company, on a level rivaled in influence by perhaps only Ford and General Electric in the mainstream.  Everyone takes pictures, and Kodak catered to the masses, iterating repeatedly based on consumer needs.
But, eventually, the company made a bad bet, choosing to protect film at a time when everything was going digital (even though its engineers helped invent some of the basic technology), and that bad bet cost it that lofty position as an important company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smells Like a Stupid Idea</title>
      <link>/2016/01/22/terrible-product-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 09:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/01/22/terrible-product-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Let&amp;rsquo;s say you had a terrible idea. It&amp;rsquo;s not an uncommon thing; we all have them daily. But what if, unlike most people, you were able to get money to create and fund that terrible idea, ensuring that it would turn into a car wreck that the world would be unable to miss? If that&amp;rsquo;s the case, you might want to keep reading, because there&amp;rsquo;s a good chance we might mention your terrible idea for a product in today&amp;rsquo;s Tedium, which is all about terrible product ideas—for example, this novelty bath mat that makes what look like bloody footprints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s Your Gimmick?</title>
      <link>/2015/12/04/television-history-gimmicks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/04/television-history-gimmicks/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: These days, it seems like TV is all about gimmicks: Think reality shows, TV shows that recap the TV shows that literally just aired, limited series designed to recycle old hit shows, and even live theatre productions like The Wiz. TV executives are like P.T. Barnum-style hucksters, willing to try anything to keep us watching. And it&amp;rsquo;s always been that way, honestly—if they can make watching your boob tube into an &amp;ldquo;event,&amp;rdquo; they know they&amp;rsquo;ve sucked you in.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>