<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Retail on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/retail/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Retail on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 07:53:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/retail/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Halloween-Industrial Complex</title>
      <link>/2018/10/17/halloween-stores-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 07:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/17/halloween-stores-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey all, with the just-announced bankruptcy of Sears (which I have a timely piece about) and the liquidation of Toys ‘R’ Us this year, now felt like a good time to relive one of my favorite Tedium pieces, the story of the pop-up Halloween store, complete with refreshed data and the whole bit.
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: When a retail chain or store inevitably shuts down, it leaves an open sore in the real estate sector—with no more Blockbuster nights to be had nor any fresh tenants to be found (Perhaps mattress stores?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Effects</title>
      <link>/2018/09/26/why-airport-stores-are-named-after-tv-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 05:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/09/26/why-airport-stores-are-named-after-tv-networks/</guid>
      <description>Hey all! In lieu of a new piece, tonight’s Tedium is a lightly updated classic edition discussing one of the weirdest phenomena you’ll see at the airport: The naming conventions of the stores. Admit it, you’re curious.
Today in Tedium: When you travel to different places—in the U.S. in particular, perhaps less so outside of it—the airports often feel like they’re designed of a single piece of cloth, despite the fact that they’re most certainly not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gift Of Abstraction</title>
      <link>/2018/01/17/gift-cards-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/17/gift-cards-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: You ever run into a situation where you return something to a store, and the only option that you have available to you is to receive the balance as a gift card? Certainly, this is a frustrating state of affairs, especially if it’s a store you don’t particularly like. Despite that, the gift card—a retail phenomenon that came out of nowhere slightly more than two decades ago to redefine our relationship with gifts—has become a hugely popular industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching Labels</title>
      <link>/2017/11/14/retail-theft-ticket-switching/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/14/retail-theft-ticket-switching/</guid>
      <description>Recently I had two pretty good six-packs of beer for $3.99 each. I had scored a deal because I wasn’t picky—the beers were rebranded by a grocery store to celebrate a special event that happened months prior, but the tell was on the cap—these beers, despite the labels, had been brewed by a well-known local craft brewer, and were the same beers that were in the “beer cave” for seven dollars more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Running Out of Widgets</title>
      <link>/2017/09/13/barnes-noble-third-place-widgets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 05:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/13/barnes-noble-third-place-widgets/</guid>
      <description>Editor’s note: Apple’s revelation on Tuesday that it was rethinking its approach to stores into something akin to a “town square” got me thinking about an old piece I wrote a while back—one that I, ironically, was just interviewed about for Ozy. In lieu of a fresh one, here’s a lightly refreshed 2015 piece that still feels pretty relevant.
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: When physical objects can be turned into a series of bits and bytes and streamed over the airwaves, the result is that stores start running out of things to sell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Booting Up The Cash Register</title>
      <link>/2017/08/04/early-computer-retailers-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 07:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/04/early-computer-retailers-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The modern computer store, as I&amp;rsquo;ve argued in the past, is a bit of a mess. It’s all about the hard sell (in a gigantic box) at the cost of any personality whatsoever. It was so bad that Apple (and later, Microsoft) had to create its own self-branded stores to ensure their products were seen in the proper light. This is kind of painful, of course, because personal computers were really the domain of the hobbyist at first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Tech Hit Retail</title>
      <link>/2017/07/21/point-of-sale-retail-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 07:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/21/point-of-sale-retail-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: If it feels like the the “robots are trying to steal our jobs” meme is a new development, I have some news for you: It’s really not. For decades, automation has been implied to be the cause of—and solution to—all life’s problems. Nowhere is this more the case than in the halls of retail, where automation helped redefine our interaction with shopping in important ways. And those innovations are still happening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Were Selling Computers All Wrong</title>
      <link>/2016/10/12/big-box-retail-computers-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 07:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/10/12/big-box-retail-computers-problems/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The big-box technology store isn&amp;rsquo;t dead yet—and in the case of Best Buy, it&amp;rsquo;s actually doing pretty well, beating financial estimates by a country mile. But as a whole, the concept of the sprawling electronics chain is far from its peak. In fact, it&amp;rsquo;s sort of another shade of the office-supply store. Despite that, investors keep trying to revive this idea. Right now, an investor named Ronny Shmoel is trying to bring Circuit City back to life as a physical presence, roughly seven years after the brand was mothballed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hometown Proud</title>
      <link>/2016/07/08/hometown-proud-iga-independent-grocers-alliance-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/07/08/hometown-proud-iga-independent-grocers-alliance-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: While I don&amp;rsquo;t hold the simple, evocative opinions of small-town life that John Mellencamp does—I think large cities are pretty cool, and I&amp;rsquo;m not sure where I&amp;rsquo;ll die yet—I do appreciate the fact that they exist. But let&amp;rsquo;s be clear: On a competitiveness front, they&amp;rsquo;re at a sheer disadvantage compared to large cities with a much larger reach, more options, and more people. As a result of this, good luck finding a vegan bakery in a small town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Little off the Top</title>
      <link>/2016/02/17/barber-shop-credit-card-transactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 03:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/02/17/barber-shop-credit-card-transactions/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: If you find yourself in a mom-and-pop barber shop or hair salon of any kind, you might find this common (but annoying) state of affairs in play: Despite the fact that basically every other store on the block accepts credit cards, the barber shop is the lone holdout on that front, forcing consumers who may have otherwise stopped paying cash for most things long ago to hit up the ATM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Don&#39;t Win Friends With Salad</title>
      <link>/2016/02/05/salad-bar-history-factoids/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/02/05/salad-bar-history-factoids/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Last month, a major lobbying group for the school lunch industry won a victory that involved salad bars. The School Nutrition Association, feeling the pressure because of what it called arduous nutrition rules, fought for (and won) a slightly more reasonable policy, including rules that specifically allowed schools to continue to offer salad bars to those super-grubby, messy kids. Some local health inspectors tried to veto the salad bars, claiming they created health hazards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;d Buy That for a Dollar</title>
      <link>/2016/01/20/dollar-stores-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 08:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/01/20/dollar-stores-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The dollar store is one of capitalism&amp;rsquo;s greatest gifts to itself, if you think about it. Here&amp;rsquo;s a business model that has, quite brilliantly, taken advantage of the ebbs and flows of supply and demand. It turns products that don&amp;rsquo;t cost a lot to produce into things that actually make money hand over fist, despite the seemingly tight margins. Like companies that turn the liquidation of products into a viable business model and the makers of generic products, dollar stores have their place in the pantheon of retail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frozen Karma&#39;s Gonna Get You</title>
      <link>/2015/12/30/klondike-bar-trademark-lawsuit-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 01:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/30/klondike-bar-trademark-lawsuit-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: What would you do for a Klondike bar? Most people would probably go to the nearest store, buy a package of chocolate-covered ice cream novelties, and make sure that the package eventually finds an icebox—well, as long as they don&amp;rsquo;t finish said novelties first. (That said, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m ashamed of what I did for a Klondike bar&amp;rdquo; makes for a pretty good T-shirt slogan.) The food conglomerate Kraft was willing to do more than most for a Klondike bar: They saw an opportunity to usurp a rising regional dairy treat with their own version, blatantly ripping it off, causing a listeria outbreak, and finding themselves mired in legal battles, all within the span of a few years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas on Repeat</title>
      <link>/2015/12/23/christmas-nostalgia-psychology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 20:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/23/christmas-nostalgia-psychology/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: This is a special Wednesday morning issue, in an effort to get ahead of your holiday travel. We&amp;rsquo;ll be back to our normal Tuesday/Thursday schedule next week.
Today in Tedium: Every year, I have a tradition that I&amp;rsquo;ve followed pretty religiously for more than a decade. Whether in its original form or in its Mystery Science Theater 3000 send-up, I&amp;rsquo;ll watch the junk-culture film Santa Claus Conquers the Martians, despite knowing that the movie is perhaps one of the worst of all time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything Must Go</title>
      <link>/2015/11/25/liquidation-sales-everything-must-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 09:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/11/25/liquidation-sales-everything-must-go/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a great deal on athletic goods and live in a big city on the East Coast, your best option may perhaps be City Sports. The athletic chain, which has been around for more than 30 years, announced earlier this month that it was closing its doors, ensuring this Black Friday is a little bit more of a Bleak Friday for fans of italicized Helvetica type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identifying a Real Fake</title>
      <link>/2015/10/30/why-fake-ids-exist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/10/30/why-fake-ids-exist/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: True story—over the weekend, a restaurant attempted to suggest that I had a fake ID. The ID was a few years old, granted, and it has a small crack in it, but it nonetheless was a real form of identification. The waiter made a joke along the lines of the ID looking like a fake ID he used in college, which seemed like a bad joke until a few minutes later, when the manager came out and asked to look at it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generic Internet Article</title>
      <link>/2015/10/23/generic-products-private-labels/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 07:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/10/23/generic-products-private-labels/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In 1986, about a decade removed from his icon-setting days as lead singer of the Sex Pistols, British punk architect John Lydon released an album with his follow-up band, Public Image, Ltd., that had an extremely high-concept name. In fact, it didn&amp;rsquo;t technically have a name at all. If you bought the record on vinyl, it was called Album; if you bought it on CD, it was called Compact Disc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I got the munchies</title>
      <link>/2015/07/22/i-got-the-munchies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 06:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/07/22/i-got-the-munchies/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: &amp;rdquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t have to go home, but you can&amp;rsquo;t stay here,&amp;rdquo; Grammy award-winning songwriter Dan Wilson frequently sings to the unwashed masses at many a college town bar around the country. (Fun fact: He won that Grammy not with Semisonic, but for writing a Dixie Chicks song.) And often, they don&amp;rsquo;t go home. Instead, they go to restaurants made for easing the next morning&amp;rsquo;s hangovers. Or they do go home, but then they order late-night food that gets delivered to dorm rooms so fast, they freak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big in Brazil</title>
      <link>/2015/07/17/sega-master-system-brazil/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/07/17/sega-master-system-brazil/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Here’s a true fact that will blow your mind—the game-maker Sega started out as an American company, not as a Japanese one. Sure, much of its success came about after it moved to Japan, but it was not by any means a company that necessarily needed Japan, like notable competitors Nintendo, Sony, and NEC did. While the company had one solid era of major success in the American market—where the Sega Genesis went toe-to-toe with the Super NES and became one of the most popular systems of the ‘90s—it was Brazil where Sega really came into its own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outside-the-Bottle Thinking</title>
      <link>/2015/07/15/bottle-design-outside-the-bottle-thinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/07/15/bottle-design-outside-the-bottle-thinking/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It may be the most famous hard-to-read bottle in history. For generations, Dr. Bronner&amp;rsquo;s 18-in-1 Pure Castile Soap has become an essential tool for many looking to stay clean without the extra chemicals they throw into more main-line soaps. But all the benefits that come with the soap (it&amp;rsquo;s highly concentrated, it&amp;rsquo;s effective at getting you clean) are joined by Emanuel Bronner&amp;rsquo;s unusual opinions about just about everything—particularly his unique take on religion called the &amp;ldquo;Moral ABC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Machine That Gives You Stuff</title>
      <link>/2015/06/26/how-vending-machines-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 07:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/26/how-vending-machines-work/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Vending machines are one of the few things keeping us away from the dream of a cashless society. The devices, which offer up an array of items for a little bit of pocket change, are silent but prevalent. They represent some of our most technologically advanced furniture, and they&amp;rsquo;ll probably always be there for us in our time of need. Today&amp;rsquo;s Tedium discusses their history—along with why, for some reason, they make us want to steal stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The first 12 cost a penny, but …</title>
      <link>/2015/06/12/columbia-house-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/12/columbia-house-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Yesterday, a coworker and good friend of mine revealed to me a fact that made me feel very old. We were talking about Spotify—and his desire not to pay $10 per month for the service—and I referenced Columbia House. He did not know what I was talking about. I was taken aback by this news—I thought everyone knew what Columbia House was! The mail-order CD service (along with its competitor BMG) had a bright moment in the early &amp;lsquo;90s, only to see its business model fall apart thanks to iTunes, and later, Spotify.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give us some credit</title>
      <link>/2015/06/10/credit-card-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/10/credit-card-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The payment card as we know it is both more popular than ever and, well, dying. According to a 2013 Federal Reserve study, the number of credit card payments in the United States passed the number of check-based payments for the first time, and debit cards passed that mark way back in 2004. But the magnetic swipe isn&amp;rsquo;t long for this world—the industry is switching to a chip-based system this year, and mobile payments threaten to put cards out to pasture soon after that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This one&#39;s for the wounded</title>
      <link>/2015/05/20/history-of-bandages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/20/history-of-bandages/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Blood is a terrible thing to waste, and for centuries, the ways to stop blood from leaving the body were inefficient at best and not exactly easy to use. But one day, a guy spotted a problem that his wife was having and came up with one of the most brilliant solutions for solving simple injuries that the world had ever seen. And we’ve only kept innovating from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t mess with the Michelin Man</title>
      <link>/2015/04/10/michelin-guide-unusual-side-businesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/04/10/michelin-guide-unusual-side-businesses/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The problem with giving anyone on the street the right to review a restaurant is that he or she can easily be influenced by the wider political or social climate in setting their review score. When it comes to Yelp, the way the wind blows has a ton of influence on the final rating, something Indiana&amp;rsquo;s Memories Pizza learned the hard way when they took a stance in favor of the state&amp;rsquo;s controversial religious freedom law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Get Sauced</title>
      <link>/2015/03/18/ranch-dressing-lets-get-sauced/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/18/ranch-dressing-lets-get-sauced/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It was a business model that was destined to happen at some point. With overpriced lunches at fast-casual restaurants and unfortunate late-night fourthmeals at GrubHub alike sporting a certain buttermilk something-or-other at all times, someone was bound to build an entire restaurant concept around it—lest Sriracha get all the attention. And happen it did: Last week, word of a restaurant that includes ranch dressing in every single menu item (besides, we&amp;rsquo;re assuming, the drinks—ranch milkshakes, everyone!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You probably don&#39;t understand watches</title>
      <link>/2015/03/13/apple-watch-haters-you-probably-dont-understand-watches/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/13/apple-watch-haters-you-probably-dont-understand-watches/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: If someone shows you a $10,000 watch, do you understand its inherent value, or do you roll your eyes? Do you think it looks ugly? Do you think that watches that cost a quarter of the average American&amp;rsquo;s salary make any sense whatsoever? Do you see them as an opportunity to play up the class wars a little more? Or are you a techie thinking about watches in terms of that awesome laptop with the USB-C port?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PC LOAD LETTER</title>
      <link>/2015/02/06/office-supply-stores-seventh-circle-of-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/06/office-supply-stores-seventh-circle-of-hell/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It was one of about a million things hidden in the so-called Cromnibus bill that passed late last year. But it&amp;rsquo;s something that reflects a big change in the nature of how offices everywhere get stuff done. Last year, the Government Printing Office got rid of a name that dated back to the Civil War—and became the Government Publishing Office. When the federal government is downplaying its usage of paper and trying to push stuff on the cloud, you know office supply stores are in trouble—and that they are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sodium chloride? So crazy.</title>
      <link>/2015/01/16/sodium-chloride-so-crazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/16/sodium-chloride-so-crazy/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Late last month, 11 cars were damaged—and three crushed—by a giant avalanche of salt that spilled out of a Morton&amp;rsquo;s holding facility in Chicago onto the vehicles sitting at a nearby Acura dealership. The building, which has the company&amp;rsquo;s fairly ironic slogan &amp;ldquo;When it rains it pours&amp;rdquo; emblazoned on it, suffered severe structural damage, and the mess it left behind took more than a week to clean up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>