<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Video Game History on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/video-game-history/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Video Game History on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/video-game-history/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>An Extra Serving</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/nesticle-history-extras-part-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/nesticle-history-extras-part-one/</guid>
      <description>[big]What a day! My article on Vice&amp;rsquo;s Motherboard this week about the history of NESticle—the Nintendo Entertainment System emulator whose early success paved the way for people to play vintage games on their computers whenever they want—took a while to get past the finish line, and came only after I gave the piece a haircut.[/big]
To augment the story, I’m gonna spend the next couple of Daily Tedium pieces highlighting things I hoped to get into the original piece but were trimmed out because the piece was getting a bit lengthy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australian Rules Nintendo</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/nintendo-beam-software-australia-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/nintendo-beam-software-australia-history/</guid>
      <description>[big]Recently I found myself hanging out in a retro video game store, looking at the cheapo bin at the various titles for the NES and other systems. If you’ve done something similar in the recent past, you’ll know that the cheapo bin will inevitably be filled with lots of sports games. It doesn’t matter if the sports games are well-regarded or even iconic—for whatever reason gamers just don’t want to buy them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retail’s Tech Champion</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/sears-technology-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/sears-technology-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: For a wide variety of reasons, Sears has been a company creaking its way through modern times for longer than many of the people reading this have even been alive. It was a fundamental company to the American revolution—while it didn’t invent the mail-order catalog, it made it a successful business and set the stage for decades of followers. But I don’t want to wallow in Sears’ failings; there are plenty of other outlets for that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Knockoff Game</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/game-boy-knockoff-consoles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/game-boy-knockoff-consoles/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: If you wander through some corners of eBay, or Amazon, or even YouTube, you’ll see ‘em: The clones. Cheap clones. Expensive clones. Clones that play five different systems. Clones that rip off multiple consoles at once. Some, even, open source. But before there were clones, there were cheap knockoffs. And the target of some of the most obvious cheap knockoffs was the Game Boy—a device that, despite its lack of color screen, captured the imagination of millions of 8-year-olds back in the early ‘90s.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>