<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Startups on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/startups/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Startups on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 09:42:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/startups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Google’s Zombie</title>
      <link>/2017/11/15/google-feedburner-rss-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/15/google-feedburner-rss-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Google may be the internet’s greatest murderer of ideas. Between its numerous acquihires, its aggressive approach to launching (and discarding) moonshots, and its tendency to build impressive products only to kill them months later, Google may be the greatest example of a cold-blooded idea killer in history. But one product under the search giant’s lineup strikes my fancy in particular, because Google never killed it, even though everyone thought it would.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Sock Puppets Go To Heaven</title>
      <link>/2017/01/13/pets-dot-com-failure-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/13/pets-dot-com-failure-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: How much was the Silicon Valley bubble responsible for the companies that failed the hardest at the turn of the 21st century? Conversely, how responsible were the basic ideas behind those companies for those failures? Was it really terrible timing, or a stock market that couldn’t support the tech world’s innovation during a hugely creative period? Or did the tech world simply prop up ideas, or at least businesses, that didn’t actually work?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>