<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lawsuits on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/lawsuits/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lawsuits on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 19:04:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/lawsuits/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Unsettled</title>
      <link>/2018/05/01/ticketmaster-live-nation-free-ticket-settlement-boycott/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 19:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/01/ticketmaster-live-nation-free-ticket-settlement-boycott/</guid>
      <description>Nearly a quarter-century ago, Pearl Jam—which had become the biggest band in the world around this time effectively by ignoring the music industry orthodoxy of the time—decided to take on live music’s biggest middleman.  It probably hurt their career to take aim at Ticketmaster, which had become known for charging expensive service fees on every ticket it sold. But the politically minded band did, going so far as to file a complaint with the Justice Department and speak in front of Congress about the problem, something rock bands don’t usually do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Can Dance If We Want To</title>
      <link>/2017/10/31/nyc-dancing-regulation-repeal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 06:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/31/nyc-dancing-regulation-repeal/</guid>
      <description>New York City has long been known as a fairly progressive place, one known as welcoming to ethnic and cultural groups long marginalized by society. So it’s surprising that the city’s laws regarding dancing are more appropriate for a small town in an ‘80s movie.  The city’s long, strange aversion to dancing is finally expected to come to an end on October 31st when a prohibition-era law is expected to be repealed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Annoying Clicking Sound</title>
      <link>/2016/12/07/iomega-zip-disk-click-of-death-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/12/07/iomega-zip-disk-click-of-death-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: As proprietary, non-standardized formats go, Iomega’s Zip drive got a heck of a lot further than most of its competitors. It managed to improve on a format people were used to (the old floppy) just enough that it ensured it’d gain popularity. It fit niches for people who had to share a lot of data. And it even had a sizable base of home users—which was impressive for its time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frozen Karma&#39;s Gonna Get You</title>
      <link>/2015/12/30/klondike-bar-trademark-lawsuit-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 01:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/30/klondike-bar-trademark-lawsuit-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: What would you do for a Klondike bar? Most people would probably go to the nearest store, buy a package of chocolate-covered ice cream novelties, and make sure that the package eventually finds an icebox—well, as long as they don&amp;rsquo;t finish said novelties first. (That said, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m ashamed of what I did for a Klondike bar&amp;rdquo; makes for a pretty good T-shirt slogan.) The food conglomerate Kraft was willing to do more than most for a Klondike bar: They saw an opportunity to usurp a rising regional dairy treat with their own version, blatantly ripping it off, causing a listeria outbreak, and finding themselves mired in legal battles, all within the span of a few years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Game Genie Generation</title>
      <link>/2015/07/01/the-game-genie-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/07/01/the-game-genie-generation/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: For kids of a certain age, the Game Genie was a life-changer. Literally. It could change the number of lives you had in whatever cartridge you put it on, as well as do a bunch of other crazy things to the game you were playing. It provided a thrill that we&amp;rsquo;ve kinda gotten away from as video games have grown more complex, but the device leaves behind a rich legacy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>