<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Psychology on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/psychology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Psychology on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 20:41:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/psychology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas on Repeat</title>
      <link>/2015/12/23/christmas-nostalgia-psychology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 20:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/23/christmas-nostalgia-psychology/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: This is a special Wednesday morning issue, in an effort to get ahead of your holiday travel. We&amp;rsquo;ll be back to our normal Tuesday/Thursday schedule next week.
Today in Tedium: Every year, I have a tradition that I&amp;rsquo;ve followed pretty religiously for more than a decade. Whether in its original form or in its Mystery Science Theater 3000 send-up, I&amp;rsquo;ll watch the junk-culture film Santa Claus Conquers the Martians, despite knowing that the movie is perhaps one of the worst of all time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Get Profane</title>
      <link>/2015/09/16/lets-get-profane-nature-of-swearing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 07:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/09/16/lets-get-profane-nature-of-swearing/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Profanity is good for the soul. It encourages you to let out frustrations that might have driven you crazy, and (if used correctly) it might just help you win an argument. These reasons were probably front of mind for Willian Barboza, who wrote three profanities on the traffic ticket that the city of Liberty, New York gave him. (He also changed the town&amp;rsquo;s name to &amp;ldquo;Tyranny.&amp;rdquo;) The result of that profanity—ironic, considering the town&amp;rsquo;s name—is that Barboza was arrested and jailed for the action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Livin&#39; on the Edge</title>
      <link>/2015/05/29/art-decency-shocking-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/29/art-decency-shocking-content/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: That sound you hear is Tipper Gore&amp;rsquo;s eyes bulging out. On June 1, a new video game called Hatred aims for the absolute edge of decency and taste, with a plot line that essentially involves killing innocent people en masse for no good reason other than to push forth the destruction of society. &amp;ldquo;We say ‘yes, it is a game about killing people’ and the only reason of the antagonist doing that sick stuff is his deep-rooted hatred,&amp;ldquo; its makers state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Despite All My Rage …</title>
      <link>/2015/02/25/anger-rage-psychology-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2015 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/25/anger-rage-psychology-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: 1995 was the year that Billy Corgan got in our faces and shouted, &amp;ldquo;Despite all my rage, I am still just a rat in a cage!&amp;rdquo; And since then, we&amp;rsquo;ve only gotten angrier as a society. All of our failings are tied to that inner rage that makes for good drama … but causes the most damage. Last week, uber-scientist Stephen Hawking called aggression &amp;ldquo;the human failing I would most like to correct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quitting is OK</title>
      <link>/2015/01/30/andrew-sullivan-quitting-is-ok/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/30/andrew-sullivan-quitting-is-ok/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Everyone is addicted to something. There are certain addictions that we carry around with us that eventually need to be put to bed. Andrew Sullivan, one of the greatest (and most controversial) pundits of the early 21st century, was addicted to blogging. Sully, who&amp;rsquo;s was one of the most popular online writers of his era and the first big-name writer to devote his life to the practice, announced that he was quitting his longtime platform, The Dish, on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>