<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>New Years Day on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/new-years-day/</link>
    <description>Recent content in New Years Day on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 10:16:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/new-years-day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Millennium Blues</title>
      <link>/2017/12/27/y2k-pop-culture-oddities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 10:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/27/y2k-pop-culture-oddities/</guid>
      <description>Hey all, Ernie here with another piece from contributor David J. Buck—who’s taking a break from covering outsider music to bring you a tale of twisted culture at the turn of the century … and the dawn of the new millennium.
Today in Tedium: Remember the terrifying, tumultuous, insert-scary-adjective-here year leading up to the new millennium? Did the uncertainty of the what the future held keep you up at night? Do you feel a sense of nostalgia for NBC’s Y2K: the Movie?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Drop the Ball Again</title>
      <link>/2016/01/01/tedium-trends-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 04:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/01/01/tedium-trends-2016/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Here it is, mofos—issue 100 of Tedium, the Dull Side of the Internet. A year–and 99 issues—ago, we launched this thing by looking ahead at the year 2015. Now 2015 is over, and we need new things to hope and dream for. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about the inane things that will come to define the 2016 calendar year. Despite the focus on the inane, we promise that there will be no mentions of a man whose name rhymes with Monald Mump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time To Drop The Ball.</title>
      <link>/2015/01/01/tedium-time-to-drop-the-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/01/tedium-time-to-drop-the-ball/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Tedium. Here&amp;rsquo;s the first issue of the twice-weekly newsletter that&amp;rsquo;s bound to become the only email you read—just in time for New Year&amp;rsquo;s Day. And in honor of everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite hangover catalyst, we&amp;rsquo;re gonna tell you some crazy crap about the first holiday of the year, as well as the holiday that bookends it. May your internet be functional as you scroll through this message on your electronic reading device of choice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>