<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crime on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/crime/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crime on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 07:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/crime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>They Steal Horses, Don’t They?</title>
      <link>/2018/05/09/horse-thief-detective-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/09/horse-thief-detective-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Often, theft is something very much defined by its era. In the past decade, smartphone thefts have grown rampant (occasionally leading to cute stories that cross borders and cultures), and it wasn’t too long before that when objects like sneakers and car stereos were the targets of robbery. Perhaps the target of the criminal activity changes—perhaps someone’s taking aim at your cryptocurrency at the moment—but the basic concept (what’s yours is now mine) doesn’t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fishing For Checks</title>
      <link>/2018/04/18/mail-fishing-theft-phenomenon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/18/mail-fishing-theft-phenomenon/</guid>
      <description>When I described to my wife the nature of the story I’m about to tell you about, I called it a “phenomenon,” to which she responded asking whether or not it was too strong a word to describe what sounds like a truly bizarre form of theft.  But as it turns out, knuckleheads using strong glue and string to pull letters (or, let’s be honest, checks) out of mailboxes is a phenomenon called “mail fishing,” and it’s a phenomenon that highlights the weaknesses of a system that is already struggling to keep up with the modern day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ink-Stained Headlines</title>
      <link>/2017/03/16/printer-ink-criminal-activity-theft/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 07:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/16/printer-ink-criminal-activity-theft/</guid>
      <description>You know what’s a terrible racket? Printer ink. Driven up by artificial markets and complex, incompatible cartridge systems, printers have become one of the most depressing parts of any computing experience—especially if you own one at home.  And they bring out the worst behavior in companies. Hewlett-Packard last year had a scandal on its hands after it added digital rights management to its printers, then turned it off after people complained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security In Stereo</title>
      <link>/2016/11/30/car-stereo-security-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/11/30/car-stereo-security-lessons/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Car stereos play an important role in making traveling in vehicles bearable. They give radio a reason for continued existence. They help to downplay the dull noises of wheels hitting asphalt, to blunt out engine trouble when it arises. But for decades, car stereos have had a problematic feature: They often were the most obvious thing that could be stolen out of a vehicle. Thieves could break a window, pull out the stereo with some basic tools, and sell the device on the black market for a pretty penny.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>