<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vinyl on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/vinyl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vinyl on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 09:47:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/vinyl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Books on Vinyl</title>
      <link>/2016/02/19/audiobooks-blind-vinyl-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 09:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/02/19/audiobooks-blind-vinyl-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: It&amp;rsquo;s the great challenge of a newsletter editor when they hear this phrase—&amp;rdquo;hey, this newsletter would be really good as a podcast!&amp;rdquo; I understand the demand for things like this, because people love sounds running into their ears when they&amp;rsquo;re on the go, and you have to physically press your fingers down on your phone to read Tedium. But I&amp;rsquo;m way more clever and way less likely to say &amp;ldquo;like&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;y&amp;rsquo;know&amp;rdquo; when I write things down, so that&amp;rsquo;s why this comes in a text format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genuine Imitation Leather</title>
      <link>/2015/09/09/genuine-imitation-leather/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/09/09/genuine-imitation-leather/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: As any cursory watch of an episode of Happy Days will tell you, we&amp;rsquo;re obsessed with the look of leather—but perhaps not fans of the way leather is produced. Much like a meal at McDonald&amp;rsquo;s or a fur coat, we&amp;rsquo;re more impressed with the final result without any worries about where it came from—because thinking about where it came from potentially raises some heavy ethical questions. For the plastics industry, it&amp;rsquo;s long been the perfect opening for a synthetic alternative, and there are plenty of varieties out there, most made from variations of vinyl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tape Deck Heart</title>
      <link>/2015/08/21/magnetic-tape-revival/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2015 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/08/21/magnetic-tape-revival/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: When&amp;rsquo;s the big comeback for magnetic tapes coming around, anyway? These days, vinyl is making a serious comeback with the public. Even Taylor Swift is selling a ton of vinyl records these days. But in a world where streaming and optical discs are more common than ever, the magnetic tape—which arguably has as much nostalgic hipster cachet as the vinyl record, and across a variety of formats at that—hasn&amp;rsquo;t seen nearly as much love.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>