<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hotel Psychology on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/hotel-psychology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hotel Psychology on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 07:40:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/hotel-psychology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tales From The Minibar</title>
      <link>/2018/04/04/why-are-hotel-minibars-expensive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/04/why-are-hotel-minibars-expensive/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: More than 20 years ago, a reporter for The New Republic took a sharp stab at a famous conservative conference by implying nefarious activity that involved a minibar. “The minibar is open and empty little bottles of booze are scattered on the carpet,” the reporter wrote of the 1997 Conservative Political Action Conference (CPAC). “On the bed, a Gideon Bible, used earlier in the night to resolve an argument, is open to Exodus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Vacancy</title>
      <link>/2016/03/25/hotel-psychology-amenities-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2016 07:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/03/25/hotel-psychology-amenities-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: When we go to a hotel, especially a nice one where we&amp;rsquo;re dropping a couple hundred bucks for a single night&amp;rsquo;s stay, we expect a lot out of the experience—something nicer than our schlubby apartment, preferably with an exotic or urban locale easily in sight. But when we open the door, no matter how ugly the motel we end up staying in turns out to be, there are always a handful of things that are always consistent—the TV and remote, the well-made bed, the cheap artwork on the walls.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>