<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English Language on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/categories/english-language/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English Language on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 09:55:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/english-language/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Suburban Dictionary</title>
      <link>/2018/03/02/sniglet-history-rich-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 09:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/02/sniglet-history-rich-hall/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, Ernie here with an item from a brand new writer for the newsletter, Karen Corday. Today, she has a whole lot to tell you about sniglets. What’s a sniglet? Read on to find out.
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: Comedian Rich Hall introduced sniglets—“any word that doesn’t appear in the dictionary but should”—in 1982 on the HBO comedy news show Not Necessarily the News. Several books followed, three of which were New York Times best-sellers, along with a daily comic panel and assorted sniglets merchandise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They Should Stop</title>
      <link>/2016/08/05/singular-they-grammar-copy-editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 07:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/08/05/singular-they-grammar-copy-editing/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Of all the turf wars that have complicated the landscape of grammar over the past few hundred years, the most complicated and frustrating may be that of the singular &amp;ldquo;they.&amp;rdquo; It may be the most controversial word use in the English language—because it highlights a hole in the language where a better-fitting word should go. It creates a conflict between writers and editors who want things to follow the natural symmetry of Latin, and people who find they the only logical option for referring to a single person without a gender attached.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Made Scunthorpe Famous</title>
      <link>/2016/07/27/scunthorpe-problem-profanity-filter-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 07:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/07/27/scunthorpe-problem-profanity-filter-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The internet&amp;rsquo;s many messy algorithms—the things that tell a server somewhere how to handle a given issue—have never been perfect. To the contrary, they break often, partly because humans remain far more capable to find the edge cases of a software platform than software developers are of anticipating them. Nowhere is this better exemplified than with the nature of swearing, a sport that bots have always been more prudish about than the public as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enuf is Enough</title>
      <link>/2015/11/20/word-lobby-orthography-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 09:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/11/20/word-lobby-orthography-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: In their own quiet ways, spelling and grammar are each forms of lobbying. Language is one of the few facts of everyday life that started out as a variety of opinions on what things should be called. And those opinions, like a diamond pressed into form, slowly molded into a definitive shape. But there&amp;rsquo;s a limit to how much we&amp;rsquo;re OK with as a society—hence the popularity of dictionaries and style guides, which draw up a map for how we use words on a daily basis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>