<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pizza on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/pizza/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pizza on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 07:47:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/pizza/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Not Delivery, It’s …</title>
      <link>/2018/04/18/frozen-pizza-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 07:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/18/frozen-pizza-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Have you heard the good news? Frozen food is back, baby! After years on the sidelines, Healthy Choice is seen as a healthy choice again; people looking to put on a home banquet are looking towards Banquet; hungry men are choosing Hungry Man. The future is frozen, and if you’re not warming up to cold foods, you’re not cool. With tonight’s Tedium, I’d like to focus on one specific kind of food put on ice, the frozen pizza, and why it’s become an icon of prepared American food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Memedom</title>
      <link>/2018/03/01/every-headline-on-the-internet-meme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 20:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/01/every-headline-on-the-internet-meme/</guid>
      <description>On Monday, something happened which I feel the need to address. I found a picture of a particularly depressing piece of pizza on Twitter. I saw a couple other folks making jokes about this pizza. And I decided to make a joke about something I’m very familiar with: Journalism.  Little did I know that I would be responsible for creating a tweet so viral that it had the potential to crash my phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special Delivery</title>
      <link>/2017/05/16/unique-pizza-delivery-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 07:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/16/unique-pizza-delivery-methods/</guid>
      <description>As I highlighted recently, Amtrak trains are rife with delays—which can be blamed on a combination of failing infrastructure and a lack of track ownership.  We can’t solve the problem of Amtrak very easily, but pizza is a pretty nice salve.
On Sunday, a mechanical failure knocked out a train on the way to Washington from New York City, eventually leading passengers to have to switch trains. While they were stuck waiting in the Wilmington, Delaware, area, someone stuck on the underfunded transit medium got the idea to call a local pizza place for nourishment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>