<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sound Blaster on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/sound-blaster/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sound Blaster on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 07:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/sound-blaster/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Some Noise</title>
      <link>/2018/05/11/sound-blaster-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/11/sound-blaster-history/</guid>
      <description>Hey all, Ernie here with a classic (though lightly updated) Tedium piece about one of the defining pieces of ’90s computer technology: The Sound Blaster. Crank it up!
Today in Tedium: Before we embraced MP3s as the official noise of the internet (taking the place of screechy modems), it took a while before the synthesized notes of our musical past could be modulated through the inner-workings of a computer. Some of our earliest computers, for example, could only make very basic bleeps and bloops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Some Noise</title>
      <link>/2016/02/10/creative-sound-blaster-sound-card-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 05:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/02/10/creative-sound-blaster-sound-card-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Before we embraced MP3s as the official noise of the internet (taking the place of screechy modems), it took a while before the synthesized notes of our musical past could be modulated through the inner-workings of a computer. Some of our earliest computers, for example, could only make very basic bleeps and bloops. But in 1989, everything changed when a Singaporean company called Creative Technology hit upon the perfect approach for synthesizing sound.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>