<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stuff on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/stuff/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stuff on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/stuff/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatching a Plan</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/hatchimal-alternatives-eggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/hatchimal-alternatives-eggs/</guid>
      <description>Currently, it’s easier to get a nest-style bed for a Hatchimal than it is to get an actual Hatchimal.
Not that the buzzy toys may be worth it anyway, based on the class-action lawsuit filed against the toymaker Spin Master after the toy animals failed to hatch.
All of this makes me wonder whether we might be better off buying something else that hatches and hoping for the best.
Fortunately, it’s possible—and it’s a great workaround for a notable policy Amazon has against selling live animals in most cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Talk About Forks, Baby</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/weird-forks-to-buy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/weird-forks-to-buy/</guid>
      <description>[big]Utensils are the great equalizer. &amp;ldquo;I once saw a forklift lift a crate of forks, and it was way too literal for me,&amp;rdquo; late philosopher and one-liner king Mitch Hedberg apparently once said. It may be the deepest thing ever said about forks.[/big]
That&amp;rsquo;s because we generally don&amp;rsquo;t talk about forks very often, or utensils in general, really.
That&amp;rsquo;s despite their extreme prevalence. Everyone has to use a utensil at some point in their lives, whether they&amp;rsquo;re sporks, forks, spoons, or chopsticks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Live Forever</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/worlds-hottest-peppers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/worlds-hottest-peppers/</guid>
      <description>[big]Eating hot peppers is apparently a great way to avoid having a stroke or heart attack, according to a recent study from the University of Vermont’s Larner College of Medicine. The study found that people who ate hot peppers tended to live longer despite the fact that they had other bad habits, such as smoking.[/big]
To be fair, it’s not entirely clear where the direct tie is between the peppers and the longevity (the researchers speculate that capsaicin helps prevent obesity), but going by the crazy logic of studies like this, it only makes sense that we take a logical leap of our own: If you eat increasingly hotter peppers, you should theoretically be able to live forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terrible Digital Trinkets</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/terrible-novelty-usb-drives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/terrible-novelty-usb-drives/</guid>
      <description>[big]Not too long ago, I acquired a pretty useful USB drive that is a combination of large and small. It’s large because it has 128 gigabytes of storage, which comes in handy for my experiences testing Chromium OS and Ubuntu on my MacBook Pro. It’s small because it’s designed to recede in my laptop. It’s about the size of the tip of my finger. It’s, of course, incredibly easy to lose.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>