<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Live Animals on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/live-animals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Live Animals on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 05:58:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/live-animals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stable Rent</title>
      <link>/2017/09/20/horse-ownership-nyc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 05:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/20/horse-ownership-nyc/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Hey guys, Ernie here with the latest piece from Andrew Egan, who previously told us about going to the lobby and grabbing ourselves a treat. This time, he&amp;rsquo;s makin&amp;rsquo; hay.
&amp;nbsp;
Today in Tedium: People have powerful connections to their pets. They brighten our day and wrack us with worry when they get sick. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s dogs, cats, parrots, or snakes, people will go to extreme lengths to accommodate their pets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatching a Plan</title>
      <link>/2017/02/04/hatchimal-alternatives-eggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 07:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/02/04/hatchimal-alternatives-eggs/</guid>
      <description>Currently, it’s easier to get a nest-style bed for a Hatchimal than it is to get an actual Hatchimal.
Not that the buzzy toys may be worth it anyway, based on the class-action lawsuit filed against the toymaker Spin Master after the toy animals failed to hatch.
All of this makes me wonder whether we might be better off buying something else that hatches and hoping for the best.
Fortunately, it’s possible—and it’s a great workaround for a notable policy Amazon has against selling live animals in most cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Taboola of the 1930s</title>
      <link>/2016/06/22/johnson-smith-company-taboola-outbrain-advertising/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/06/22/johnson-smith-company-taboola-outbrain-advertising/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: When I see people complaining about the images and links shared through the &amp;ldquo;content discovery&amp;rdquo; platform Taboola and its cousin Outbrain—something I admittedly have been known to do—I inevitably find myself drawn to the &amp;ldquo;taboo&amp;rdquo; part of the Israeli company&amp;rsquo;s name. Because, if you think about it, it&amp;rsquo;s a really good descriptor of the images you see adding noise to nearly every large site on the internet. They show ways of life and images you wish didn&amp;rsquo;t exist—images of stuff that shouldn&amp;rsquo;t exist, if there was a God.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>