<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</title>
    <link>/tags/microsoft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Microsoft on Tedium: The Dull Side of the Internet.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 07:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/microsoft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Double Trouble</title>
      <link>/2018/09/05/disk-compression-stacker-doublespace-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 07:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/09/05/disk-compression-stacker-doublespace-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: As anyone who has ever owned a smartphone with the minimum amount of flash storage knows, space runs out fast, and once you realize you need more than you’ve allocated yourself, it’s way too late. In computing, this is a story that goes back decades, to a time when giant platters walked (OK, rolled) the Earth. But while running out of storage space on a 16-gig iPhone is annoying, it’s at least reasonable; you can put stuff on the cloud, and if the space drives you nuts, you can always upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clippy Couture</title>
      <link>/2018/08/31/clip-art-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 07:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/31/clip-art-history/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Art is everywhere. It’s easier to access than it’s ever been. All you need to do to access art is to turn on your search engine of choice—Google, Flickr, Giphy—and start searching. The hard part of this, of course, is that this art is often copyrighted, and while there are cases where the copyright is a bit more loosey-goosey (thank you, Creative Commons), many times, if you’re trying to print off a flyer or newsletter for your local sect of Satanists, you might need a free alternative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Internet&#39;s Final Frontier</title>
      <link>/2018/07/06/smart-bathroom-technology-toilets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 07:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/06/smart-bathroom-technology-toilets/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Thanks to the ever-shrinking nature of our electronics, the internet can go literally anywhere. I mean anywhere. It fits in your bag, appears on your television set, shows up on your desk, it makes a great window into your fridge, and even appears in your pocket. And since it fits in your pocket, that means you can take it inside the bathroom, making it a worthy replacement for a certain series of books we covered earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Killed The Encyclopedia?</title>
      <link>/2017/07/14/who-killed-the-encyclopedia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 07:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/14/who-killed-the-encyclopedia/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: The CD-ROM was sold to the public and the world as a way to bring interactive multimedia experiences into our homes. (Certainly, that&amp;rsquo;s how the magazine world tried to sell it.) But beyond that, it was a sheer amount of storage for a price that was insane to consider at the time. And that meant that some of the earliest products produced for the CD-ROM format were of the reference variety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Code Is Junky</title>
      <link>/2017/03/03/microsoft-frontpage-history-web-design-wysiwyg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 09:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/03/microsoft-frontpage-history-web-design-wysiwyg/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: As I’ve covered a few times in the past, the hard part about any budding technology—whether it’s delivering packages, driving down interstate highways, or beaming satellite signals to homes around the country—is the infrastructure, how easy that infrastructure is to use. The internet is obviously a pretty key example of this issue in action, with products like WebTV and CompuServe imagining a specific direction for reading content online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Internet Will Be Televised</title>
      <link>/2016/09/14/webtv-history-20th-anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 07:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/09/14/webtv-history-20th-anniversary/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Terrible product ideas are a dime a dozen, but what about ideas that are fascinating, and perhaps executionally sound, but conceptually flawed? How often do they come about? And how often is it that they stick around the market for 17 years, despite fairly limited public interest? Such is the case of WebTV, the set-top device that allowed you to surf a television-optimized version of the web. On September 18, 1996—20 years ago this week—a startup firm released a device that meant to bring the internet to the living room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The History of Internet Explorer Hatred</title>
      <link>/2015/03/20/the-history-of-internet-explorer-hatred/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/20/the-history-of-internet-explorer-hatred/</guid>
      <description>Today in Tedium: Your browser says a lot about you. It highlights your socioeconomic class, your knowledge of computing, your inherent biases, and even the likelihood that you’re a failure at just about everything. For many people, using Internet Explorer was a sign that your relative or co-worker didn’t “get it,” and their resistance to changing browsers was a sign that they never would. Developers, without knowing your name or your circumstances, would curse you under your breath, because your clicking on their website made their job harder.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>