<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Retail Quirks on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/retail-quirks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Retail Quirks on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/retail-quirks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Effects</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/why-airport-stores-are-named-after-tv-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/why-airport-stores-are-named-after-tv-networks/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey all! In lieu of a new piece, tonight’s Tedium is a lightly updated classic edition discussing one of the weirdest phenomena you’ll see at the airport: The naming conventions of the stores. Admit it, you’re curious.
[big]Today in Tedium: When you travel to different places—in the U.S. in particular, perhaps less so outside of it—the airports often feel like they’re designed of a single piece of cloth, despite the fact that they’re most certainly not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching Labels</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/retail-theft-ticket-switching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/retail-theft-ticket-switching/</guid>
      <description>[big]Recently I had two pretty good six-packs of beer for $3.99 each. I had scored a deal because I wasn’t picky—the beers were rebranded by a grocery store to celebrate a special event that happened months prior, but the tell was on the cap—these beers, despite the labels, had been brewed by a well-known local craft brewer, and were the same beers that were in the “beer cave” for seven dollars more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Halloween-Industrial Complex</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/halloween-stores-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/halloween-stores-history/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
Hey all, with the just-announced bankruptcy of Sears (which I have a timely piece about) and the liquidation of Toys ‘R’ Us this year, now felt like a good time to relive one of my favorite Tedium pieces, the story of the pop-up Halloween store, complete with refreshed data and the whole bit.
&amp;nbsp;
[big]Today in Tedium: When a retail chain or store inevitably shuts down, it leaves an open sore in the real estate sector—with no more Blockbuster nights to be had nor any fresh tenants to be found (Perhaps mattress stores?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Were Selling Computers All Wrong</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/big-box-retail-computers-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/big-box-retail-computers-problems/</guid>
      <description>[whitebox]
[big]Today in Tedium: The big-box technology store isn&amp;rsquo;t dead yet—and in the case of Best Buy, it&amp;rsquo;s actually doing pretty well, beating financial estimates by a country mile. But as a whole, the concept of the sprawling electronics chain is far from its peak. In fact, it&amp;rsquo;s sort of another shade of the office-supply store. Despite that, investors keep trying to revive this idea. Right now, an investor named Ronny Shmoel is trying to bring Circuit City back to life as a physical presence, roughly seven years after the brand was mothballed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>